<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ArrayOfDialogue xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Recruiter_SO_Prequest_01</Key>
    <Value>Welcome to Sorobor Academy. How can I help you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Recruiter_SO_Prequest_a_01</Key>
    <Value>I’m interested in signing up. What can you tell me about the Academy?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Recruiter_SO_Prequest_02</Key>
    <Value>Sorobor Academy is the greatest house of learning in Aurai. Whether you want to learn history, mathematics, literature or the art of commanding an army, we have a place here for you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Recruiter_SO_Prequest_03</Key>
    <Value>Our trade networks also dwarf those of even Levant. So, if you’re looking to strike it rich, or develop connections with the best and brightest in Aurai, you’re also definitely in the right place.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Recruiter_SO_Prequest_04</Key>
    <Value>Sorobor values individuals who are flexible, ambitious, and autonomous. If you think you have what it takes to learn how to be a true credit to all Aurai, you are welcome here.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Recruiter_SO_Prequest_b_01</Key>
    <Value>I hear there’s a Ley Line in Harmattan. Where can I find it?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Recruiter_SO_Prequest_05</Key>
    <Value>Try the door on the other side of the hall, the one with the crystals. It’s free to use. If you want to learn how to tap into your newfound power, we would be glad to teach you, for a fee.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Recruiter_SO_Prequest_a_04</Key>
    <Value>I’m in! How do I sign up?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Recruiter_SO_Prequest_06</Key>
    <Value>Excellent, first sign here an-.....Wait, hold on. I recognize that name...This could be troublesome...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Recruiter_SO_Prequest_a_06</Key>
    <Value>Is there a problem?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Recruiter_SO_Prequest_07</Key>
    <Value>Unfortunately yes. According to my ledger, your bloodline is currently under a rather complex Blood Price. That...Complicates things a little.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Recruiter_SO_Prequest_a_07</Key>
    <Value>There’s got to be a way to resolve this.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Recruiter_SO_Prequest_b_07</Key>
    <Value>Of course this damned Blood Price follows me everywhere I go...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Recruiter_SO_Prequest_08</Key>
    <Value>No need to get upset, this happens frequently enough. All applicants with a Blood Price on their family need to be approved through the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Provost of Academic Affairs&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Give him this note, and he’ll look into this for you. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;He should be in the library&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Recruiter_SO_Prequest_09</Key>
    <Value>There’s nothing more I can do on my end to sign you up. This is the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Academic Provost’s&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; business now. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;You’ll find him in the library&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, I believe.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Recruiter_SO_Prequest_c_01</Key>
    <Value>I’m just looking around.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Recruiter_SO_Prequest_10</Key>
    <Value>Very well. Enjoy your visit!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Prequest_01</Key>
    <Value>I’m afraid I’m swamped with work right now, visitor. I have a foot-high stack of theses to read and judge. Like this one on...Oh my. Unless he’s got a veritable stack of evidence here, this one’s destined for the rejection pile.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Prequest_02</Key>
    <Value>Hmm? Yes, I’m the Academic Provost. What’s this about? As you can see I’m quite busy.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Prequest_02_a</Key>
    <Value>I was told to speak with you about getting admitted into the Academy.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Prequest_03</Key>
    <Value>Hmm? Let me see that note...Ah. Yes, that would complicate your admittance here. Under normal circumstances, a Blood Price wouldn’t be too big a deal, but given how you are the only member of your bloodline, and only make a lighthouse keeper’s salary...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Academic_SO_Prequest_a_03</Key>
    <Value>You think I’m a risk, don’t you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Academic_SO_Prequest_b_03</Key>
    <Value>I’m a seasoned adventurer now, I’ll have you know!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Prequest_04</Key>
    <Value>Don’t worry, we aren’t going to turn you away without giving you a chance. If we did that for every risky venture we wouldn’t be half as rich and influential as we are. You’ll just have to prove that you’re an asset first, that’s all.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Prequest_05</Key>
    <Value>I’d advise you to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;seek out a sponsor&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Your most likely bets are the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Arcane Dean&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Military Dean&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, or the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Provost of Mercantile Affairs&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. They’re the ones most inclined to be receptive to you at the moment.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Prequest_06</Key>
    <Value>Our Arcane Dean, &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mr Turnbull&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, should be around the Academy somewhere. The Military Dean, &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Victor Berthelot&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, should be around the Military District in the North-East of town.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Prequest_07</Key>
    <Value>And if your adventuring has made you rich, Our Mercatile Provost &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sekiguchi Meiko&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; would most definitely be interested in sponsoring you. She should be around the Marketplace.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Prequest_08</Key>
    <Value>Once you’ve gotten a sponsor, &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;please have a word with Headmaster Salaberry&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Show him a sponsor signature, and you’re in.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Prequest_09</Key>
    <Value>Ah, so you’ve gotten a sponsor’s signature. Excellent. Just one last step and your complex admittance case will be resolved. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please have a word with Headmaster Salaberry&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, and you’ll officially be a Soroborean!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Academic_SO_Prequest_a_08</Key>
    <Value>Thanks for the help.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Academic_SO_Prequest_b_08</Key>
    <Value>I’d better be! I hate being given the runaround like this!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Prequest_10</Key>
    <Value>Well, shoo. You have no further business with me. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;It’s in the headmaster’s hands now&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Headmaster_SO_Prequest_01</Key>
    <Value>Ah, you. I’ve been expecting you. I see the Academic Provost has approved your application.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Headmaster_SO_Prequest_a_01</Key>
    <Value>Yeah, after making me jump through a bunch of hoops.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Headmaster_SO_Prequest_02</Key>
    <Value>If that’s a dealbreaker for you, then you might want to rethink your application to Sorobor Academy. If you intend to rise through the ranks here, you will need to put in a lot of time and diligence, whether academic or mercantile.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Headmaster_SO_Prequest_b_01</Key>
    <Value>I’m eager for the opportunity, sir.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Headmaster_SO_Prequest_03</Key>
    <Value>You’ll go far here with an outlook like that. If you intend to rise through the ranks here, you will need to put in a lot of time and diligence, whether you try seek success in the academic or mercantile realms.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Headmaster_SO_Prequest_04</Key>
    <Value>You’ve proven you can be of use, so I have little doubt you’ll be able to find yourself a place here, even with your blood price payments to manage. But I do wish to impress upon you what joining Sorobor means...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Headmaster_SO_Prequest_05</Key>
    <Value>When the Scourge came knocking on Harmattan’s gates, and the old nobles argued and delayed, it was us who seized the day. We formed a meritocracy, based on what each of us could do to reinvent the future. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Headmaster_SO_Prequest_06</Key>
    <Value>We took our humble university, and turned it into a power to rival the entirety of the Blue Chamber Collective. To join us is to commit to being a part of that legacy. Are you prepared to rise to that challenge?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Headmaster_SO_Prequest_07</Key>
    <Value>You must be bold, curious, and driven to earn not just your daily bread, but also the respect of your peers. We have a reputation for being the ones who can solve any problem, and acquire any item, and we expect you to live up to it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Headmaster_SO_Prequest_commit</Key>
    <Value>(&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;This is a turning point in my life...Am I ready to commit to the Sorobor Academy?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Headmaster_SO_Prequest_a_07</Key>
    <Value>Sign me up. I’ll surpass those expectations!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Headmaster_SO_Prequest_b_07</Key>
    <Value>I need to think this over.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Headmaster_SO_Prequest_08</Key>
    <Value>Then, done. Welcome to Sorobor Academy, [PlayerName]. As of this moment, you are an apprentice here.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Headmaster_SO_Prequest_09</Key>
    <Value>Very well. Your application will remain open. Return whenever you feel you are ready. There’s no need to rush.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Headmaster_SO_Prequest_10</Key>
    <Value>Take your time getting to know the town and academy. Once you’re settled in, try to make yourself useful, and see if one of our Deans will take you under their wing. That will be all, [PlayerName]. Off you trot.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Prequest_01</Key>
    <Value>Could you hold on just a minute please? I’m in the middle of noting down some essential things about a theory I have. I promise I’ll give you my full attention some other time, alright?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Prequest_02</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Prequest_a_02</Key>
    <Value>I need a sponsor in order to join the Academy. Can you help?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Prequest_03</Key>
    <Value>I’m not sure that I-...Oh hey! I know that name! My sister-in-law Helen has written about you! I hear that you got involved with a large trade expedition on just a Lighthouse keeper’s pay. You must be exceptionally resourceful to pull that off!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Prequest_a_03</Key>
    <Value>It would have been more impressive if the ship didn’t sink on home’s doorstep...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Prequest_04</Key>
    <Value>Anytime you take a risk, you roll the dice. Sometimes they come up snake eyes. That’s life.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Prequest_b_03</Key>
    <Value>That I am, sir.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Prequest_05</Key>
    <Value>And confident too! Yes, I think your presence at the academy will be a boon to us all.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Prequest_06</Key>
    <Value>Well, I’m convinced you might be of use to us. Tell you what, &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;If you’re a mage, I’ll sponsor you&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. If you’re not one already, feel free to use our Ley Line, it’s open to the public.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Prequest_07</Key>
    <Value>Ah, you’re a mage! I can tell by the way you carry yourself. Alright, let me sign that for you...And done! Bring that back to the Academic Provost, and you should be let in without any further trouble.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Prequest_01</Key>
    <Value>Ah, a visitor to Harmattan! Welcome! My name is Victor Berthelot, I am the Dean of military affairs here. Never forget, the Antique Plateau is an extremely dangerous place. If you need protection, the Wolfgang Mercenaries are there to help!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Prequest_02</Key>
    <Value>Oh, you poor soul, they’re making you run all over the place for this aren’t they? Alright, I’ll do you a favor and sign off on this. Just to keep this an even trade though, I’ll need a little something in return.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Prequest_03</Key>
    <Value>&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Come back with a Power Coil&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; and I’ll gladly become your official sponsor. You should be able to get one from the marketplace, or from one of the Human-shaped Golems out there. Be wary, those Golems pack a punch!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Military_SO_Prequest_a_02</Key>
    <Value>I’ve got the item you wanted!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Prequest_04</Key>
    <Value>Ah, excellent. I hope you didn’t get hurt on my account. There, your form is signed! I hope to work with you again in the future, [PlayerName]! If there’s ever anything you need, I’ll be here for you. Go get ‘em!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercantile_SO_Prequest_01</Key>
    <Value>Amba, good visitor! Welcome to the Harmattan Market! Feel free to sample goods from all over the continent, all in one convenient place.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercantile_SO_Prequest_02</Key>
    <Value>A sponsor, hmm? Let me see that...Ah. You have a Blood Price, no? Then this will be simple. Prove to me you can stay on top of your finances, and this is a done deal as far as I’m concerned.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercantile_SO_Prequest_03</Key>
    <Value>&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bring me 200 Silver&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; as a down payment on your tuition, and I’ll sign that sponsorship form for you, no further questions asked.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Mercantile_SO_Prequest_a_03</Key>
    <Value>Deal. Here’s your money.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercantile_SO_Prequest_04</Key>
    <Value>A wise investment on your part. Here you are, your form is signed. Now, go forth and generate wealth and power for us all, Apprentice!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Prequest_01</Key>
    <Value>So, you’re here to join the Academy too, eh? Just got done signing up, myself. The name’s Desy.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Prequest_02</Key>
    <Value>And that guy over there is Artois. He’s a bit of a softy, nearly got himself killed fighting a single Pistol Shrimp by the lake after all, but I feel like he’s got potential. With a heart like his, a little more discipline and strength might almost make a hero outta him.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>player_buddy_SO_Prequest_02_a</Key>
    <Value>So, where are you from?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Prequest_03</Key>
    <Value>Born and raised in a war camp near Karaburan. I spent my childhood sharpening swords, making traps and gathering medicine for the warriors, and my youth learning to face the Scourge in combat.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Prequest_04</Key>
    <Value>Our camps and traps and patrols are what keep so many Scourge confined to the Gates of Catharsis. While Elatt takes much of the credit, and I will admit he’s a big help, it’s our blood and sacrifice that keeps the worst of the hordes at bay.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>player_buddy_SO_Prequest_02_b</Key>
    <Value>I take it you have a plan in mind for your time here?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Prequest_07</Key>
    <Value>I’ll side with any branch that’ll help me get the connections I need. I’m not here so much to learn things, but rather to meet the people I’ll need to know to make sure my war camp is well-supplied and the most prepared to face the Scourge.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Prequest_08</Key>
    <Value>I’ve got my eyes on the Military branch, but if I turn out to be a natural at Alchemy, or Engineering, or Magic, I’ll pick whatever works for me. Like I said, I’m not here to play student. I’ve got a lot of people back home who are counting on me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>player_buddy_SO_Prequest_02_c</Key>
    <Value>Well, good luck!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Prequest_09</Key>
    <Value>Likewise. Look after yourself out there. The only one you can trust to keep you safe is yourself and your sword arm!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Prequest_01</Key>
    <Value>Ah, here to join Sorobor as well? I’m Artois Sutherland, pleasure to make your acquaintance!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Prequest_02</Key>
    <Value>That girl over there, Desy, we were in the same caravan to Harmattan when we got ambushed by a Pistol Shrimp near the lake. She’s real strong. That said, she cares more than she lets on. She’s surprisingly gentle when applying first aid to people!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Prequest_03</Key>
    <Value>I’m from the Sutherland family. We’re pretty big back in Berg, although we haven’t quite been so prominent in the last decade or two. How Rissa Aberdeen manages to keep so much influence with such a narrow bloodline, I will never understand.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Prequest_04</Key>
    <Value>Mother would have preferred I try to study to become a chamberlord, or join my cousin Julius as a hunter. But becoming a member of Sorobor Academy and helping create the future of Aurai through research and trade has long been my dream.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Prequest_05</Key>
    <Value>I’m hoping to join the History Division and become a Scholar or even someday a Master there. There is just so much of our ancestor’s lives buried under the carnage the Scourge unleashed, and I want to know all of it!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Prequest_06</Key>
    <Value>Then again, Victor Berthelot was already kind enough to help me out. Maybe it’s a sign that I’m more suited to join the Military Branch. Being a hero, and protecting the innocent would suit me just fine too.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Prequest_07</Key>
    <Value>Good luck to you too! If you sign up to join Sorobor as well, I hope we get to work together! More hands make for light work, after all!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Caravaneer_SO_Prequest_00_a</Key>
    <Value>What’s it like, working for Sorobor Academy?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Caravaneer_SO_Prequest_01</Key>
    <Value>Ah! Yes, I can see why you’d be curious. Sorobor Academy is a storied institution, going back to even before the Scourge. It’s more than just a place of learning. It’s where the greatest minds in Aurai congregate to shape its future.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Caravaneer_SO_Prequest_02</Key>
    <Value>As long as you can put in the work, you’ll get quite a bit out of it. Connections, wealth...It asks a lot of hard work out of you, and years of effort before you see a payoff, but I can’t imagine living any other way.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Caravaneer_SO_Prequest_02_a</Key>
    <Value>I’d like to join Sorobor Academy. How would I go about doing that?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Caravaneer_SO_Prequest_03</Key>
    <Value>Hmmm...I’d recommend you &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;concentrate on not losing your lighthouse first&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, [PlayerName]. Speak with me once that’s been resolved, one way or another.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Caravaneer_SO_Prequest_04</Key>
    <Value>A worthy goal, [PlayerName]. Yes, I think you’d fit right in. I’m planning on making the journey to our home city, Harmattan right now, actually! If you’d like a lift, I can absolutely take you along!  ...For a fee, of course.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Caravaneer_SO_Prequest_05</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Caravaneer_SO_Prequest_06</Key>
    <Value>Best of luck to you on your journey, my friend! </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>HighClassInnNews_SO_Prequest_01</Key>
    <Value>Welcome to Harmattan, friend! If you want to speak with anyone important, I’d advise you to visit Sorobor Academy. If you’re into magic, they’ve got a Ley Line open for public use too!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>LowClassInnNews_SO_Prequest_01</Key>
    <Value>A visitor huh? Make sure you take a walk around the central market. There are plenty of wonderful goods from all across Aurai for sale there!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Up_Ladder_01</Key>
    <Value>Just when I’m done evaluating one stack of theses, another one shows up. It’s enough to make even a bookworm like myself begin to detest paperwork!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_AskHelp_SO_Up_Ladder_01</Key>
    <Value>I’m looking for work, is there anything I can do?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Up_Ladder_02</Key>
    <Value>Go bother one of the Deans. I’m sure they have plenty of grunt work for an apprentice like you to do. Don’t come bother me again.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>TimeSink_SO_Up_Ladder_player_a</Key>
    <Value>So, is there a place for me in your branch of the academy?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>TimeSink_SO_Up_Ladder_player_b</Key>
    <Value>I’ve done what you asked!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Up_Ladder_01</Key>
    <Value>I was so close in that last experiment, I can feel it. If I can just find the right runic combination...Hmm? Well, what do you want? I’m rather preoccupied right now.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Up_Ladder_02</Key>
    <Value>Actually, yes, there’s something you can do for me. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;I need a Purity Potion&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. I use them when doing experiments on the Scourge, and I’m fresh out.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Up_Ladder_03</Key>
    <Value>Excellent work, apprentice. Keep this up and you’ll make Initiate in a matter of months!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>TimeSink_SO_Up_Ladder_player_c</Key>
    <Value>Wait...Months?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Up_Ladder_04</Key>
    <Value>There aren’t any shortcuts in Sorobor, no matter what &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Victor&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; will tell you. The man seems too eager to snap up new apprentices for my liking, even if he is the best at what he does. I don’t like it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>History_SO_Up_Ladder_01</Key>
    <Value>Every artifact and ruin we discover is a new source of heartbreak. We’ve lost so much because of the Scourge. Not just people, but culture, literature and who knows what else. We owe it to those who lost their lives to remember what they lived for.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>History_SO_Up_Ladder_02</Key>
    <Value>You want to help me? You? Then stay out of any ruins you might find, and whatever you do, don’t plunder anything you find there!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>History_SO_Up_Ladder_03</Key>
    <Value>There are valuable historical relics out there and uncultured goons making off with them for some quick silver will just rob everyone else of their history. Stick to driving off bandits. They’re even worse when it comes to respecting our shared history.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_History_SO_Up_Ladder_03_a</Key>
    <Value>How can I become an initiate if I can’t take on all the jobs that I can?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>History_SO_Up_Ladder_04</Key>
    <Value>Go pester &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Victor Berthelot&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; if you want a hand out! We don't exactly have much crossover in our fields of study, but I only hear good things about him. And he’s often willing to take a chance on new initiates.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Naturalist_SO_Up_Ladder_00</Key>
    <Value>It’s always so upsetting when an upstart apprentice goes and runs their mouth! That potion of extreme stamina restoration would have sold like poutine on a winter’s day. So what if overuse leads to heart failure? That’s no reason to ban it!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Naturalist_SO_Up_Ladder_01</Key>
    <Value>Ah, you’re one of our new apprentices. Be a dear and give me a hand, will you? &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Gather 2 Nightmare Mushrooms and give them to my man at the low-class inn. His name’s Pete&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. I’ll pay you for your trouble.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Naturalist_SO_Up_Ladder_02</Key>
    <Value>Oh, and by the way, make sure to let him know his “order of spices has arrived”. Got it? Because that’s what this is. A spice delivery. Got that?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Naturalist_SO_Up_Ladder_02_a</Key>
    <Value>Aren’t those...Poisonous?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Naturalist_SO_Up_Ladder_03</Key>
    <Value>That’s what some of my alchemists say, but I also hear it’s a very widely used spice in meat stews, so who’s to say, eh?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Naturalist_SO_Up_Ladder_04</Key>
    <Value>Thank you for handling that delivery! Here, your cut.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Naturalist_SO_Up_Ladder_04_a</Key>
    <Value>I get the feeling that you just had me deliver poison to a bandit...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Naturalist_SO_Up_Ladder_04_b</Key>
    <Value>I didn’t just participate in some kind of drug deal, did I?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Naturalist_SO_Up_Ladder_05</Key>
    <Value>How RUDE of you! This is a perfectly legitimate spice trade! It’s completely ethical and above board!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Naturalist_SO_Up_Ladder_06</Key>
    <Value>Anyway, keep it up, Apprentice! With an attitude like that, you’ll make Initiate by the end of the year!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Naturalist_SO_Up_Ladder_06_a</Key>
    <Value>End of the year?! There’s no quicker way?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Naturalist_SO_Up_Ladder_07</Key>
    <Value>Well, &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Victor Berthelot&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; sometimes takes on Initiates pretty quickly. Don’t believe any of the rumors about him, mind you. The other Deans just want to poach his Initiates once he whips 'em into shape.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Shady_SO_Up_Ladder_01</Key>
    <Value>Ugh, I hate Harmattan. Too crowded, too many people. Too many potential places for a threat to hide. I feel so much safer outside the walls. At least out there, I know everything is a threat.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Shady_SO_Up_Ladder_01_a</Key>
    <Value>Your...Err...Order of spices has arrived?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Shady_SO_Up_Ladder_02</Key>
    <Value>Ah, ‘bout time. Gimme. Go tell our mutual friend thanks, will you? Now shoo.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Shady_SO_Up_Ladder_01_b</Key>
    <Value>Erica sent me to deliver some Nightmare Mushrooms.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Shady_SO_Up_Ladder_03</Key>
    <Value>Quiet, you fool! Didn’t she tell you the pass-phrase?  *Sigh*  Fine, hand ‘em over and shoo, will you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Engineer_SO_Up_Ladder_01</Key>
    <Value>Oh hey there. Don’t mind me, I’m just juggling about 4 potential projects right now. There’s so much lost technology that I desperately want to reverse engineer and surpass!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Engineer_SO_Up_Ladder_02</Key>
    <Value>Oh, perfect timing, then! I'm testing the effect of &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Leyline Water&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; as Golem fuel. Can you run down to the Mana Lake and fetch me some?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Engineer_SO_Up_Ladder_03</Key>
    <Value>That’s exactly what I need. Good work, Apprentice! Some of my initiates will be very thankful for your work!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Engineer_SO_Up_Ladder_04</Key>
    <Value>Eh, maybe eventually. You’re getting a little ahead of yourself, Apprentice. You should take some classes, prove you know something. Do some business, prove you can make something, you know? You’re trying to jump the curve by a couple months!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Engineer_SO_Up_Ladder_05</Key>
    <Value>Well, you can always see if &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Victor Berthelot’s&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; got anything needing doing...I don’t particularly get on well with him, but he does often take an interest in new Apprentices. He might be able to give you a leg up.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_Wait</Key>
    <Value>I’m currently dealing with a difficult contract with the Wolfgang Mercenaries, Apprentice. I don’t have time right now. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Come back in a bit, alright&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_00</Key>
    <Value>Ah, one of the new Apprentices. Looking for some work? The Military branch is always looking for some new brave souls to protect Aurai!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Military_SO_Up_Ladder_00_a</Key>
    <Value>I’m looking for something big. Something that will lift me out of Apprenticeship.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_01</Key>
    <Value>The other academy branches are yanking your chain, aren’t they? Typical. I feel like everyone in this damned academy enjoys taking advantage of the new hires and demands things of them with nary a thought for their well being.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_02</Key>
    <Value>Well, don’t worry, I’ll look out for you. I was in your shoes once. In fact, work with me and I can guarantee that I’ll take care of your monthly Blood Price payments for you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_03</Key>
    <Value>You say that you’re ready to take on something on the Initiate level, do you? Alright, I have JUST the task for you. I won’t sugar coat it, the job is going to be dangerous. But if you pull this off, I’ll recommend you for a much faster promotion.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Military_SO_Up_Ladder_a_03</Key>
    <Value>I’m in. What do you need me to do?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Military_SO_Up_Ladder_b_03</Key>
    <Value>No thanks. I’ll do this the right way.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_04</Key>
    <Value>Excellent. I’ve got two other apprentices, Artois and Desy, on jobs out in Antique Plateau. They’re handling two deliveries that have ended up a little...Complicated. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;I’d like you to run support for them and help them out with both their tasks&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_05</Key>
    <Value>Well, enjoy being a glorified errand runner for the next year or two, then. The only way to really rise up in the Academy is to be bold and ambitious. Those who try to do things “the right way” never really go anywhere.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_06</Key>
    <Value>First, a package was supposed to come from Sirocco, but the courier was robbed by bandits up near the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;northern lake&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. I need you to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;head up there, find the bandits, and recover the package&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. They’re likely to be hunkered down in some &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;ruins&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_07</Key>
    <Value>I don’t care if you use violence or diplomacy. Just recover the box. It’s about this small, and has the wax seal of Sirocco on it. It’s confidential, so do NOT open it. Got that, [PlayerName]?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_08</Key>
    <Value>Secondly, I have a sensitive delivery that needs picking up. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Head out from the south elevator, then cut north-east through the downtown ruins. There should be a tiny ruin that’s up against the Harmattan cliff wall.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; My contact should be inside.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_09</Key>
    <Value>The...ah...Person I’m expecting is a little...Different. Don’t attack them or do anything rash. I just want the item with as little trouble as possible. Just give him this glass bottle, and let him do the rest.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_10</Key>
    <Value>I sent Artois to deal with the bandits and Desy to deal with the cave pickup. Not that I’m too worried, but I’d sleep better at night knowing there’s someone double checking their work. Like I said, it’s a dangerous mission. Good luck!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_11</Key>
    <Value>Ah, good, you’re all back. Looks like it’s a good thing I sent you along, [PlayerName]. Do you have the little box from Sirocco?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Military_SO_Up_Ladder_11_a</Key>
    <Value>Yes I do. We really need to talk about what you asked us to do.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_12</Key>
    <Value>Come now, I did tell you it would be a dangerous mission, didn’t I?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_13</Key>
    <Value>The wax seal on the box is broken...I sincerely hope that was the bandits doing and not yours. I told you the contents were confidential!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Military_SO_Up_Ladder_13_a</Key>
    <Value>So we don’t have the right to know what kind of product we’re delivering?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_14</Key>
    <Value>We are just an intermediary, so no, we don’t. All that matters to us is that we get the goods where they need to go. What the goods actually are is irrelevant. You’ll sleep better not poking your nose into these kinds of things.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Military_SO_Up_Ladder_14_a</Key>
    <Value>The bandits broke the seal, yeah.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_15</Key>
    <Value>Really, now... And yet the contents of the box are still inside. I find it very unlikely that they’d have left Tsar Stones inside if they knew what was in it. Well, whatever. The goods are here, that’s all that matters.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_16</Key>
    <Value>Ah, the box is still sealed, excellent. I hope the bandits gave you no trouble?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Up_Ladder_11</Key>
    <Value>They gave ME trouble, that’s for sure. I’m sorry, boss. I should have been more vigilant.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_17</Key>
    <Value>Tsk tsk, sounds like you need some training, Artois. Fortunately, you’re in the right place for it. I’ll have you in fighting shape in no time.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_18</Key>
    <Value>And what about my contact at the cave? Did you get the blood from him?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Military_SO_Up_Ladder_18_a</Key>
    <Value>It turned into a fight. The damn creature nearly killed me!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_19</Key>
    <Value>Dammit, I warned you not to-...And now the bottle is cracked! There’s going to be even less for the Naturalist branch to work with. Use your heads next time, you fools!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Military_SO_Up_Ladder_18_b</Key>
    <Value>I have your bottle of blood. And I killed the Butcher afterwards.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_20</Key>
    <Value>You...You what?! I...Alright, consider me quite impressed. I’m going to send someone to bring the corpse in for research. Well done, both of you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Military_SO_Up_Ladder_20_a</Key>
    <Value>You’re...Not mad that it ended up like that?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_21</Key>
    <Value>Why would I be mad? You accomplished your objective, brought me the blood, AND you rid the world of an extremely dangerous creature all in one trip. I’d say everyone wins here.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Military_SO_Up_Ladder_18_c</Key>
    <Value>Yes. I have the blood. What in Elatt’s name do you need this for?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_22</Key>
    <Value>As for what these things are for, I don’t know, and I don’t plan to know. I was paid a great deal of money to ensure these goods get where they need to be, and that’s all any of us need to know. Discretion is a skill all three of you should learn.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_23</Key>
    <Value>Well then, I’ll be keeping a close eye on all of you. One or two more jobs like this, and I’ll take you under my wing as Initiates. For now, enjoy a very happy payday with the promise of many more to come!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_17</Key>
    <Value>Don’t bother. I’m done doing anything for you. You were working with the Butcher of Men, the most monstrous Scourge there is, and you don’t even care why your client arranged for it. That goes beyond merely being irresponsible!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_18</Key>
    <Value>I cannot work under someone who is willing to work with humanity’s greatest enemy. Especially not if they can’t even justify their actions!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_24</Key>
    <Value>Think for a moment, girl.  Do you think I would have made this arrangement and not have taken measures to ensure he does not leave the region alive? I informed the Wolfgang Mercenaries about this delivery before even sending you off.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Up_Ladder_12</Key>
    <Value>Oh. That’s not so bad then. They’re professionals, I’m sure they’ve already got that thing cornered by now!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_25</Key>
    <Value>They will make certain that the Butcher does not leave the region alive. Not unless he gets extremely lucky. So you see, I didn’t make a deal with him. I used him. There’s a difference.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_19</Key>
    <Value>I don’t see much difference, to be honest. Nothing good can come from trading with that monster.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_26</Key>
    <Value>Tsk, you should really consider the benefits of diplomacy, dear. Besides, I’m working on solutions to slaughter the Scourge with greater efficiency already. Would your family want you to walk away from the opportunity to destroy the lot of them?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_20</Key>
    <Value>I know they wouldn’t want me to work with a man who is willing to do business with the creature that killed several of them. And I think the Headmaster might agree.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_27</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_28</Key>
    <Value>There’s no need to be so nasty, girl. Besides, no one would believe a fresh Apprentice over a Dean who’s put in years of loyal service keeping the Antique Plateau safe and secure.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_29</Key>
    <Value>And even if anyone DID...Well, I’m just asking you to consider the harm that might be done to innocent people if our military’s ability to fight the Scourge is compromised, that’s all.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_21</Key>
    <Value>Ugh, fine! But I’m still done taking orders from you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Military_SO_Up_Ladder_29_a</Key>
    <Value>I’m out too. I’m not working with someone who is willing to work with the Butcher!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_30</Key>
    <Value>Well, see, that’s a shame. Because if you’re out, who is going to keep paying off your Blood Price, hmm? I guarantee you that no one else in this organization will help a liability like yourself. ...I’ll make sure of that.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_31</Key>
    <Value>Your only option for success is to stick with me, [PlayerName]. So I suggest you stop questioning me and do as you’re told. I could make life VERY miserable for you if you don’t.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Military_SO_Up_Ladder_29_b</Key>
    <Value>As long as our deal is still good, I’ll stay.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_32</Key>
    <Value>Ah, the deal about your Blood Price? Don’t worry, I’ve already sent along this month’s payment. You can trust me, [PlayerName]. I look after my assets.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Military_SO_Up_Ladder_33</Key>
    <Value>In any case, you all completed your missions. Enjoy your reward. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Come back in a few days&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; and I’ll have plenty more work for you to do, [PlayerName]. I have some very interesting research being done that I think you and Artois will enjoy.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bandit_SO_Up_Ladder_01</Key>
    <Value>Well, well, another visitor. Well, you know what they say, dark is the night without a moon...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Bandit_SO_Up_Ladder_01_a</Key>
    <Value>Is that some kind of pass-phrase?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bandit_SO_Up_Ladder_02</Key>
    <Value>If it was, you clearly don’t know the response, now do ya? Start talking, or start emptying those pockets, tourist, before we empty ‘em for ya!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Bandit_SO_Up_Ladder_01_b</Key>
    <Value>There’s a package you intercepted. Hand it over. This doesn’t have to get violent.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bandit_SO_Up_Ladder_03</Key>
    <Value>Yeah, boyo over there had the same story. Well, you ain’t gettin’ it, it’s ours now. ...Although...Our operatin’ budget’s been a little tight for a while...Alright, I can see parting with that item and ONLY that item if you bring me what I we need.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bandit_SO_Up_Ladder_04</Key>
    <Value>So, &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;resupply us with 5 sticks of ordinary Meat Jerky, one waterskin, an Iron Claymore and an Iron Halberd&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. You bring those, we trade you the little box, and we let your little buddy go.  Sound fair?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Bandit_SO_Up_Ladder_04_a</Key>
    <Value>That’s surprisingly fair. Alright, I’ll be back with your goods.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bandit_SO_Up_Ladder_05</Key>
    <Value>Elatt be praised, someone who’s reasonable and doesn’t think they’re some kind of badass! Alright, we’ll be waiting for you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Bandit_SO_Up_Ladder_04_b</Key>
    <Value>No deal. Hand it over or I’ll crack your skulls.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bandit_SO_Up_Ladder_06</Key>
    <Value>Well, can’t say we weren’t reasonable. Whupp ‘em, gang!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Bandit_SO_Up_Ladder_04_c</Key>
    <Value>Here’s your resupply. Now hand over that box with Sirocco’s wax seal on it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bandit_SO_Up_Ladder_07</Key>
    <Value>Alright, alright, don’t blow a blood vessel. Everybody wins here today. Alright, let’s see where I put that...Ah, here’s the box for you. Now, take that coddled Sutherland boy and skedaddle, got it?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bandit_SO_Up_Ladder_08</Key>
    <Value>Pack it up, people! Let’s get lost before the Wolfgang start pokin’ around here!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Up_Ladder_01</Key>
    <Value>I spent days laboriously copying history books into blank ones, and the Dean barely paid me for it! Said I should be doing it for the love of history. That won’t put bread on my plate!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Up_Ladder_02</Key>
    <Value>There has to be a better way to climb the ranks than by endless thankless work! I’m better than this! All systems have shortcuts...I just need to figure out the one for this Academy...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Up_Ladder_03</Key>
    <Value>Thanks for helping me out, [PlayerName]. I thought I could negotiate with these guys. Turns out they thought ransoming me might be more profitable for them. *sigh* That’ll show me for assuming people still have common decency.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Artois_SO_Up_Ladder_03_a</Key>
    <Value>Normally bandits don’t negotiate. The fact they were open to it at all is strange...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Up_Ladder_04</Key>
    <Value>Huh. You’re right. I’m fairly certain they were using a passphrase as well. I wonder...Do you think someone in Harmattan’s got a deal going with them? It would explain who’s giving them an “operating budget”.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Up_Ladder_05</Key>
    <Value>And all that trouble for a little box like that. I’m mighty curious to know what’s inside that Victor wants so badly.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Artois_SO_Up_Ladder_05_a</Key>
    <Value>(Break the wax seal and open the box)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Up_Ladder_06</Key>
    <Value>(Two glimmering gems greet your eyes...They appear to have been forged with an exceptionally sharp point on one end, with an empty bulb on the other)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Up_Ladder_07</Key>
    <Value>Is that...Elatt’s name, those are Tsar Stones! They seem to have been forged into...Bullets, look like. Not sure what that glass bulb is supposed to be used for, though...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Artois_SO_Up_Ladder_05_b</Key>
    <Value>(Don’t open the box)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Up_Ladder_08</Key>
    <Value>Come on, we risked our lives for that thing! ...Oh, fine. You’re right, actually. We’re supposed to be professionals.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Up_Ladder_09</Key>
    <Value>I’ll &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;head back to Harmattan&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Thanks for the assist, [PlayerName]! I owe you one!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Artois_SO_Up_Ladder_03_b</Key>
    <Value>Why’d you even try to negotiate with bandits? They’re already outlaws, Artois!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Up_Ladder_10</Key>
    <Value>I mean...That’s fair. But bandits are still people. They have their own reasons for operating outside society. Assuming they’re all pure evil might be common sense, but they’re still human and should be given basic dignity. They’re not Scourge, after all.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Up_Ladder_13</Key>
    <Value>Ah, there you are! Glad you made it back safe too!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Up_Ladder_14</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_01</Key>
    <Value>At least my labor back in the war camps was silently appreciated. I feel like half the people I’ve done work for are just using me. I can read it in their body language as they turn away once we’re done doing business.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_02</Key>
    <Value>I get the impression that unless I do something that really makes me stand out, climbing up the social ladder here is going to take ages. Hmm...How can I prove I’m worth my salt...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_03</Key>
    <Value>(Desy seems barely conscious, she looks like she’s taken a serious strike to the ribs)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_22</Key>
    <Value>Ach...I definitely cracked a rib in that fight. Thanks again for bailing me out, friend.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_23</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Butcher_SO_Up_Ladder_01</Key>
    <Value>Another one...Who is your master, human? Speak or die.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Butcher_SO_Up_Ladder_01_a</Key>
    <Value>Umm...I work for Victor? Are you the...err...Person who has something for him?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Butcher_SO_Up_Ladder_01_b</Key>
    <Value>Victor sent me. He wasn’t kidding when he said you were different!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Butcher_SO_Up_Ladder_02</Key>
    <Value>Finally. Hand me that jar of glass. This exchange leaves me open and vulnerable, and I want it over and done with NOW.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Butcher_SO_Up_Ladder_03</Key>
    <Value>(The glowing Immaculate punctures an organ along it’s arm, and pours a steady stream of hissing black blood into it until the jar is full)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Butcher_SO_Up_Ladder_04</Key>
    <Value>It is done. Take this to your master. Ensure it is given to whom it was intended. Do not break it, for if you do, I will take your life as vengeance for wasting my blood.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Butcher_SO_Up_Ladder_04_a</Key>
    <Value>And...What exactly do you intend we do with your blood?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Butcher_SO_Up_Ladder_05</Key>
    <Value>Hsss...Why would I tell you and spoil the element of surprise? I did not become the apex predator of all life by being foolish. Your master knows who this must be given to, and what must be done with it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_04</Key>
    <Value>No...Don’t let him leave...&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Stop him&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_04_a</Key>
    <Value>Wait, is that Desy back there?! What did you do to her?!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Butcher_SO_Up_Ladder_06</Key>
    <Value>This one attacked me. It is a brainless creature. I am not some weak-willed beast who feels guilt over their actions. No. I was born to kill and fight. It stood no chance against me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Butcher_SO_Up_Ladder_06_a</Key>
    <Value>You’re no ordinary Immaculate...What ARE you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Butcher_SO_Up_Ladder_07</Key>
    <Value>You puny things call me the Butcher. You speak it in fear. So, I like it. It makes my two hearts throb with purpose.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_05</Key>
    <Value>He’s...The most vicious Immaculate known to man. He can’t...We can’t let him escape!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Butcher_SO_Up_Ladder_08</Key>
    <Value>Why should I change who I am? Why should I care about harm done to anything that isn’t like me? Slaughter makes me feel satisfied. It relieves my suffering. So tell me, human. Why should I stop?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Butcher_SO_Up_Ladder_09</Key>
    <Value>Can you say your kin are any different? Your human city is built upon the death of hundreds. I can hear their blood wailing in the walls. This city will die, one way...Or another.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Butcher_SO_Up_Ladder_06_b</Key>
    <Value>You feel no guilt over the harm and slaughter you’ve caused? Really?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Butcher_SO_Up_Ladder_10</Key>
    <Value>Whatever made me the way I am did so for a reason. Why should I argue with them? My killer’s instinct...It is why I exist. It guides me to slay our true enemy. Until the day comes when I can kill him, I will have to settle for killing base animals like you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_06</Key>
    <Value>Animals?! You’ve...killed thousands! You claim intelligence, but...Gah...You are nothing more than a bloodthirsty monster! Evil incarnate!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Butcher_SO_Up_Ladder_11</Key>
    <Value>Tsss...This one clearly did not learn its lesson. It is very fortunate that I will not be killing it today, though I very much want to. I cannot accept more delays leaving this place full of nasty steel beasts.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Butcher_SO_Up_Ladder_12</Key>
    <Value>Stand aside, human. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Do not bar my way, or you will suffer my wrath&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Butcher_SO_Up_Ladder_12_a</Key>
    <Value>Go ahead, leave. I hope we never cross paths again...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Butcher_SO_Up_Ladder_13</Key>
    <Value>You are a wise little human. Because if we do meet again, I will have no reason to spare you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Butcher_SO_Up_Ladder_12_b</Key>
    <Value>No. I can't let a monster like you get away alive.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Butcher_SO_Up_Ladder_14</Key>
    <Value>Brainless, like the other one! I will enjoy your death, puny one. Die, and take my pain away!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_07</Key>
    <Value>Dammit, you let him go. How many innocent people did we just doom to be slaughtered at his hands?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_08_a</Key>
    <Value>You said he’s the most vicious Immaculate ever known. He would have killed me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_09</Key>
    <Value>...Alright, that’s fair. You’d have to be at least as strong as a Champion of Elatt to stand a chance against him in single combat. The fact that I’m still breathing is already a miracle. You did the smart thing, [PlayerName]. I can’t fault you for it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_08_b</Key>
    <Value>The mission was to just get the “delivery”. I’m not risking losing that promotion.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_10</Key>
    <Value>If he kills anyone else after this, their blood is on your hands. Don’t you ever forget that. Friends I grew up with have been killed by that thing. The Scourge may be instinctively drawn to destruction, but the Butcher is far worse. He REVELS in it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_11</Key>
    <Value>Y-you did it. I don’t believe it. You killed the Butcher of Men! I...I can’t quite believe my eyes!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_11_a</Key>
    <Value>Looks like I’m just that good.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_12</Key>
    <Value>Huh. I guess you’re right. Well, don’t let that go to your head. You know what they say about pride and falls. Still...Thank you. I knew people who were killed by that thing.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_11_b</Key>
    <Value>Same here. I guess I was just better prepared, and a little lucky.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_13</Key>
    <Value>Heh. Don’t be so modest. Come on, luck or not, you still killed the Butcher of Men. I owe you, [PlayerName]. I’ve lost friends to that damnable monster.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_13_a</Key>
    <Value>I wonder why he wanted to deliver his blood to Victor?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_14</Key>
    <Value>I don’t know. I’m going to be having some very serious words with him when I &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;return to Harmattan&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Dealing with Immaculates...It’s bad enough. But the Butcher? He embraces violence and evil. Only a madman or a fool would make a bargain with him.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_14_a</Key>
    <Value>Do you need help getting back to Harmattan?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_15</Key>
    <Value>I’ll be fine getting back on my own. I have a few potions in my bag to patch myself up. I’ll let them work their magic and head back on my own once I’m well enough to sprint. Go on ahead without me, I’ve been hurt worse before.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_16-a</Key>
    <Value>Ugh...The weapons that the Scourge use are downright soaked in corruption and the Butcher’s is no exception. I’m going to need to clean this wound VERY carefully. I have no intention of dying from a Scourge infection in some unknown cave!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Up_Ladder_16</Key>
    <Value>Oh, thank Elatt, I thought we were both done for...This is the first I’ve ever heard of the Butcher of Men sparing anyone...What in Aurai is he planning that he’s willing to spare lives?!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>HighClassInnNews_SO_Ladder_01</Key>
    <Value>Did you hear? The recent trade caravan from Sirocco got waylaid by outlaws! It was near &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Golem Lake, just North of Harmattan&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>HighClassInnNews_SO_Ladder_02</Key>
    <Value>Bandits came charging down from the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;cliffside above the lake&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, and robbed them blind before scurrying back up the mountain trail! I was counting that delivery of fine silk, dammit!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>LowClassInnNews_SO_Ladder_01</Key>
    <Value>One of our explorer patrons just came back from a trip around the edge of the region. He claims he saw an Immaculate that glowed blue, and that it was camping with...Some kind of monstrous giant.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>LowClassInnNews_SO_Ladder_02</Key>
    <Value>I don’t believe the Ash Giants get along with the Scourge, so...Honestly, I’m willing to chalk it up to the man having one too many bottles of wine that night.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercantile_SO_Ladder_01</Key>
    <Value>You are from Cierzo, no? I have heard worrisome rumors of pirates and bandits planning an attack...If you have time, I would suggest you return there and see if they are true.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Headmaster_SO_Ladder_01</Key>
    <Value>I’m afraid I’m quite busy, [PlayerName]. Unless it’s urgent, I have no time for you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_Knife_00</Key>
    <Value>&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;I don’t have any new work for you just yet&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, [PlayerName]. I’m still waiting on some news from the Naturalist branch. Feel free to take a few days off.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_Knife_01</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName], there you are! I’ve got work for you. The Naturalist division’s come back to me with some of their findings on the blood you retrieved for us, and I need you to act on them.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Knife_01</Key>
    <Value>So...What did they do with the Butcher’s blood?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_Knife_02</Key>
    <Value>Shh, keep that to yourself! But yes, there was enough left over to do a bit of experimentation. And we discovered some interesting properties the blood has. I have a new Power Coil design in mind, and I need you to get the first prototype ready.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Victor_SO_Knife_02_a</Key>
    <Value>I don’t see the connection. What does Scourge blood have to do with a Power Coil?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_Knife_03</Key>
    <Value>According to the Naturalist branch, Scourge blood emits a certain kind of energy. They theorize that’s how the Scourge can tell each other apart. And Scourge less intelligent than an Immaculate don’t attack their own kind. It’s in their nature not to.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_Knife_04</Key>
    <Value>Furthermore, when exposed to an electric charge, and some small-scale spellcraft, Scourge blood will be attracted to other sources of Scourge blood.  Essentially, we can use it to give our Golems the ability to track Scourge beasts more effectively.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Knife_02</Key>
    <Value>So...to sum up, if we use these new Power Coils in our Golems, not only will they be able to track down the Scourge, but better stalk them and infiltrate their tunnels? That’s quite the breakthrough!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_Knife_05</Key>
    <Value>Exactly, Artois! This kills multiple birds with one stone. If, that is, it works in practice. Hence, why I’m asking you to go see a contact of mine to make a prototype.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Victor_SO_Knife_05_a</Key>
    <Value>Why not just ask the Engineering division to design it?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_Knife_06</Key>
    <Value>And have them take all the credit? No, I want to do this my way. We’re going to use &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;one of my contacts in Levant&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; to design the prototype. Once I’m sure the design will work as intended, I’ll contract the Engineering branch for full production.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_Knife_07</Key>
    <Value>I need you to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;head to the city of Levant in Abrassar Desert. My contact there will give you the details&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; of the task at hand. Give him this package, he’ll know what to do.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_Knife_08</Key>
    <Value>&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Speak to one of our Caravaners and see if he’ll give you a lift&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, at least partway there. Levant’s the great big city in the East of the desert. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;The man you’re looking for is named Orsten , the engineer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Knife_03</Key>
    <Value>Do you want me to grab my backpack and give [PlayerName] a hand on the journey, Victor?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_Knife_09</Key>
    <Value>No, I want you working with the Wolfgang Mercenaries, Artois. They’ve found a cache of broken Golems in the mountains, and I want someone I can trust to make sure none go “missing”, if you catch my drift. We need as many as we can get.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_Knife_10</Key>
    <Value>Now remember, [PlayerName], your next few blood price payments will depend on your performance here. So make sure you put your back into it, Apprentice!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Victor_SO_Knife_10_a</Key>
    <Value>Wait, I thought you said you’d guarantee that you’d cover my blood price!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_Knife_11</Key>
    <Value>Well, yes. But I can’t support a liability at my own expense, you know. That’s not how the real world works. You need to earn your keep, [PlayerName].</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Victor_SO_Knife_11_a</Key>
    <Value>You’re seriously using me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_Knife_12</Key>
    <Value>I don’t appreciate your attitude. You are the one who came to ME for a quick rise up the social ladder here, and you want me to pay your Blood Price for you. I’d say it is YOU who is using ME, Apprentice.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Victor_SO_Knife_10_b</Key>
    <Value>Alright, I’m on it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_Knife_13</Key>
    <Value>Ah, you’re back. Did you bring the new Power Coil prototype?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Victor_SO_Knife_13_a</Key>
    <Value>Yes, here it is.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_Knife_14</Key>
    <Value>...Huh. This seems like the absolute minimum job. Are you sure you didn’t slack off? If you aren’t being passionate about the work, don’t expect to get anything out of it!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_Knife_15</Key>
    <Value>Mmm...Alright, this is a little less well designed than I expected, but I guess it’ll have to do. It does prove that the theory is sound at least. I’m going to see to it that it gets a few solid field tests in.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_Knife_16</Key>
    <Value>Ah, yes, this looks good. The design seems solid. I’ll run a field test or two to see just how well it performs, and have the Engineering branch start making more of these.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_Knife_17</Key>
    <Value>Oh. Oh wow. Yes, this is exactly what I was hoping for. Excellent work. As soon as we get a full field test done, I’ll have the Engineering branch start making as many of these as we can afford.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Merc_SO_Knife_01</Key>
    <Value>I’ll be glad to test it out for ya. We have just the operation in mind, actually. We’ve tracked a pack of Immaculates to a canyon cave and have ‘em cornered. With this new Coil in one of our Golems, we can spring a trap on ‘em and wipe ‘em out.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_Knife_18</Key>
    <Value>Ah, this is Henri. He’s the leader of the Wolfgang Mercenaries. One of his scouts discovered some Immaculates squatting in a cave nearby.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Merc_SO_Knife_02</Key>
    <Value>Heh, if you want, come on and join us later. We’d be glad to show one of Victor’s mates how it’s done out there!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_Knife_19</Key>
    <Value>Anyway, you’re free for now. Here, your reward for the job. I will let you know the next time I need you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Victor_SO_Knife_19_a</Key>
    <Value>That’s all? For such a long journey?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_Knife_20</Key>
    <Value>I don’t appreciate that tone, [PlayerName]. Someday you’ll appreciate all that I do for you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Victor_SO_Knife_19_b</Key>
    <Value>Let me know when there’s something else I can do!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_Knife_21</Key>
    <Value>I will indeed, Apprentice. You’re proving to be quite an asset! A little longer and your promotion is guaranteed!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_Knife_22_a</Key>
    <Value>I’ve got nothing more for you, right now. Come back in a few days, [PlayerName].</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>PLAYERNAME_SO_Knife_24</Key>
    <Value>(You still have that &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;package to deliver to Gregory Turnbull&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, the Arcane Dean...)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_Knife_22</Key>
    <Value>I know what you did. And I won’t be played for a fool. How could you turn on me after all I’ve done for you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Victor_SO_Knife_22_a</Key>
    <Value>All you’ve done? You’ve been using me from the start. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_Knife_23</Key>
    <Value>You’ve made the worst kind of enemy possible, betrayer. You’ll come to regret your foolish action.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Victor_SO_Knife_22_b</Key>
    <Value>I believe in Turnbull’s ideas.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_Knife_24</Key>
    <Value>So, you’re just so sensitive and foolish you let Turnbull play you. If I were you, I’d be wary of any food he gives you, in case he decides to start his Wendigo experiments again.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Contact_SO_Knife_00_a</Key>
    <Value>Victor sent me to get some help from you, to make a prototype Power Coil.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Contact_SO_Knife_01</Key>
    <Value>Ah, I’ve been waiting for you. Do you have Mr Berthelot’s package?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Contact_SO_Knife_01_a</Key>
    <Value>Here you go. He said you’d know what to do with it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Contact_SO_Knife_02</Key>
    <Value>So, this is distilled Immaculate blood, huh? I don’t know how you Soroboreans got it, nor how you distilled it, but I can work with this. Let’s see if Victor’s little theory will hold water...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Contact_SO_Knife_03</Key>
    <Value>I was hoping to have everything I needed to start work on the coil right away, but unfortunately I’m missing some essential components and most of the city’s mercenaries are too busy hunting down the Sand Corsairs to help me out.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Contact_SO_Knife_04</Key>
    <Value>Victor told me you can handle a little danger. I’ll need you to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;acquire a few things from in an old ruin called the Electric Lab&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. It’s to the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;North, down from the cliff we’re on&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. An explorer has confirmed all that we need is in there, you just need to find them.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Contact_SO_Knife_05</Key>
    <Value>I absolutely need a chunk of the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;huge red crystal&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; that’s been reported deep in the bowels of the lab. Without a piece of a Heavily Corrupted Mana Stone, there’s no way for this Coil to properly hold the charge while surrounded by Immaculate Blood.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Contact_SO_Knife_06</Key>
    <Value>If you can also supply &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;a bottle of Lightning Grease, three replacement valves, and a normal Power Coil&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, things would go significantly smoother.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Contact_SO_Knife_07</Key>
    <Value>For the Lightning Grease, keep an eye out for some kind of &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;green-ish metal vessel&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; that’s steaming hot. For the replacement valves, there’s bound to be a &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;supply closet&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; with spare parts in there somewhere.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Contact_SO_Knife_07_a</Key>
    <Value>You’re asking for quite a bit of stuff...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Contact_SO_Knife_08</Key>
    <Value>Like I said, I only REALLY need a chunk of the large red crystal, but &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;the end result will be considerably better&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; the more of the other parts you bring in.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Contact_SO_Knife_07_b</Key>
    <Value>Can’t you send the guy who confirmed that these things are in the Electric Lab?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Contact_SO_Knife_09</Key>
    <Value>He’s long gone. The guy lost his partner to a Hive Lord and gave up on adventuring entirely. I can’t say I blame him, after a loss like that.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Contact_SO_Knife_07_c</Key>
    <Value>I’ll be back when I have the components you need, then.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Contact_SO_Knife_09_a</Key>
    <Value>I have the items you needed.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Contact_SO_Knife_09-Fix_01</Key>
    <Value>Are you certain? I want the items all at once. If there is something you are missing, go get it now.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Contact_SO_Knife_09-Fix_01_a</Key>
    <Value>I have everything I want to hand over. Here’s that Corrupted crystal you wanted...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Contact_SO_Knife_10</Key>
    <Value>Wow, when that adventurer said the Mana Stone had been “Corrupted” he wasn’t kidding. Then again...The Devourer was slain above that lab...The blood leaking into the place must have...*cough* Yes, this altered Mana crystal will do nicely.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Contact_SO_Knife_10_a</Key>
    <Value>Here’s a bottle of Lightning Grease.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Contact_SO_Knife_11</Key>
    <Value>Perfect, that’ll help this thing maintain a charge for considerably longer. Mr Berthelot’s instructions did say efficiency was important!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Contact_SO_Knife_10_b</Key>
    <Value>I’ve got your three replacement valves.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Contact_SO_Knife_12</Key>
    <Value>Thank you. I’ll make some tweaks to these, and then Victor can replace the Power Coil housing in his Golems with these modified ones. They’ll provide a much smoother power transfer, allowing for more raw power when needed.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Contact_SO_Knife_10_c</Key>
    <Value>I’ve got a spare power coil for you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Contact_SO_Knife_13</Key>
    <Value>Ah, thank you. There’s a few small parts in these that I’m going to need to use...Making new Power Coils from scratch is a science we haven’t completely figured out, but we’re getting closer with each new one.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Contact_SO_Knife_10_d</Key>
    <Value>That’s all I have for the job.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Contact_SO_Knife_14</Key>
    <Value>Alright, I’ve gotten most of the unit’s housing prepared while you were out. Give me just a moment to put it all together and test it...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Contact_SO_Knife_15</Key>
    <Value>Jolly good. This prototype looks like it’s going to hold up just fine. I wouldn’t rely on it for heavy duty work, but I’m sure your people at the Academy will be able to refine the design further. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tell Mr Berthelot it was nice doing business with him&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Contact_SO_Knife_16</Key>
    <Value>Oh, by the way, while you’re in Harmattan, &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;mind delivering this other item to the Arcane Dean, a Mr Turnbull&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;? He’d put in a request for a device to measure runic frequencies not long ago, and I’ve just now put the finishing touches on it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Contact_SO_Knife_16_a</Key>
    <Value>You keep asking a LOT from me, you know.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Contact_SO_Knife_17</Key>
    <Value>How about I pay you for the transport in advance? You’re going to Harmattan anyway, so what’s the big deal?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Contact_SO_Knife_16_b</Key>
    <Value>Well, as long as I’m going there, sure.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Contact_SO_Knife_18</Key>
    <Value>Alright, see to it that both items get where they are needed. Don’t forget to put in a good word for me with both of them! I need all the good business I can get!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Merc_SO_Knife_03</Key>
    <Value>Oy! I told you that punk was workin’ with em! Activate the barrier!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Barrier_Pillar_SO_Knife_01</Key>
    <Value>(You can’t manually disable the barrier while under attack!)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Barrier_Pillar_SO_Knife_02</Key>
    <Value>(With great care, you rip open one of the panels on the side of the barrier generator. It will take a bit of time and effort disable it safely, but it’s well within your ability to do)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Barrier_Pillar_SO_Knife_03</Key>
    <Value>(With the barrier disabled, Desy will be able to meet up with the Immaculates, and smuggle their leader into Harmattan! &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Your mission is complete&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;!)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_01</Key>
    <Value>Ugh, when will that runic frequency metronome be finished? It’s been weeks since I commissioned it! And STILL no word from that damnable &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Levant artisan&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Knife_01_a</Key>
    <Value>Well, here it is. An engineer in Levant asked me to deliver this to you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_02_Player</Key>
    <Value>(You have the item he requested...But it’s probably for the best to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;finish your job for Victor first&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_03</Key>
    <Value>Ah! Thank you for handling the delivery! I’ve been doing some experiments on the effect of runes on the Scourge, and this should be of extreme assistance to my work.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Knife_03_a</Key>
    <Value>Speaking of Scourge...Be on the lookout. There’s a gang of Immaculates camping in a canyon nearby. Victor’s got the Wolfgang to go kill them, thankfully.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_04</Key>
    <Value>Victor...What? Oh damn. Damn! How did he find them?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Knife_04_a</Key>
    <Value>Is something wrong? What’s the issue with him killing a few Immaculates?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_05</Key>
    <Value>The Immaculates he mentioned to you...If they really are the ones hiding in that canyon cave up North, &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;I think they’re the ones who are working with me&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Knife_05_a</Key>
    <Value>Wait, what do you mean you’re working with Immaculates?!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_06</Key>
    <Value>Hold! It’s not what it sounds like. I think I’ve found a way to eliminate their killing urge. And I need an Immaculate to test my theory on. If Victor kills them...Then it could be years before I have another opportunity to test the theory like this!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_07</Key>
    <Value>I can tell you have doubts. Let me prove it to you. Come to my laboratory. I guarantee that if I show you my work, you’ll change your mind. See that &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;circular panel on the floor, behind this pillar&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;? Lift it up and come down to my hidden workspace.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Knife_07_a</Key>
    <Value>There are secret passages in this Academy?!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_08</Key>
    <Value>Well, yes. Back when the old nobility used to run things, it was the only way to perform research they didn’t approve of. Now, move it! There’s a lot on the line!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_09</Key>
    <Value>Thank you for coming. Desy tells me you two already know each other.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Knife_05</Key>
    <Value>Yeah, [PlayerName] was working with Victor too. And being exploited over their Blood Price. He turned around and held that over your head, didn’t he, [PlayerName]?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Knife_09_a</Key>
    <Value>You said you’d be able to convince me. So convince me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_10</Key>
    <Value>So, first, I was trying to discover a way to destroy the Scourge with magic. They have a deep connection with the Corruption, so I wanted to find a way to use long-lasting runes to dispel it, and essentially starve the entire horde.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_11</Key>
    <Value>Then, I noticed something odd. The Scourge have a much deeper connection to Rune Magic than I thought. So...See that Illuminator in the cage? I was able to, with considerable injury to myself, I might add, apply some runes onto its body.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_12</Key>
    <Value>With the right combinations of runes, I was able to alter it’s behaviour. A few tests later, and I was convinced. The Scourge’s urge to kill all living things, and especially their instinct to hunt Elatt, is actually an invocation from a spell.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_13</Key>
    <Value>In fact, when I took a closer look at some Scourge blood that the Naturalist division was working on, I confirmed even the blood itself reacts violently. Everything about the Scourge’s base nature is controlled by that spell’s command.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_14</Key>
    <Value>Then, with the corpse of the Butcher of Men that the Naturalist branch was so kind to loan me, I confirmed that in Immaculates, that spell is applied in a much more focused manner. It’s harder to change, but still allows for them to retain their free will and intelligence.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_15</Key>
    <Value>And if there’s a spell involved...There’s a counter-spell that can mitigate the effect.&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt; I am convinced that we can eliminate the killing urge from the entirety of the Scourge&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Remove their instinct to kill Ellat and their urge to harm everything else.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Knife_15_a</Key>
    <Value>And...What’s the point of that? They’re still monsters, right?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Knife_15_b</Key>
    <Value>Wait...If it’s possible to do that...That could change everything.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_16</Key>
    <Value>Follow my logic and imagine what this means for a moment...If the Scourge are directed to desire violence via a spell, and we break that spell... What happens next?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_17</Key>
    <Value>Your typical Scourge beasts become nothing more than wild animals. Rather than attack and harm everything around them, they’ll only kill what violates their territory or safety. It will significantly reduce the scale of their rampages.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_18</Key>
    <Value>And as for the Immaculates...They are intelligent, yet they are driven by instinct to kill Elatt. Because this task is impossible, they lash out against all living things in their frustration. If you remove that killing urge, what would an intelligent species do?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_19</Key>
    <Value>Some will carry on as usual, because it’s what they know. Others will choose to do something else with their lives. Others may side against the Scourge who seek violence, in hopes that it will secure peace with humanity.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_20</Key>
    <Value>The entire brains behind the Scourge horde will fall into utter and complete chaos. Chaos that can be exploited. It will make dealing with the Scourge considerably easier, and cut the number we need to kill by an incredible margin.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Knife_11</Key>
    <Value>The war will basically almost end itself. The Scourge go from a unified horde to a divided muddle of animals and individuals. It’s not a perfect solution, but...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_21</Key>
    <Value>Would annihilating all of them be a more expedient solution? Of course. But I haven't discovered how to do that. We know that this solution WORKS. At least, it does in small-scale experiments.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Knife_21_a</Key>
    <Value>And we get to save a sentient species in the process.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_22</Key>
    <Value>Yes, that's a nice bonus. Having an entire species owe us the mother of all favors would be incredible. Could you imagine the wealth and power that will flow through Sorobor as a result?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Knife_21_b</Key>
    <Value>Turnbull, be honest with me. What are the odds that you'll be able to pull it off?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_23</Key>
    <Value>I don't DO odds. A task is either possible, or impossible. And with a little more effort, I can push it from one to the other. I’m the Dean of Arcane Studies, bending the world to my will is what I do.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_24</Key>
    <Value>But even if my theory is correct, I can't truly make it happen without an actual Immaculate to work this magic on!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_25</Key>
    <Value>If you can save even one Immaculate and bring it here, I will make you an Initiate in the Arcane branch immediately, and handle your Blood Price for you. No catch, I just need your help.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Knife_25_a</Key>
    <Value>Alright, I’m convinced. You can count on my help.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_26</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName], I want you to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;go to the cave the Immaculates are hiding in. It’s in a small mazelike canyon, North of the Cultural District in the East&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Get there before the Wolfgang do!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_27</Key>
    <Value>As for you, Desy, I need you to prepare a wagon and get ready to smuggle our new friend back into the city.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Knife_12</Key>
    <Value>Wait, why not send me to the cave first, Gregory? I know the one you’re talking about, I could probably get there faster!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_28</Key>
    <Value>Because [PlayerName] won’t attract any suspicion. Victor thinks they’re on his side. The Wolfgang won’t suspect a thing until it’s too late.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Knife_25_b</Key>
    <Value>I’m...Not entirely convinced.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_29</Key>
    <Value>I’m aware that this isn’t as ideal as wiping the Scourge out, and that it feels like we’re cooperating with the enemy...But this would be a dramatic shift in the nature of the war. It would save an incredible number of lives.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Knife_29_a</Key>
    <Value>And how do I know you won’t take advantage of me? I’ve been burned before.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_30</Key>
    <Value>Fair concern. But I’m being upfront and open with you now, aren’t I? I’m leaving myself vulnerable in hopes of convincing you to help me. Do you want our deal in writing as an official contract? Because that can be arranged.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Knife_30_a</Key>
    <Value>...Alright. I’ll trust you. I’m going to help.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Knife_30_b</Key>
    <Value>I want it in writing. And Elatt help you if I have to take this to the headmaster.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_31</Key>
    <Value>I assure you that you will not. I’ll have your promotion approved by the time you’re back.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_32</Key>
    <Value>My sister-in Law Helen’s always told me that you’re resourceful, [PlayerName]. Prove it to me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_33</Key>
    <Value>The two of you pulled it off. Well done. I’ve explained to our new friend here what we plan to do, and he’s willing to cooperate.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Knife_33_a</Key>
    <Value>Even after we clobbered him? You must have a silver tongue, Turnbull.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Knife_18</Key>
    <Value>HHSSSSS! You should have sent Turnbull himself to speak with me from the start. He is far more convincing than you, human! If any of my kind died in our pointless fight, consider your life marked!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_34</Key>
    <Value>In any case, as far as I'm concerned, you are welcome here in the Arcane Branch, [PlayerName]. Put in the work, and we'll treat you right.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_35</Key>
    <Value>Look, I’ll be blunt, if you’re not a mage, you don’t belong here. But, so long as you remain useful to us, I’ll treat you like anyone else in the branch. Please do consider either becoming a mage, or joining another branch eventually.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Knife_36</Key>
    <Value>&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;I’ll let you know the next time I need you&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, Initiates. In the meantime, try to keep a low profile. Victor likely won’t take this lying down.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Knife_01</Key>
    <Value>Hey, [PlayerName]. Taking care of yourself?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Desy_SO_Knife_01_a</Key>
    <Value>About as well as I can. You?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Knife_02</Key>
    <Value>I’m working with Gregory Turnbull in the Arcane branch these days. He’s actually got me helping with a particularly...Well, massive project. We’re pushing the limits of what rune magic is capable of. It’s wild stuff.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Desy_SO_Knife_02_a</Key>
    <Value>I didn’t realize you were a mage!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Knife_03</Key>
    <Value>Yup, I visited the Academy’s Ley Line as soon as I got here. I’ll take every tool I can get my hands on. Only a fool, or someone with a VERY specific plan in mind would to otherwise.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Desy_SO_Knife_02_b</Key>
    <Value>Good luck to you, Desy.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Knife_04</Key>
    <Value>Likewise, friend. I hope you get out from under Victor’s thumb sooner than later.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Knife_06</Key>
    <Value>So, Turnbull’s taken you into his confidence too, huh? I hope you able to help us. We need every advantage we can get right now.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Desy_SO_Knife_06_a</Key>
    <Value>You left because Victor made a deal with the Butcher! And now you’re helping Gregory while he’s working with Immaculates! Why the change of heart?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Knife_07</Key>
    <Value>You’re right. I’m not quite comfortable with this...But those Immaculates actually did come to us for help in removing their violent instinct, and Gregory says he can actually do it... I’m willing to give this harebrained scheme a chance.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Knife_08</Key>
    <Value>The Butcher of Men is one thing. Immaculates actively trying to change themselves for the better is another. Besides, this plan might actually shift the terms of war on a level that will help not just family back home, but everyone.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Knife_09</Key>
    <Value>Listen, no one hates the Scourge more than me. I’ve lost friends and family to them. My entire youth was spent on learning how to kill them. And even I’m convinced this plan’s worth a shot.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Desy_SO_Knife_09_a</Key>
    <Value>Huh. I didn’t think this was something you could change your mind over.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Knife_10</Key>
    <Value>Keeping one’s mind and heart open is important to growing and making new allies. This research comes close to the line I won’t cross, but doesn’t step over it. I’m willing to see it to the end.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Knife_13</Key>
    <Value>Well, the thing’s still breathing. Small mercies, huh? I don’t know how Turnbull intends to convince this Immaculate to help us now that we’ve attacked it and its friends, but if he insists we bring one home...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Knife_14</Key>
    <Value>I’ll handle smuggling him into Harmattan. You &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;go take care of the mercenaries outside the cave&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. I hate to leave that on you, but someone’s got to make sure no one sneaks in here to slit this thing’s throat while it’s down.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Knife_01</Key>
    <Value>So...Come to slay us, have you? You were foolish to come without help, human!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Immaculate_SO_Knife_01_a</Key>
    <Value>No I’m not! I’m here to help you! I work with Gregory Turnbull!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Knife_02</Key>
    <Value>True, we did come here to receive his aid in ridding us of our instinct to hate and kill our natural enemy. But nearly a full moon we have waited, and now men with spells and steel gather outside our cave with intent to kill. We are clearly betrayed!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Immaculate_SO_Knife_02_a</Key>
    <Value>You’re not betrayed! I’m here to help you escape!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Immaculate_SO_Knife_02_b</Key>
    <Value>I swear, I have nothing to do with those men outside!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Knife_03</Key>
    <Value>Is that so? Humans so often claim all Immaculates are the same, yet when we are cornered like vermin, you want us to tell the difference between which human is friend and which is foe? </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Knife_04</Key>
    <Value>Why should we trust in you to be any different from those men? Why do you claim to want to help us overcome our killing urge? Why do you CARE, human? We are monsters to your kind!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Immaculate_SO_Knife_04_a</Key>
    <Value>Even your mortal enemy would prefer peace. Elatt would give your kin a chance.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Knife_05</Key>
    <Value>HHHHSSSSS! Speak not the enemy’s name again, or I will rend your arteries from your flesh and pour the marrow from your bones over my head! ...Even the mere mention of the enemy’s name instills in me a rage I cannot contain!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Immaculate_SO_Knife_04_b</Key>
    <Value>Less humans will be killed by Scourge. The end of this war benefits everyone.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Knife_06</Key>
    <Value>Hmph. A rational reason, then. I can understand that. It is the same for me. My species is finite. Every human who slays an Immaculate robs the world of their unique voice, thoughts and perspectives. I wish only for the slaying to stop.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Immaculate_SO_Knife_04_c</Key>
    <Value>It’s called human decency. Some of us really do care.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Knife_07</Key>
    <Value>HAH. I have encountered precisely one kindhearted human being in my hundred years as Immaculate. Why would they name such a thing human decency if it’s not shared by most humans? Perhaps it just means “humans being decent to humans”, hmmm?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Knife_08</Key>
    <Value>We have been taken advantage of before, by people who promised us freedom from our instinctual shackles. Every time, we have either faced disappointment, or worse, betrayal. What makes you think that this time it will be different?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Immaculate_SO_Knife_08_a</Key>
    <Value>The Arcane Dean is the best mage we have. He can already control an Illuminator.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Knife_09</Key>
    <Value>Can he now? He can control the lowest and weakest of us Scourge like a common pet? Does he really think he will have such success with my kin? To turn us all into his pawns? The language you use, human, it is telling of your master’s motives.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Immaculate_SO_Knife_08_b</Key>
    <Value>Sorobor has more resources and knowledge than anyone. We CAN make it work.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Knife_10</Key>
    <Value>...So, you are saying that if this last attempt fails, we can give up all hope? Even if this fails, then, it has merit. Whether we are freed, or whether we can cast aside all false hope, I will be able to make peace with my existence... I am tempted, human.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Immaculate_SO_Knife_08_c</Key>
    <Value>It’s your only shot at survival. If you don’t change, the war will eventually end you all.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Knife_11</Key>
    <Value>Ssss...You strike deeply at my two hearts, human. But this is the truth. The war can only end with our destruction, or a change so great that humanity must re-assess their views of us. It is a grave risk, but one that makes sense to me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Knife_12</Key>
    <Value>Even if Turnbull can help us...What do you humans intend to do if you succeed in removing our deepest instinct? Will we be freed from our chains, only to find our unity shattered, and easy pickings for your warriors to slay?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Immaculate_SO_Knife_12_a</Key>
    <Value>I can’t promise there will be peace, even if I personally want it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Knife_13</Key>
    <Value>A fair answer. I cannot promise that our kind will choose a life of peace either. This fills neither of us with confidence...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Immaculate_SO_Knife_12_b</Key>
    <Value>Well, I guess you’ll be just like us, won’t you? You’d be like any other human tribe.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Knife_14</Key>
    <Value>So you would assimilate us? Remove what makes us different? There is little difference from that, and using us as your pawns. You dare to think you have that right? It is no wonder you think you can change our very nature!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Immaculate_SO_Knife_12_c</Key>
    <Value>I could ask the same. Will your kin use their freedom to betray us, or work with us?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Knife_15</Key>
    <Value>I do not have an answer either, human. Many want nothing more than solitude, others revel in their violent instincts, others obey it merely because they know no alternative. I suppose unpredictability is the curse of freedom we would both share...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Knife_16</Key>
    <Value>I will give you and the human Turnbull this chance, then. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;I will come with you&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.  But you must &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;clear a path for my kin to escape&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Those men outside the cave will try to kill us the moment we step outside.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Knife_17</Key>
    <Value>I remain unconvinced. In fact, I believe you were sent here to stall for time, so those men could better spring their trap. You have made your final mistake, human!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Electric_SO_Knife_01</Key>
    <Value>(This must be the Heavily Corrupted Mana Stone you’re looking for. You chip off a chunk and stash it in a satchel.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Electric_SO_Knife_02</Key>
    <Value>(This should be one of the replacement valves you need for the new Power Coil!)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Electric_SO_Knife_03</Key>
    <Value>(This has to be the container that holds the “Lightning Grease”. It bubbles and sparks as you pour it into a small earthen pot for transportation.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Knife_04</Key>
    <Value>Victor’s gotten me training with the Wolfgang. I had no idea that Runic Trap spells could be used the way they taught me! We’re so lucky to have such skilled mercenaries working alongside us!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Knife_05</Key>
    <Value>I had my doubts about Victor, but I’m over them. He’s a harsh boss, but he really is trying to do his best to make life safer for us all. I wish Desy was a little more open-minded... She’s wrong about him.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Knife_06</Key>
    <Value>Ugh...Every single one of my muscles is in open revolt...Mining Golems out of a collapsed mountain wall was not a good time. I think you got the easy job!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Artois_SO_Knife_06_a</Key>
    <Value>I’ll remember that next time I need to explore ruins teeming with danger, thanks.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Knife_07</Key>
    <Value>Really? You had to explore ancient ruins to finish the job? You definitely got the more interesting job!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Artois_SO_Knife_06_b</Key>
    <Value>If you count a multi-region journey to be easy, sure.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Knife_08</Key>
    <Value>It is, though, isn’t it? As long as you pace yourself, it’s a nice long hike. Sounds relaxing to me, to be honest!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>HighClassInnNews_SO_Knife_01</Key>
    <Value>Did you hear? A pack of Immaculates was spotted up North recently! I hear it was somewhere &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;in the mountains North of the ruined cultural district, in the East&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;! I hope the Wolfgang gets rid of them right quick!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>LowClassInnNews_SO_Knife_01</Key>
    <Value>A former explorer came by recently, talking about his last job exploring the Electric Lab in Abrassar Desert. Apparently the job went on long enough that he and his partner nearly fell asleep walking home...And that’s when a hive lord pounced on ‘em...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Engineering_SO_Knife_01</Key>
    <Value>Bah, yet again Victor tries to keep all the glory of scientific discovery to himself! This is why I can’t stand the man! He’s too damn paranoid!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Naturalist_SO_Knife_01</Key>
    <Value>Would you believe one of my apprentices thinks I know nothing of Alchemy? I know how to make money off of it, isn’t that the same thing?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>History_SO_Knife_01</Key>
    <Value>Did you know? We once elected a council of nobles to lead us. And yet...When the underclasses flooded the upper city to flee the Scourge, every last one of our nobles abandoned us. Things have been better since Sorobor took the reigns of power here.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Knife_01</Key>
    <Value>Forgive my temper today. I’m dealing with a letter I received from my brother, Damian. The man’s paranoia of Elatt knows no bounds anymore! *Sigh* It’s no wonder why Taleron left him!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Knife_02</Key>
    <Value>Damian was so much easier to deal with back when Taleron was his voice of reason!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercantile_SO_Knife_01</Key>
    <Value>I worry that one of my scholars is involved in some business he’ll regret out in Abrassar...Risky ventures are one thing...Old Levant is another.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_01</Key>
    <Value>I’m hard at work, figuring out how to help our new friend here. Once I need your help again, I’ll let you know. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;For now, just give me some space to work&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, [PlayerName].</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_02</Key>
    <Value>Ah! Your arrival is most opportune. We have a serious problem, Initiate. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_03</Key>
    <Value>So, have you heard about how the old Golem production facility started up again, after that rogue Golem made its proclamation just outside? Well, some people have started finding ways inside.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_04</Key>
    <Value>An explorer found a rune wall down in a mine tunnel in there...From his description, I think &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;one of those runes might be exactly what I need&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; in order to crack the Immaculate’s spell wide open.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_05</Key>
    <Value>The problem is, there’s plenty of Scourge that have managed to infiltrate the place as well. The engineering branch just decided that it was highly likely that this tunnel could be used to bypass the walls and invade the city.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_06</Key>
    <Value>And guess who just got the contract to not just guard the tunnel but also collapse it with explosives?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Sabotage_06_a</Key>
    <Value>Victor and the Wolfgang Mercenaries, I assume.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_07</Key>
    <Value>Exactly. Now, he could just as easily collapse the tunnel deeper in and let us keep our access to the rune wall, or at least allow me to examine it first. But given our recent...Antagonism...He’s taking more drastic action.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_08</Key>
    <Value>He’s going to collapse the tunnel beyond, in front of, and directly on top of the Rune Wall, permanently blocking all access. And he’s ordered his Wolfgang friends to keep the area clear of any interference, with lethal force if they have to.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Sabotage_08_a</Key>
    <Value>What? Why’s he going so over the top with this?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Sabotage_08_b</Key>
    <Value>Somehow, I’m not surprised it’s coming to this.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_09</Key>
    <Value>Well, first of all, I think it’s personal at this point. He’s a man who hates to lose control. And not only did you leave his service, you immediately acted against him behind his back. The rumor mill is churning over this and he's losing face.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_10</Key>
    <Value>I suspect his urge right now is to do whatever it takes to solidify his position, and make his opposition, that’s you and me, look as weak as possible right now. Regardless of whether it destroys priceless history or knowledge in the process.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_11</Key>
    <Value>Secondly...I suspect he knows what we’re working on. Having the Scourge hordes become less of a threat means less work for him, and less contracts for the Wolfgang. They all stand to lose business if we succeed.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Sabotage_11_a</Key>
    <Value>So he's going to deliberately stop us from fixing the Scourge, by any means, huh?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_12</Key>
    <Value>Precisely. Now, the only one who can officially delay the demolition and get the Wolfgang to stand aside for me is the Headmaster. And he’s been summoned to Berg to be questioned by the Blue Chamber over a recent incident there.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_13</Key>
    <Value>The demolition is scheduled to take place in about &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;20 days&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. The headmaster is unlikely to get back before then, and no one from Sorobor is even allowed to see him at the moment. So, unless that demolition suffers some mysterious setbacks...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Sabotage_13_a</Key>
    <Value>Can't I just write down the runes and show them to you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_14</Key>
    <Value>Oh really. How familiar are you with Rune Magic, Initiate?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Sabotage_14_a</Key>
    <Value>Uh...Not at all, actually.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_15</Key>
    <Value>Right, so...Why are you even offering? Rune Magic doesn’t work like that.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Sabotage_14_b</Key>
    <Value>I know the basics.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_16</Key>
    <Value>Uh huh. Well, let me explain some advanced theory to you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Sabotage_14_c</Key>
    <Value>I know the Advanced Syntax.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_17</Key>
    <Value>Oh. Impressive. But you see the problem then, right?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_18</Key>
    <Value>Runes have a multitude of contexts depending on positioning, ordering and inflection. It's like a language where each letter’s meaning can change drastically. Each rune also has a magical signature that can't be passed on with just sketches.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Sabotage_13_b</Key>
    <Value>You’re asking me to commit sabotage.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_19</Key>
    <Value>If I have just a sketch, which I already do, I can hazard a guess at how to compel the rune, but I'm still just shooting fireballs in the dark. I might succeed, or I might trigger some completely unintended and unhelpful effect.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Sabotage_00</Key>
    <Value>I would much rather avoid any unpleasant surprises, thank you. Do not “wing it”, as you humans say, unless you absolutely must.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_20</Key>
    <Value>I've got an especially good eidetic memory, I just need 15 minutes in front of that wall and I'll know everything I need to know. But if I don't get that delay...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Sabotage_20_a</Key>
    <Value>How essential is this one rune?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_21</Key>
    <Value>It’s important enough that &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;I'm asking you to perform sabotage&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; against a Dean and put your life in danger. I’m not asking this of you lightly.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Sabotage_21_a</Key>
    <Value>A few mysterious setbacks, coming right up, then!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Sabotage_21_b</Key>
    <Value>...This had better pay real well. You’re asking me to risk my entire career.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_22</Key>
    <Value>I’ve spent the last few hours putting together the details of the job. Here's what we know for sure.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_23</Key>
    <Value>One, the tunnel in question is in the part of the factory accessible through a &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ruined Golem Warehouse&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, in the old battlefield just beyond the front gate. I don’t know how the Wolfgang got a key to the place, but you’ll likely need your own.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_24</Key>
    <Value>Two, the Wolfgang Mercs have been hired to run security for the mine tunnel. There are at least 2 guys, plus one dog Golem with the new Power Coil model as backup patrolling near the tunnel entrance.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_25</Key>
    <Value>Three, The mercs have also been hired to provide the explosives, although in order to get certain materials, they're taking out a series of loans from the Mercantile Provost.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_26</Key>
    <Value>Four, The Engineering Branch said they've detected another splinter tunnel that goes into the part of the factory under the Mana lake, near the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Troglodyte Warren&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; down there.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_27</Key>
    <Value>So, I've put together five options we could pursue to delay the project. Here’s the plan...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_28</Key>
    <Value>Option 1, &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;remove the Power Coil from the Dog Golem that’s guarding the tunnel&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, and replace it with this busted one. The Golem will be on low power Scourge detection mode, so you should be able to sneak up and make the switch easily.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_29</Key>
    <Value>Do that, and they'll need to scramble to get a replacement. If possible, avoid confronting the actual mercenaries there. Considering how important destroying the tunnel is...Conflict there could have lasting consequences on our reputation.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_30</Key>
    <Value>Option 2, &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;sabotage the detonators&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; that the mercs will use. They're likely to use &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;three explosive packages, which they should be keeping at their camp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. All you need to do is swap the red wires in the bombs with the blue ones, and they won't work as intended.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_31</Key>
    <Value>Option 3, if that side-tunnel that goes &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;under the mana lake&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; is actually connected to a trog burrow, throw this pot of &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Helen’s Troglodyte Pesticide&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; down there. It’ll flush them towards the mine tunnel where they’ll sow confusion among the guards.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_32</Key>
    <Value>And lastly, we can try to call in a favor or two from the academy’s provosts. You might be able to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;convince the Mercantile provost, Sekiguchi,  &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; to withhold the next few loans, which will force the Wolfgang to delay.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_33</Key>
    <Value>Finally, the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Academic Provost, Hugo, &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; is nominally the head of Sorobor while the Headmaster is gone. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;A letter from him&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; to delay the demolition might buy us a little time.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_34</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_35</Key>
    <Value>Now, get this done swiftly and thoroughly, but try not to go overboard, alright? We just need to buy some time, not shut the entire operation down.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_36</Key>
    <Value>I'd split this between you and Desy, but I’ve sent her to Berg to go request an official response from the Headmaster. I don't know if I can trust the rest of my branch, so you're all I've got.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Sabotage_36_a</Key>
    <Value>You trust me more than people who you’ve worked with for years?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_37</Key>
    <Value>In general? No. For dealing with Victor? Yes. I know that in no uncertain terms he has it out for you. You have no reason to go back to him.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Sabotage_37_b</Key>
    <Value>I’m on it. I’ll be back when I’m done.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_37_b</Key>
    <Value>So, how’s the mission going? Do you have an update for me?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Sabotage_37_a</Key>
    <Value>I'm not done just yet...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Sabotage_37_d</Key>
    <Value>I’m done.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Sabotage_37_c</Key>
    <Value>Can you run the plan by me again?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_37-2</Key>
    <Value>Alright, I’ll go over the plan again. Listen up!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_38</Key>
    <Value>You weren’t able to get a single task done? *sigh* I really expected more of you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_39</Key>
    <Value>Are you sure? You’re positive that we can’t make the outcome more certain?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Sabotage_39_a</Key>
    <Value>I'm positive we're in the clear. Any more would be unsafe.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_40</Key>
    <Value>This looks like it’ll be close. Very close. But it should work. Good job out there [PlayerName].</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_41</Key>
    <Value>It feels like you did a little bit of overkill, but better safe than sorry. Excellent work, [PlayerName].</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_42</Key>
    <Value>Good job out the-...Wait, you did everything on the list? Didn't I say not to go overboard? Well, let's just hope that doesn’t have unintended consequences. We actually do need that tunnel blocked before the Scourge use it...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_43</Key>
    <Value>Well...All we can do now is wait until Desy comes back with news from the Headmaster...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_44</Key>
    <Value>Hah! Success! You delayed the demolition long enough that Desy was able to get an official letter from the headmaster through! I have both the time and the authority to go examine that Rune Wall!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_45</Key>
    <Value>Excellent work, [PlayerName]. You’ve earned your reward. Now, I have runes to memorize!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_46</Key>
    <Value>Word just came in. They’ve gone and demolished the tunnel....</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Sabotage_47</Key>
    <Value>*sigh* I guess we’ll just have to make do without that critical rune. You did put your life on the line, so I can’t in good conscience deny you a reward...But damn if this doesn’t sting.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Objective_SO_Sabotage_01</Key>
    <Value>(This looks like one of the bombs that will be used to demolish the tunnel)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Objective_SO_Sabotage_01_b</Key>
    <Value>Time to sabotage this thing...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Objective_SO_Sabotage_02</Key>
    <Value>(You easily swap the wires. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;This bomb has been successfully sabotaged&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;!)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Objective_SO_Sabotage_03</Key>
    <Value>(That’s all three bombs sabotaged. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;This objective is completed&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;!)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Objective_SO_Sabotage_04</Key>
    <Value>(The dog Golem is on low-power mode, as expected. You could easily swap its Power Coil for the defective one)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Objective_SO_Sabotage_05</Key>
    <Value>(You swap the Coil with little difficulty. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Dog Golem has been successfully sabotaged!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Objective_SO_Sabotage_06</Key>
    <Value>(This is definitely the Troglodyte Tunnel that Gregory told you about. Throwing the Trog Pesticide down there should flush them away from the entrance, and down further, towards the mine tunnel).</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Objective_SO_Sabotage_06_a</Key>
    <Value>I’ll just chuck that Troglodyte Pesticide down there...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Objective_SO_Sabotage_07</Key>
    <Value>(Almost immediately, you hear gurgled screams of discomfort from the tunnel, and the thudding of Troglodyte feet fleeing deeper inside. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Looks like the plan is working!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercantile_SO_Sabotage_01</Key>
    <Value>I’m not sure you’re aware, but the Blue Chamber Collective and Levant have gone to war. This is a very strong time to turn a profit in the sale of supplies or weapons. I’d advise you to jump on this chance on this before the war cools off!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Mercantile_SO_Sabotage_01_a</Key>
    <Value>I need a favor...I need you to squeeze the Wolfgang Mercenaries finances a little.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercantile_SO_Sabotage_02</Key>
    <Value>Oh, is that all? And why, pray tell, is that?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Mercantile_SO_Sabotage_02_a</Key>
    <Value>It’s...Ah...A trade secret.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercantile_SO_Sabotage_03</Key>
    <Value>I suppose I could hold off on their next loan of cash for a few days...But the question is, what’s in it for me? Tell me, [PlayerName] are you frightened of ghosts?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercantile_SO_Sabotage_04</Key>
    <Value>Hmm. Well, &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;I do owe you a little favor&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; for that business with the vanishing pilgrims...That information has been a gold mine for me. Very well, I’ll hold off on their next loan for a few days, just for you, my friend.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Mercantile_SO_Sabotage_03_a</Key>
    <Value>Ghosts don’t scare me. I can handle them in a fight if I need to.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Mercantile_SO_Sabotage_03_b</Key>
    <Value>Ghosts? No thank you, I don’t want to hear any more of this!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercantile_SO_Sabotage_05</Key>
    <Value>Very well. Up to the north is &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Old Harmattan&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, the old district where the elected nobles of the last age of this city governed. They barricaded themselves in there during the worst of the Scourge assault.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercantile_SO_Sabotage_06</Key>
    <Value>Well, the place is wall-to-wall ghosts now. No one is permitted to open that front gate, for fear that the ghosts will start roaming the region searching for prey. They seem content enough to stay put otherwise.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercantile_SO_Sabotage_07</Key>
    <Value>Enclosed in that living tomb with all their riches, we can only assume they all turned on one another and refused to move on out of spite or misery. I want a specific kind of wealth from them.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercantile_SO_Sabotage_08</Key>
    <Value>There should be an &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;old ledger&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; somewhere in there, with records of ancient debts. I should be able to...Hmmm...Hold that over a handful of people. The threat alone of that knowledge would be enough.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercantile_SO_Sabotage_09</Key>
    <Value>I’ve heard tell that the ledger was stored in a &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;basement, near the outer walls, far from the sealed doors. Find that basement, grab the ledger, and bring it to me&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Only then will I take care of this little favor for you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Mercantile_SO_Sabotage_09_a</Key>
    <Value>I got your ledger for you!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercantile_SO_Sabotage_10</Key>
    <Value>So it really does exist...And it’s in better condition than I expected! Yes, I think I’m going to be able to put this to some very good use, yes indeed...Consider those loans to the Wolfgang Mercenaries delayed, Initiate.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ledger_SO_Sabotage_01</Key>
    <Value>(This looks like the ledger you were tasked with retrieving. Better &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;bring it to the Mercantile Provost&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Sabotage_01</Key>
    <Value>I loathe whenever the Headmaster has to leave the city. Everyone comes to me for any individual problem! As if I didn’t have enough work on my plate already!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Sabotage_01-2</Key>
    <Value>I can’t see why the Chamberlords would have reason to think the Headmaster could have anything to do with the attack on their recent council meeting. At least, not enough reason to justify demanding he make the journey all the way to Berg!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Academic_SO_Sabotage_01-2_a</Key>
    <Value>I need a favor. I need a letter asking for the delay of that tunnel demolition.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Sabotage_02</Key>
    <Value>I see...Do you understand how essential it is to shut that tunnel down? For something this important, only the Headmaster would have the authority to delay it, even for a single day!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Sabotage_03</Key>
    <Value>That said...&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;You’ve done VERY right by me already&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, what with that evidence you picked up in the marsh. I’ll return the favor. Just give me a moment...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Sabotage_04</Key>
    <Value>Well, look what I found just lying around! A letter, demanding a single day’s delay for the demolition, with the Headmaster’s signature on it! Don’t tell anyone where it came from or I’ll see to it you’re expelled, understand?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Sabotage_05</Key>
    <Value>By the by, have I told you that I offer *ahem* “Calligraphy lessons”? &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;300 Silver&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, paid in advance, and I can show you how to sign your name all fancy, just like the headmaster does.  ...Do you follow what I’m really saying?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Academic_SO_Sabotage_05_a</Key>
    <Value>Yes sir, I understand exactly what you mean. I’ll be back with the money shortly.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Academic_SO_Sabotage_05_b</Key>
    <Value>On second thought, this sounds far too risky. Forget I said anything.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Academic_SO_Sabotage_05_c</Key>
    <Value>Here’s your 300 silver. Now, about those lessons...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Sabotage_06</Key>
    <Value>Nevermind the lessons. Here, I have a “practice letter” for you. It’s written exactly in the headmaster’s style, and the signature will match precisely.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Academic_SO_Sabotage_06_a</Key>
    <Value>And it’s a letter about delaying a tunnel demolition! What a happy “coincidence”.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Sabotage_07</Key>
    <Value>Indeed. Now, let us never speak of this again. Don’t tell anyone where this came from, or I’ll see you expelled, understand?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Sabotage_01</Key>
    <Value>I know what your master is doing. The Tracker Coil doesn’t lie. There’s literally an Immaculate somewhere in Harmattan! You and Turnbull brought the enemy into our city!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Sabotage_02</Key>
    <Value>I think I know what you’re trying to do with those Immaculates. You’re trying to change them. But you won’t be able to. You can’t change what you are. Even IF you change their nature, there’s nothing stopping them from killing by choice.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Artois_SO_Sabotage_02_a</Key>
    <Value>Is Victor at least treating you alright?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Sabotage_03</Key>
    <Value>He’s made me a full Scholar for my work. The Wolfgang’s been training me personally. And trust me, we’re going to find those missing Immaculates and destroy them.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Sabotage_04</Key>
    <Value>Please, stop letting Turnbull manipulate you. It’s bad enough he somehow got to Desy. I can’t understand how she could leave Victor over him trying to trap the Butcher, only to turn around and work with the enemy herself! It’s insanity!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Artois_SO_Sabotage_02_b</Key>
    <Value>Victor literally made a deal with the Butcher. We’re just trying to stop the Scourge.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Sabotage_05</Key>
    <Value>Wrong. Victor tried to USE the Butcher of Men, he tried to trap him. You are literally working with the enemy! You really think those...Monsters can be saved? If you do, you are naive to the extreme.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Sabotage_06</Key>
    <Value>They are using you. Even if you can end their hatred of Elatt, they’ll just use that to pretend to be reformed, and then they’ll stab us all in the back. It’s in their very nature to kill!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Sabotage_01</Key>
    <Value>Your Turnbull is not gentle in his magical prodding. I can only hope he finds the solution he seeks before my patience wears out...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Immaculate_SO_Sabotage_01_a</Key>
    <Value>It’s noble of you to want to “fix” yourself.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Sabotage_02</Key>
    <Value>Hmph. Don’t patronize me, human. I find it...Upsetting that my nature drives me to kill and maim. Ending life relieves my suffering, yes, but it hurts something deep inside me. Some ancient memory that is forever just inches from my grasp.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Sabotage_03</Key>
    <Value>I gave up long ago on recollecting what I was before I awoke as Immaculate. All that matters is what I do with my life in the present moment. And what I want is peace. Freedom. The chance to create a future for myself of my own choosing.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Immaculate_SO_Sabotage_01_b</Key>
    <Value>You called those other Immaculates your Kin... Are they...Family?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Sabotage_04</Key>
    <Value>Family...That word is familiar, but I’m not certain. All Immaculates can tell one another apart without need for names, or personal connection to one another. We form packs based on shared goals or ideas. So...No, they are not “family”.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Sabotage_05</Key>
    <Value>I suppose I call other Immaculates my kin because we CAN form these bonds with one another. I pity the Grotesques...They may share our physical form, but they lack the ability to feel, and think as we do. It...Unsettles me to be honest.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Sabotage_06</Key>
    <Value>I am thankful I was spared that fate. To see a mirror image of myself, a mindless animal motivated only by our killing urge...It is one of the reasons I decided I must find a way to cast off these magical shackles and become free.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Immaculate_SO_Sabotage_01_c</Key>
    <Value>So, you know that what drives you to kill is the effect of a spell, right?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Sabotage_07</Key>
    <Value>Yes, Turnbull proved it to me. I should be enraged, but instead, I feel only anguish. My freedom is shackled, because a human made it so. And yet...I feel like we were never intended. Like we are some unhappy mistake that should never have been.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Sabotage_08</Key>
    <Value>Whomever created us...They had no right to meddle with such primal magic. No living being deserves our fate.. None would want to be a slave to such a spell, to be hunted and feared for something that was never your fault to begin with.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Immaculate_SO_Sabotage_01_d</Key>
    <Value>What will you do if we fail?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Sabotage_09</Key>
    <Value>Hmph. Do everything you can, human. Because should this fail, I will have no choice but to accept that there is no salvation for my kind. Perhaps I will have to accept that only way I will know peace is to slay what cannot be slain.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Sabotage_10</Key>
    <Value>Hmm...No. I suppose I would retreat from the world to wait in solitude until time finally claims me. I am weary of violence and pain, and this impossible task my Kin and I are bound to.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Sabotage_01</Key>
    <Value>Huh? What are you doing here in Berg? Turnbull told me you’d be trying to buy me some time! You should be in Harmattan!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Desy_SO_Sabotage_01_a</Key>
    <Value>I just thought you could use a hand.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Sabotage_02</Key>
    <Value>There’s nothing you can do for now. I’m bothering the guards day and night already. Until they let Headmaster Salaberry speak with anyone from the Academy, all we can do is wait.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Sabotage_03</Key>
    <Value>So please, get back to Harmattan and delay that demolition as much as you can! I’m counting on you to do your part!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Desy_SO_Sabotage_01_b</Key>
    <Value>I’m on personal business.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Sabotage_04</Key>
    <Value>Personal- ...Our entire project is about to go up in smoke and you’re on personal business?! Get back to work before I boot you back to Harmattan myself!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnMerc_SO_Sabotage_01</Key>
    <Value>Ugh, I hate whenever I’m assigned to guard that little tower shack. It’s cold and windy up there! I know why we HAVE to guard it, but...We should just dismantle the damn thing, it’s a security liability for the entire Wolfgang camp!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>HighClassInnNews_SO_Sabotage_01</Key>
    <Value>One of the Wolfgang guys was bragging around here that he got a promotion for finding a key to get into the ancient warehouse that’s near the clock tower out there.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>HighClassInnNews_SO_Sabotage_02</Key>
    <Value>He said he managed to dig up the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;key&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; somewhere under the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;old Hippodrome&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Although to be honest, I kind of doubt that. Why would there be a connection to the old Golem Production Facility under the Hippodrome, of all places?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>LowClassInnNews_SO_Sabotage_01</Key>
    <Value>One of my regulars came back seriously spooked the other day. He found this &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;cave North of town, near some shallow water, just a little East of Old Harmattan&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. So, like you do, he poked around in there.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>LowClassInnNews_SO_Sabotage_02</Key>
    <Value>Turns out that it led to some basements under that accused place. He nearly got skewered by a swarm of ghosts in there!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Engineering_SO_Sabotage_01</Key>
    <Value>These new Power Coils we’re being asked to make...Yes, I could see these being the key to victory against the Scourge! I only wish I’d been the one to invent them!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Naturalist_SO_Sabotage_01</Key>
    <Value>My Master of Potioncraft is demanding a raise. I hate cutting down our profits, but he IS my greatest source of them...Bah, I guess I have no choice...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>History_SO_Sabotage_01</Key>
    <Value>It’s such a shame the old Rune Trains are still out of commission...What I wouldn’t give to see one of them soar across the region while I still live...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Divided_00</Key>
    <Value>I’m making good progress on the spell. All we need to do is push a little further and hope that Victor doesn’t trace the sabotage to us, and we should be in the clear. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;I’ll let you know the moment I need you&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, [PlayerName].</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Divided_01</Key>
    <Value>We have a problem, Initiate. A serious problem. Victor’s played his hand.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Divided_02</Key>
    <Value>His Tracker Power Coil project is complete and is in full production. And he’s used it to prove to the Headmaster that we’ve been harboring an Immaculate inside the city walls.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Divided_03</Key>
    <Value>To make matters worse, a Wolfgang scout spotted a small army of Scourge beasts heading into the region, and then lost track of them. I fear that Victor intends to frame us as working with the Scourge hordes directly.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Divided_04</Key>
    <Value>The Headmaster has called an inquiry into the matter. I’ve managed to petition for the right to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;defend ourselves in debate&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; there. He’s given us some time to prepare, but it’s not much.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Divided_04_a</Key>
    <Value>We haven’t even pacified the Immaculate yet! Are we going to be ready for this?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Divided_04_b</Key>
    <Value>Then let’s crush Victor at this debate. What do we know about it?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Divided_05</Key>
    <Value>Looking at the situation, I think I know the main subjects that Victor will try to turn on us. The effectiveness of the experiment, the actions we’ve taken to perform it, and the safety of Harmattan.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Divided_06</Key>
    <Value>Considering what we’ve put together for the experiment...I think &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;it looks quite promising&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Unless we seriously fumble the debate, we should be able to rub Victor’s nose in our success.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Divided_07</Key>
    <Value>Considering what we’ve put together for the experiment...Performing it on such short notice is going to be a little difficult. I have faith I can make it appear to work, but &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;we’ll need to absolutely nail the debate&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; in order to convince the Headmaster.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Divided_08</Key>
    <Value>Considering what we’ve put together for the experiment...Ugh...&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;We’re not ready&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. We’re definitely not ready. I’m not certain we’ll be able to pacify our friend here in time, at least not in a way that will satisfy the Headmaster.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Divided_09</Key>
    <Value>As far as our methods go...You’ve kept your nose pretty clean and &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;you’ve been a credit to the Academy&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Unless you make a serious mistake at the debate, Victor’s only got allegations, and no proof.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Divided_10</Key>
    <Value>As far as our methods go...&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;It’s a little complex&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Your reputation’s not exactly stellar, but I’m sure that if you cleverly deflect any accusations Victor throws your way, you can come out of this with minimal damage to our reputation.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Divided_11</Key>
    <Value>As far as our methods go...It doesn’t reflect well on us at all, [PlayerName]. I know you did what you had to do, but &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Victor will absolutely seize on your reputation to attack us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Divided_12</Key>
    <Value>And security-wise...&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;I think we’re fine&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Against all odds, we’ve managed to maintain the safety of the region. Barring any unhappy surprises, there isn’t much Victor can use against us here.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Divided_13</Key>
    <Value>And security-wise...Our actions have, at least somewhat, compromised Harmattan’s safety. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;We should to our best not to antagonize the situation further&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Divided_14</Key>
    <Value>And security-wise... Our actions have definitely compromised Harmattan’s security. Enough that &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Victor barely has to make an argument in order to crush us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; here.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Divided_02</Key>
    <Value>Bear in mind that Victor’s probably still furious that you turned on him, [PlayerName]. He’s likely going to think you are the weakest link at the debate and keep directing his attacks towards you. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Prepare good arguments&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; in case he does.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Divided_14_a</Key>
    <Value>Let him come after me, I can handle any accusations he throws our way.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Divided_14_b</Key>
    <Value>Ugh, I’m more comfortable with weapons than words. This could go poorly...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Divided_15</Key>
    <Value>We have enough time to try to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;get another Dean to support us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.  But &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;we can’t afford to be late&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Don’t take needless risks, understand?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Divided_16</Key>
    <Value>If you think we need help with the experiment, try to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;get the Naturalist Branch to help us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Their alchemists should be able to make some kind of potion that will reduce the Immaculate’s resistance to rune magic.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Divided_17</Key>
    <Value>If you’re worried that Victor will use your reputation and actions against us, &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;speak with the Dean of the History Branch, Joliette&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. She is intensely well respected by the Academy, so if she vouches for you, it should deflect the worst that Victor can say.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Divided_18</Key>
    <Value>And if you think security is our weakness, go &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;see if the Engineering Dean can help us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. I’m sure he has plenty of extra Golems in his workshop we could get up and running to patrol the region.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Divided_19</Key>
    <Value>Once you’ve gotten someone’s support, &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;meet up with us in the Military Training Area in the North-East of Harmattan&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Victor insisted we have our discussion on his home turf.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Divided_19_a</Key>
    <Value>What are you and Desy going to do?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Arcane_SO_Divided_19_b</Key>
    <Value>Alright, got it. I’ll be back with help!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Divided_20</Key>
    <Value>I’m going to try to pacify the Immaculate immediately. More time would have been appreciated, but we can’t afford to delay any longer. Desy’s staying here with me for assistance so, unfortunately, &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;you’re on your own&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; again.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Divided_21</Key>
    <Value>We can only stretch the Headmaster’s patience about &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;20 days&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; at most. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;If you show up late, we risk losing any leverage you might have earned&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. So get on it, [PlayerName]. It’s do or die.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Divided_22</Key>
    <Value>Alright Immaculate, we’re on the clock. We’ll need to skip over some of the precautions I talked to you about and get started right now. The sooner we begin, the more time we’ll have to get this done right!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Divided_01</Key>
    <Value>Understood. Ready or not, we are out of time. Do what you need to do, Turnbull.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Arcane_SO_Divided_23</Key>
    <Value>No time, can’t talk, I’m up to my eyeballs in complex spellwork right now and can’t afford a distraction!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Immaculate_SO_Divided_02</Key>
    <Value>Ugh...This feels...Wrong. I feel like parts of my body are trying to burst out of me...Whatever Turnbull is doing is at least having some effect...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Divided_01</Key>
    <Value>I keep going over the runes that Turnbull wants us to use. I think these should work, but...Considering we don’t fully understand what kind of spell was used to create the Scourge, there’s far too many unknowns for my liking.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_Divided_03</Key>
    <Value>We’re counting on you to get that extra support, [PlayerName]. Leave this to us!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_Divided_01</Key>
    <Value>You’re one of Turnbull’s Initiates, aren’t you? I must confess my shock that you would do something as foolhardy as bringing an Immaculate into the city.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_Divided_02</Key>
    <Value>I sincerely hope that Turnbull can actually prove that it is possible to pacify them. If he’s wrong...There may be considerable consequences for the danger that he put our Academy in.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_Divided_03</Key>
    <Value>Now, hold on for just one moment. Do you realize that [PlayerName] was the one who exposed Jager Sullivan’s crimes? They had no reason to take such action if they were using nefarious means. I will have no sullying of their name at this conference!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_Divided_04</Key>
    <Value>...I am unconvinced by your experiment, Turnbull...But I’m willing to give you a chance, regardless. Stopping the Scourge demands bold, decisive action.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_Divided_05</Key>
    <Value>(You have the distinct impression that &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Headmaster Salaberry has repaid the favor&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; he owes you...)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Naturalist_SO_Divided_01</Key>
    <Value>Well, hey. Looks like your branch of the academy is in some real hot water now. I’m going to enjoy watching these fireworks.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Naturalist_SO_Divided_01_a</Key>
    <Value>Turnbull needs a potion that will reduce a creature’s resistance to Rune Magic.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Naturalist_SO_Divided_02</Key>
    <Value>Wait...You’re coming to ME for help? I’m in enough trouble as it is these days, I don’t need any more-...Wait...If you scratch our back, we’ll scratch yours. There’s something I need help with.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Naturalist_SO_Divided_03</Key>
    <Value>So, some...People I was working with have gone and turned on me. They want a pay raise, and have stolen some of my goods until I give them what they want. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Recover my goods, and inform them they’re being let go&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, and I’ll get you what you need.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Naturalist_SO_Divided_03_a</Key>
    <Value>Why do I get the feeling none of this is...Legal?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Naturalist_SO_Divided_04</Key>
    <Value>You know what they say about throwing stones in glass houses, don’t you? You’re working with LITERAL monsters. You don’t get to judge. Are you in, or not?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Naturalist_SO_Divided_04_a</Key>
    <Value>Alright, let’s trade services. I save your hide, you save ours.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Naturalist_SO_Divided_04_b</Key>
    <Value>No thank you. I will have no part in this!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Naturalist_SO_Divided_05</Key>
    <Value>&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;In the east of the Antique Plateau, just North of the Cultural District&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, you’ll find what’s left of the Fourwinds District. Look for &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;a ruined house with a dangling skeleton&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; not far from it. My former allies are in there.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Naturalist_SO_Divided_06</Key>
    <Value>Tell the goons inside our arrangement is over, and then &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;come back here with my little wooden box&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. How you manage to do that is entirely up to you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Naturalist_SO_Divided_07</Key>
    <Value>Well, I’ll be. You came back with the goods. I’m glad I took a gamble on you! Your friend, Desy, she came around here while you were gone. She’s already taken the potion to Turnbull for use in your little science project. Best of luck to you, then!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bandit_SO_Divided_01</Key>
    <Value>Well well, you again. The Soroborean who came for that little Sirocco box all that while ago. Ain’t this a surprise!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Bandit_SO_Divided_01_a</Key>
    <Value>You’ve taken some goods that belong to Erica Kasper. Hand them back over.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bandit_SO_Divided_02</Key>
    <Value>We’re outlaws, punk, we take what we want. And that hag up in the academy hasn’t been paying us what she promised either. We’re taking these goods and we’re getting out of this place to go find more profitable routes to plunder!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bandit_SO_Divided_03</Key>
    <Value>So no, you ain’t gettin’ her stuff back. In fact...Drop your bag and empty your pockets! Or don’t! Any excuse to shank someone today would make me REAL happy!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>StolenGoods_SO_Divided_01</Key>
    <Value>(This looks like the box of Erica’s stolen goods! Better take them back to her!)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>History_SO_Divided_01</Key>
    <Value>They say history favors the bold. So, as reckless as your Dean’s plan to pacify the Scourge is...I do hope he succeeds. That would be quite an excellent addition to Sorobor’s storied history.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_History_SO_Divided_01_a</Key>
    <Value>We need a favor. Would you be willing to support us at the debate?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>History_SO_Divided_02</Key>
    <Value>Ah, you want my voice, do you? Well, this timing is most opportune. To my dismay, I actually do have need of a nasty ruin-diving mercenary thug for something. Get me what I need, and I’ll gladly give you my support.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>History_SO_Divided_03</Key>
    <Value>I’ve always wanted to properly examine the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Old Theater in the East of Antique Plateau&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Unfortunately, the bridge was destroyed long before I was even born. But, I’ve heard tell that it’s possible to get in there from the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;old tunnels underneath the region&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>History_SO_Divided_04</Key>
    <Value>If you can find a way to get to that Old Theater, I need to you to find a particular painting that was last seen there. It’s a simple portrait of the man who founded Harmattan.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>History_SO_Divided_05</Key>
    <Value>&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bring it to me&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, safe and unblemished, and I will trust in you and Turnbull, no matter what your other actions have been thus far.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_History_SO_Divided_05_a</Key>
    <Value>One piece of art, brought here safely, got it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_History_SO_Divided_05_b</Key>
    <Value>On second thought, I’ve changed my mind, I don’t think I need your help.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_History_SO_Divided_01_b</Key>
    <Value>I found the portrait!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>History_SO_Divided_06</Key>
    <Value>This is...Hah! I must apologize for my conduct towards you earlier. You have done the history of Aurai much good today, [PlayerName]. I will be sure to sing your praises at the debate.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>art_SO_Divided_01</Key>
    <Value>(This looks like the portrait that Joliette asked you to find! You gently pack it up to bring home.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Engineering_SO_Divided_01</Key>
    <Value>So...I hear you guys have been trying to use magic to make the Scourge less violent? I can’t even pretend to understand how that would work, but if it actually does, I’ll applaud your cleverness.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Engineering_SO_Divided_01_a</Key>
    <Value>I need a favor. Is there something you can do to shore up the city’s defenses?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Engineering_SO_Divided_02</Key>
    <Value>City’s security, huh...We do have about a dozen Golems we use for maintenance practice for the apprentices...We could get them all up and running if you want. I do have something I’ll need done in return, however.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Engineering_SO_Divided_03</Key>
    <Value>You know that the old Golem Fabrication facility opened up a while back, right? Well, there are &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;some very rare and ancient parts I need&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; from there. Bring them to me, and I’ll get you those extra Golems. Deal?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Engineering_SO_Divided_04</Key>
    <Value>I need you to find 3 Mana Filters. You should be able to find some in the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Compromised Mana Transfer Station&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, which should be connected to the old Golem Test Chambers. They should be connected to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;some wall-mounted device, emitting blue-ish vapor&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Engineering_SO_Divided_04_a</Key>
    <Value>Deal. I’ll get you the parts you need!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Engineering_SO_Divided_04_b</Key>
    <Value>I don’t think I have time to waste fetching you old junk. I’ll ask someone else for help.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Engineering_SO_Divided_01_b</Key>
    <Value>I got the parts you need!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Engineering_SO_Divided_05</Key>
    <Value>Ah, right on time. The Golems have been put back together and are ready to go. So, I’ll just take these parts, and go tell my Master of Repairs to send the Golems out on patrol. Nice doing business with you!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Engineering_SO_Divided_05_a</Key>
    <Value>What are you planning to do with those filters I got for you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Engineering_SO_Divided_06</Key>
    <Value>One of my Initiates just put together a completely mad plan to deliver entire Marshmelon plants from Monsoon to Levant. The initial prototype worked as intended, so now it’s time to take his plan up a notch!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Engineering_SO_Divided_07</Key>
    <Value>These parts will not only let us improve the specialized vats we need to bring the Marshmelons with, but will also let us grow the fruits ourselves outside the marsh, allowing us to cut out the Monsoon middleman entirely. Maximum profit!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Engineering_SO_Divided_07_a</Key>
    <Value>If you’ll be able to grow them outside the marsh, why not sell that tech to Levant?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Engineering_SO_Divided_08</Key>
    <Value>Why should we? We stand to make considerably more profit if we keep it to ourselves and only sell them the end product! ...You WILL keep this our little secret, won’t you? It’d make the Academy look bad if you ran your mouth about it!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>parts_SO_Divided_01</Key>
    <Value>(This looks like one of the Mana Filters that Samuel wanted... It’s lighter than you thought!)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>parts_SO_Divided_02</Key>
    <Value>(You’ve picked up all the parts you were asked for!)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Divided_01</Key>
    <Value>I can’t believe you resorted to sabotage. I know we can’t prove it, but it’s obvious. The Immaculates have turned you into criminals! And for what? Because you think you can “heroically save the poor poor monsters from themselves”?!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Divided_02</Key>
    <Value>Now more than ever, I know that I’m on the right side! Victor would never compromise his morals on a half-dream of a theory like Turnbull would! You’re risking the safety of the entire city on a fantasy!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Artois_SO_Divided_02_a</Key>
    <Value>You’re completely wrong. And forgetting that Victor made a deal with the Butcher.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Divided_03</Key>
    <Value>You’ve invited one of the enemy into Harmattan itself! I don’t know where you’re hiding it, but the Tracker Coil’s Scourge Detector doesn’t lie! Don’t you dare put yourself on the same level as Victor!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Artois_SO_Divided_02_b</Key>
    <Value>It’s for good reason. We actually CAN cure them! He’s already pacified an Illuminator!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Divided_04</Key>
    <Value>Even if it’s for a “good cause” like you say, Turnbull is putting everyone in the city in danger! There is nothing that’s worth that kind of a risk! What if he’s wrong about the Immaculate? What if it’s just waiting to stab you all in the back?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_Divided_05</Key>
    <Value>Victor might have his faults, but he’s at least going about things the right way! Accuse him of whatever you want, he’s still more trustworthy than a literal monster!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>DebateBlocker_SO_Debate_01</Key>
    <Value>(Are you ready to begin the debate?)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gregory_SO_Debate_00</Key>
    <Value>Oh, there you are, [PlayerName]! You’re just in time!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gregory_SO_Debate_00_LATE</Key>
    <Value>About time, [PlayerName]! You’re late!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_00_LATE</Key>
    <Value>Indeed. This delay is inexcusable, and reflects poorly on your master’s case, Initiate!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ElattPriest_SO_DEBATE_00</Key>
    <Value>Oh, was this the initiate we were waiting on? Excellent. I am quite looking forward to seeing the fruits of this research, inquiry or not!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_01</Key>
    <Value>Very well, all the involved parties are here. We can begin. Victor Berthelot, you are accusing Gregory Turnbull of cooperating with the Scourge to undermine the safety of Harmattan. Please, make your case.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_02</Key>
    <Value>From the very start, Turnbull and his underlings have consistently used underhanded and criminal means to accomplish their goals! One underling in particular, that one standing right there!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_03</Key>
    <Value>The Wolfgang Mercenaries have reported an exhaustive list of complaints against [PlayerName]! Regardless of their outsider status, the Wolfgang Mercenaries are still an essential part of life in Harmattan, and they should be listened to!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_04</Key>
    <Value>For instance, [PlayerName] allowed several Immaculates to escape a trap set by the Wolfgang. The Immaculates have since completely escaped our grasp, and have caused who knows how much harm?! This clearly proves they’re working for the enemy!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_05</Key>
    <Value>Remember that tunnel that was a risk to the entire city? The Wolfgang have confirmed that [PlayerName] inflicted grevious bodily harm on the men who were there to guard the tunnel, putting not just their lives, but the lives of all of Harmattan, at serious risk!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Turnbull_SO_DEBATE_06</Key>
    <Value>I have signed letters from several of the merchants in the market square, who say that [PlayerName] has been exceptionally helpful to them. I’d say my Initiate has been an exceptional credit to the comfort of the citizens of Harmattan.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Turnbull_SO_DEBATE_07</Key>
    <Value>Are you certain that the Wolfgang didn’t start a fight with [PlayerName], forcing them to defend themselves? It wouldn’t be the first time those mercenaries picked a fight they shouldn’t have.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_08</Key>
    <Value>Both of our provosts have submitted evidence that [PlayerName] has been a great credit to the both of them. Are you certain you’re accusing the correct person, Victor?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_09</Key>
    <Value>I simply must express that until these complaints are fully addressed, [PlayerName] and thus, Gregory Turnbull should be scrutinized at the highest level! Well, what do you have to say for yourself? I demand an answer!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Victor_SO_DEBATE_09_a</Key>
    <Value>Says the one who was making deals with the Butcher of Men.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_10</Key>
    <Value>Preposterous! I merely attempted to entrap him. There isn’t a single witness who would corroborate that outlandish claim, that doesn’t have a reason to lie about it! Isn’t that right, Artois?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_DEBATE_11</Key>
    <Value>...Victor speaks the truth. He, in no way, made any kind of deal with the Butcher of Men. The only ones who try to make that claim are [PlayerName] and Desy, and both of their testimony is extremely suspect!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Victor_SO_DEBATE_09_b</Key>
    <Value>How can we trust the Wolfgang not to be lying on your behalf? You are close allies.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_12</Key>
    <Value>How DARE you attack their credibility! They have been essential to the security of the region since before you were BORN!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Turnbull_SO_DEBATE_13</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName] brings up a valid point. You and the Wolfgang Mercenaries work very closely together, and the lot of you have a vested interest in continued open conflict with the Scourge. If anyone’s motives are to be suspected, it’s your own!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Victor_SO_DEBATE_09_c</Key>
    <Value>What about when you contracted the Wolfgang to hunt me down after I left you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_14</Key>
    <Value>I’m afraid I don’t know what you’re talking about. Is there any way you can prove that? Your testimony alone is absolutely meaningless here. After all, you’re the one whose motives are being scrutinized!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_DEBATE_15</Key>
    <Value>Besides, if you’re going to sling baseless accusations, I know you committed acts of sabotage against us! The Wolfgang said so!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Artois_SO_DEBATE_15_a</Key>
    <Value>And plotting to destroy an ancient and important Rune Wall isn’t sabotage?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Turnbull_SO_DEBATE_16</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName] is correct. There was no need to place the explosives on the Rune wall itself, unless destroying it was half the point of that tunnel demolition! And lest you forget, wilful destruction of important history is a criminal act!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_17</Key>
    <Value>Artois, enough! Baseless accusations only serve to make us look weak!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Artois_SO_DEBATE_15_b</Key>
    <Value>Do you have more than just the unproven accusations of a mercenary gang as proof?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_18</Key>
    <Value>Silence, both of you! Shameless accusations without proof have no place here!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Artois_SO_DEBATE_15_c</Key>
    <Value>If pacifying the Scourge is possible...Wouldn’t your actions count as sabotage?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_19</Key>
    <Value>IF it’s possible. Your theory has not been proven. Whereas OUR actions have all been to protect the safety of Harmattan. I’d say we have the moral high ground here. Your petty deflection is worthless.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>History_SO_DEBATE_20</Key>
    <Value>I have heard enough, Victor. I have worked with [PlayerName] personally in recovering our lost history. The artifact was returned with care, which is more than I can say for our interactions in that regard. I will allow no slander of their reputation in my presence!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_21</Key>
    <Value>Hmm...I’m afraid that I find your evidence inconclusive, Victor. I don’t see enough evidence to pass any kind of decisive judgment on the activities of Turnbull and his initiates. A full investigation will be performed at a later date. For now, let us move on.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_22</Key>
    <Value>Enough. You have made your point, Victor. Turnbull and his Initiates have engaged in conduct that is at best irresponsible and at worst unlawful. A proper trial will be convened at a later date to determine the extent of the harm caused. For now, let us move on.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_23</Key>
    <Value>Very well. I would also argue that given the abysmal state of security in this city, and the impending threat of a Scourge invasion, we cannot trust in pacifying them! It would be incredibly dangerous to attempt any interaction with the Scourge at this time!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_24</Key>
    <Value>And due to the sabotage that we still insist that Turnbull ordered, several Scourge beasts managed to enter the city and kill innocent people! Until we are certain that every last means of entry have been sealed, we cannot afford any risk to our safety!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_25</Key>
    <Value>Furthermore, even if we ignore the Scourge, there is a gang of organized and well-armed bandits who are roaming around, waylaying caravans and traders. And they appear to have received a dramatic resupply of weapons as well!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Turnbull_SO_DEBATE_26</Key>
    <Value>Come now, you’ve been boasting about the power of your new Golems for quite a while. In fact, I’m rather certain that [PlayerName] ensured the prototype was essentially perfect. You do have to have faith in your own project, right?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_27</Key>
    <Value>I...Well...Yes. But that’s not the point! It’s still dangerous to deal with the Scourge like this, whether or not my new Golems are ready!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_DEBATE_28</Key>
    <Value>I’d like to mention that the Butcher of Men is confirmed to be dead. The most vicious of the Immaculates is long gone. Without his leadership, the Scourge are considerably hamstrung.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_29</Key>
    <Value>I...Alright, that’s fair. But who knows what other vicious Immaculates might be ready to take his place as the most vicious and cruel being known to mankind?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_30</Key>
    <Value>And do you actually think we can TRUST the Scourge after we pacify them? Free will still allows room for criminal, or even monstrous behaviour! Besides, what about the unintelligent Scourge? They don’t have the intellect to do anything but rampage!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Victor_SO_DEBATE_30_a</Key>
    <Value>Can you trust humans? Quite a few become vicious bandits.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_31</Key>
    <Value>Yes, I’d trust bandits over the Scourge. Outlaws are just individuals and small clans, not a massive horde that has spent the last century laying waste to all that breathes. Look outside at the mass of ruins out there! That’s all their handiwork!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Victor_SO_DEBATE_30_b</Key>
    <Value>So, you’d prefer they remain a unified horde dedicated only to slaughter?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_32</Key>
    <Value>I…N-no, I’d rather they be wiped out entirely! I question the ENTIRE merit of the experiment! We know that killing the Scourge works, we should be focusing on ways to make that easier!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Turnbull_SO_DEBATE_33</Key>
    <Value>Well, there’s no easy method for that. Even if we had hundreds of your new Golems, it would still take another century at least to put an end to the Scourge. Pacifying them does far more to remove the active threat the Scourge pose.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Victor_SO_DEBATE_30_c</Key>
    <Value>The Immaculates will be able to control the Scourge Beasts. They won’t rampage.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_34</Key>
    <Value>Oh, so the beings that can potentially choose evil will still be able to direct them to cause harm. I fail to see how that’s much of an improvement!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_35</Key>
    <Value>And what about the Wolfgang? If we go along with this harebrained scheme of yours, what happens if they don’t have enough work fighting the Scourge, and are forced to turn bandit in order to make ends meet? It would endanger the entire region!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Victor_SO_DEBATE_35_a</Key>
    <Value>Aurai is still dangerous. There will always be work for a famous group like them.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_DEBATE_36</Key>
    <Value>Yeah, or they could come help the war camps at the Gates of Catharsis if they want to actually make a difference. It’s obscene how they claim to be so essential to fighting the Scourge, while they mostly just hide in that well-defended camp of theirs!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Victor_SO_DEBATE_35_b</Key>
    <Value>If they’d do that, then they were never really our allies to begin with.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_37</Key>
    <Value>You did not grow up in Harmattan, hearing of how they helped restore the region after Elatt came to our aid, so your ignorance is not surprising. How DARE you suggest that those who have done so much for us are not our allies!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_38</Key>
    <Value>Hmm...Victor is right. The Wolfgang have done much for us, and for the stability of the region. If you believe such such callous things, I suggest you keep them to yourself, [PlayerName].</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Victor_SO_DEBATE_35_c</Key>
    <Value>So...Their employment matters more than protecting humanity from the Scourge?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_39</Key>
    <Value>Of course not, and how dare you suggest I meant that! I merely want to ensure a fair transition, so that they are not rewarded for their decades of service with sudden and unavoidable poverty!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_40</Key>
    <Value>You both make a strong point. We cannot put one organization’s survival over the safety of humanity as a whole, but neither should we abandon allies who have done so much for us. I will need to think more on how to handle this...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Engineer_SO_DEBATE_41</Key>
    <Value>Mate, I don’t see how you’re still worried about the city’s security. Even if that small force of Scourge were to attack the city, we’ve got a veritable army of Golems on patrol. The Scourge would be torn to shreds before they even made it up the cliff.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_42</Key>
    <Value>Hmm, I’m inclined to believe that the security of the city is strong enough to proceed, Victor. I see no reason to halt the project on those grounds.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_43</Key>
    <Value>Turnbull, I’m afraid I must agree with Victor. There are too many risks to the city at the moment. Unless you’ve got something very convincing in store, I may need to ask you to postpone your research until things have been properly secured.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_44</Key>
    <Value>Only one question remains in my mind...Turnbull, were your attempts successful? Can you prove to me that it is possible to pacify an Immaculate?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ElattPriest_SO_DEBATE_45</Key>
    <Value>I wish to know this as well. To me, this is single most important part of this inquiry. As far as I’m concerned, all else can be forgiven if it can be done. Please, tell me everything!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Turnbull_SO_DEBATE_46</Key>
    <Value>We have discovered that what drives the Scourge to attack Elatt’s followers in a frenzy is the effect of a spell. It seems that whomever or whatever created them did so for the express purpose of killing Elatt, and thus the Scourge are bound by that single instinct.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Turnbull_SO_DEBATE_47</Key>
    <Value>Therefore, I have developed a Counter-Spell that will nullify that command. In the bestial Scourge, it can provably turn them into mere animals, without the urge for mass violence against all that breathes.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Turnbull_SO_DEBATE_48</Key>
    <Value>And in Immaculates, it will give them the ability to ignore their instinct, and choose not to act upon it. It will remove their unifying purpose, and make them true individuals.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_49</Key>
    <Value>I’m still waiting on proof that this is even possible, Turnbull. Either show us that it’s possible, or stop wasting our time!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Turnbull_SO_DEBATE_50</Key>
    <Value>With pleasure. Desy? Could you go fetch our mutual friend?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ElattPriest_SO_DEBATE_51</Key>
    <Value>You...Actually brought an Immaculate INTO the city?! Have you lost your mind?! If you’re wrong, he’ll immediately slaughter me and then-</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>RunedImmaculate_SO_DEBATE_52</Key>
    <Value>HSSSS, your presence here fills me with anger...But...I can choose to withhold that anger. I would urge you to bite your tongue unless you absolutely MUST speak, Elatt-spawn.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_53</Key>
    <Value>Well well...An Immaculate and a priest of Elatt in the same room together. And the Immaculate can even speak Elatt’s name without succumbing to murderous rage. I am quite impressed, Turnbull!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ElattPriest_SO_DEBATE_54</Key>
    <Value>I...Me too. ...Alright, I’ve seen enough. I won’t aggravate the creature further. Now, If you’ll excuse me, I have a letter to send to the Cardinal. He will want to know about this as soon as humanly possible.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>RunedImmaculate_SO_DEBATE_55</Key>
    <Value>Gahh....Nnngg...Make him leave...Make him leave! It hurts to have him near! Make him leave, or I will kill him where he stands!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_56</Key>
    <Value>Well...That IS an improvement, if barely. It would seem like your theory needs more work, Turnbull. This isn’t the war-changing breakthrough you claimed it would be. It seems another few months of work will be necessary, at least!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ElattPriest_SO_DEBATE_57</Key>
    <Value>I feel the same. Very well, I will leave this discussion for now. Come speak to me once it is over, Salaberry, we will need to have a long discussion about this.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Turnbull_SO_Debate_58</Key>
    <Value>We are pushing the boundaries of magic, Headmaster. I would have preferred to wait another month or two until the research was complete, but Victor insisted this be discussed immediately.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_59</Key>
    <Value>And that seems to have been wise. Clearly the experiment is a failure and should be abandoned before it wastes more precious resources! We should focus our efforts on my new Golem improvements, which will slaughter the Scourge hordes with ease!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Naturalist_SO_DEBATE_60</Key>
    <Value>Well, I think we can say that the alchemic mix we provided is at least somewhat responsible for the experiment’s success. Honestly, I’m pretty impressed, considering what bloodthirsty maniacs the Immaculates usually are!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>RunedImmaculate_SO_DEBATE_61</Key>
    <Value>You realize I am still present, human? Bite your tongue, before I bite it for you!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_62</Key>
    <Value>This was all a big deal over nothing. Even if you can change the nature of individual Immaculates, that won’t change much of anything. Do you plan to invite the entire Scourge horde into Harmattan to pacify them one at a time?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Turnbull_SO_Debate_63</Key>
    <Value>Obviously not. The runic phrase emits an aura that expands over time. Anything that stays in contact with that aura for long enough will be affected by it. Careful placement of these runes will allow us to pacify the Scourge long-term.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Turnbull_SO_Debate_64</Key>
    <Value>The plan is to create runic totems, strategically placed in each region, and around any known entrance to the Gates of Catharsis. Then, we just let the aura expand and do its work.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Turnbull_SO_Debate_65</Key>
    <Value>In fact, our friend here might be able to act as an ambassador of sorts. The runic phrase is imprinted on his very body. Any Scourge he remains near for long enough should be permanently pacified by the counter-spell.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Turnbull_SO_Debate_66</Key>
    <Value>It’s by no means an instant solution, but it should radically change the course of our conflict with the Scouge within our lifetimes.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_67</Key>
    <Value>You want to just...”Plop down” a spell with such a far reaching, ever-expanding effect, all over Aurai...Just like that? The side effects of a spell like that could be devastating!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Victor_SO_DEBATE_67_a</Key>
    <Value>I would argue that the Scourge are far worse. Have you seen the ruins outside?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_68</Key>
    <Value>I’d pick the demons we know over the demons we don’t! A spell with an effect so immense is far too great a risk to ever place our hopes on!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_69</Key>
    <Value>I’m afraid I must disagree, Victor. The Scourge hordes continue to make civilization barely tenable, even with the Vigil Crystals and Elatt’s help. This is a risk, yes, but one that comes with great possibilities.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Victor_SO_DEBATE_67_b</Key>
    <Value>You don’t seem to think the same of unleashing more Golems that could go rogue!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_DEBATE_70</Key>
    <Value>Yeah, there’s plenty of Golems who are roaming wild with no control just outside our front door. They kill plenty of people every season. How can you guarantee that won’t happen with yours?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_71</Key>
    <Value>Faulty Golems can be repaired, and returned to their proper mission parameters. If the side-effects of the spell soak into Aurai itself long-term, the effects would be infinitely harder to contain or reverse! It’s a matter of scale, girl!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Victor_SO_DEBATE_67_c</Key>
    <Value>It’s a spell with an incredibly narrow effect. You’re overstating the risk of side effects.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_72</Key>
    <Value>Am I? Turnbull claims that the Scourge are influenced by a spell designed to kill Elatt. That too, is a spell with an incredibly narrow effect. And yet, look at all the destruction they have wrought! I think my concern is quite valid, [PlayerName].</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_73</Key>
    <Value>You make a compelling argument, Victor. There should be months...No, years of rigorous testing before a plan like this is put into effect. I want to know exactly what potential side effects there might be.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_74</Key>
    <Value>And you are certain this single counter-spell will work on all the Scourge that come into contact with it? Every single sub-species? How thorough was your research?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_74_a</Key>
    <Value>The Scourge are all directed by one spell. One counter-spell should work, then.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_75</Key>
    <Value>We would be taking a considerable risk if you’re wrong. It is unlikely that a universal solution will be so easy. Just because it works on Immaculates and Illuminators doesn’t prove it’ll work on Shelled Horrors or Grotesques!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_74_b</Key>
    <Value>We can fine-tune it later. The species that really matters is the Immaculates.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Turnbull_SO_DEBATE_76</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName] is right. Starting with them will cripple the brains behind the Scourge, which will stop the worst of the attacks. From there, we can proceed to make any changes we need to, if the counter-spell happens to not be universal.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_77</Key>
    <Value>...Hmm...Indeed. This would provoke dramatic change, even if it does not resolve the entire problem outright. I have no outright objections to that proposal.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_74_c</Key>
    <Value>We won’t know until we try, right? And we can’t try unless you give us your approval.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_78</Key>
    <Value>...Fair point. I suppose we won’t know the full effects until we try it. I confess myself skeptical...But perhaps...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>RunedImmaculate_SO_DEBATE_79</Key>
    <Value>Are you merely going to speak for me, and about me, as if I am not present?! Do I not deserve to speak for myself?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_80</Key>
    <Value>No! You are a monster, a creature created purely for destruction! You have no such right! Consider yourself lucky to even be breathing, Immaculate!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>RunedImmaculate_SO_DEBATE_81</Key>
    <Value>Monster, am I? I am a monster only by the circumstance of my creation, human. I did not choose this form, nor did I ask for my killing urge. What do you say we compare the actions we have taken, given the freedom we are capable of?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>RunedImmaculate_SO_DEBATE_82</Key>
    <Value>You have the freedom to pursue whatever you please, and yet you choose to do harm. You use your words to cause hurt, your power to dominate and control, and you ally with men who will slay anyone, innocent or not, on the promise of coin!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_83</Key>
    <Value>You...You DARE lecture me, Scourge Beast?!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>RunedImmaculate_SO_DEBATE_84</Key>
    <Value>Meanwhile, I chose to come here, risking my life and the life of my kin, on the smallest chance that I could obtain that same freedom you abuse. I fought claw and talon against my instinct to cause harm, and searched for a way to overcome it!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>RunedImmaculate_SO_DEBATE_85</Key>
    <Value>Your intentions, your circumstances of birth...All of these are meaningless! It is your actions that determine who you truly are. And I have confidence that the few actions I was freely able to make are less monstrous than those you made fully willingly!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_86</Key>
    <Value>That is enough, Immaculate. There is no need for personal attacks. I have made my decision.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>RunedImmaculate_SO_DEBATE_87</Key>
    <Value>And you, head master of these humans, are hardly any better. Look at some of those you have surrounded yourself with. You have the chance to make them do better, and yet you do not. You are nearly as guilty as they are.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>RunedImmaculate_SO_DEBATE_88</Key>
    <Value>You all claim that we Immaculates must use our new freedom responsibly, to guide and control the rest of the Scourge. And yet, YOU, human head master, do not do the same for the humans you are responsible for!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_89</Key>
    <Value>...You are quite right, Immaculate. I have indeed compromised, in order to create what I believe is a better world. But compromise is the way of humanity. And that...Is why I will give you and your kin a chance. Everyone deserves one, no matter their origin.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_90</Key>
    <Value>Enough. While I am impressed with your efforts, Turnbull, I don’t share the sentiment that this is a feasible large-scale solution. And I concur with Victor’s other very valid concerns. This project is cancelled. Permanently.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_91</Key>
    <Value>That’s enough. Although this experiment shows great promise...I cannot turn a blind eye to the other concerns. Turnbull, I forbid you from continuing work until further notice.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>RunedImmaculate_SO_DEBATE_92</Key>
    <Value>Hmph. I should have known. Humanity cannot be trusted to help us. No one can.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_93</Key>
    <Value>As for you, Immaculate...You have not harmed anyone here, so, I will allow you to leave. But should we find you again, you will be treated as any other Scourge Beast.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>RunedImmaculate_SO_DEBATE_94</Key>
    <Value>Hmph, your fairness is noted, human. You will not see me again.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_95</Key>
    <Value>Now, as to the matter of the invading Scourge Beasts...Our Tracker Power Coil suspects &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;they’re holed up in Old Harmattan&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Please, allow me to deploy our new Golems! Let me show you what they are capable of!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_96</Key>
    <Value>Granted. You have authority to proceed as you see fit. See to the destruction of those Scourge immediately, Victor!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_97</Key>
    <Value>And you, Turnbull...If you and your Initiates wish to prove to me that you are not, in fact, in league with those Scourge...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Turnbull_SO_DEBATE_98</Key>
    <Value>I understand, Headmaster. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;[PlayerName], Desy, I need you to go assist Victor’s forces at Old Harmattan&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_DEBATE_99</Key>
    <Value>Doing anything for Victor leaves a real bad taste in my mouth, but fine. Killin’ some hostile Scourge is no problem for me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_100</Key>
    <Value>Heh, well, it’s nice to have the two of you back on the right side, even if it’s just for a short while. Perhaps you’ll see the error of your ways now.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Victor_SO_DEBATE_100_a</Key>
    <Value>...Don’t push your luck, Victor.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Victor_SO_DEBATE_100_b</Key>
    <Value>Alright, alright, enough gloating. What’s the plan?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_101</Key>
    <Value>I seem to have struck a nerve, I see. Very well, there is &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;a small cave east of Old Harmattan that leads underneath it&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. We’ll attack from through there. The Scourge won’t even know what hit them before it’s too late.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_DEBATE_102</Key>
    <Value>I’ll meet you there, [PlayerName]. Grab your sharpest weapon and let’s get this mess dealt with!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_103</Key>
    <Value>That’s enough debate. Despite the rough state of the project, I feel comfortable with how you’re proceeding, Turnbull. We have details to discuss, but I give you permission to proceed nonetheless.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_104</Key>
    <Value>Well, I’m convinced, Turnbull. This is an exceptional breakthrough. You have the full support of the Academy. There are details to discuss, but overall, you’ve done phenomenal work.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_105</Key>
    <Value>And what, pray tell, do we do about the legitimate horde of Scourge that I know for a fact is bearing down on Harmattan as we speak? We don’t even know where they’re going to attack us from!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>RunedImmaculate_SO_DEBATE_106</Key>
    <Value>They are no doubt taking refuge in the place you call &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Old Harmattan&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. The abandoned walled district to the North.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_RunedImmaculate_SO_DEBATE_106_a</Key>
    <Value>In Old Harmattan? Why there?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>RunedImmaculate_SO_DEBATE_108</Key>
    <Value>Simple. It’s the one place in this accursed plateau that no human is permitted to enter, for fear of disturbing the ghosts. It was the sensible place to hide.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>RunedImmaculate_SO_DEBATE_109</Key>
    <Value>These Scourge are likely led by disciples of the Butcher of Men, planning to attack the city. I will gladly gather my pack to fight them, if you will give me that chance. If they find a foothold here, it may greatly endanger this region’s future.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Victor_SO_DEBATE_110</Key>
    <Value>Wait, Headmaster! We cannot trust an Immaculate to fight its own kind, it will betray us for certain! Allow me to deploy my Golems! Allow me to show you what they are capable of!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Salaberry_SO_DEBATE_111</Key>
    <Value>No, Victor. I want to see if this Immaculate’s intentions are honest. I will allow him to fight these invading Scourge. Turnbull, send two people to oversee this battle, and report back to me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Turnbull_SO_DEBATE_112</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName], Desy, you know what to do. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Keep our friend safe out there&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_DEBATE_113</Key>
    <Value>Never thought I’d be fighting alongside an Immaculate...Against other Scourge. It’s a wild time to be alive.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>RunedImmaculate_SO_DEBATE_114</Key>
    <Value>There is &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;a small cave east of Old Harmattan that leads beneath it&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. That is the best angle of attack. Meet me through there, humans, as quickly as you can!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Turnbull_SO_DEBATE_115</Key>
    <Value>This may be a difficult battle, [PlayerName]...Here, take this with you, and prepare yourself as well as you can!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>artois_SO_PreBattle_01</Key>
    <Value>Gah...[PlayerName]? Oh thank Elatt it’s you. I thought I was done for!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_artois_SO_PreBattle_01_a</Key>
    <Value>Artois? What are you doing here? You’re injured!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>artois_SO_PreBattle_02</Key>
    <Value>Victor sent me to...Provide backup for your...Bah! I’ll be honest, the Wolfgang and I were ordered to plant some explosives during the fight and make sure that no Scourge made it out of Old Harmattan, pacified or not. And then...Gah...I’m such a damned fool...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>artois_SO_PreBattle_03</Key>
    <Value>The Immaculate that Turnbull Pacified...It tried to make the other ones stand down willingly. They refused and attacked us. Your Immaculate...I wouldn’t be here now if he hadn’t tried to protect me...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>artois_SO_PreBattle_04</Key>
    <Value>The hostile Immaculates locked a bunch of the gates in Old Harmattan, to try to split up and corner the pacified ones...Desy and the Wolfgang are still trapped in there with them...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_artois_SO_PreBattle_04_a</Key>
    <Value>Great, so they need someone to save them, don’t they?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>artois_SO_PreBattle_05</Key>
    <Value>Yeah...Yeah they do. If you can &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;open up the gates and help them kill whatever’s leading these Scourge&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, you might still be able to win this...Take the key, go...Go try to fix this...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_artois_SO_PreBattle_05_a</Key>
    <Value>You’re injured! What about you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>artois_SO_PreBattle_06</Key>
    <Value>Ach...I...I’ll...I don’t know. I drank my last potion after I pulled that damned Corrupted spine out of my gut. I think I’m still bleeding internally. I don’t know how long I have...But maybe it’s better this way. I don’t know if I deserve any other fate...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>artois_SO_PreBattle_07</Key>
    <Value>I should have seen the signs. But I just kept...Playing the hero in my head. Because if I wasn’t on the right side all along, then everything I’d done...I was afraid to face who I’d be if I was actually wrong. And now...I have to accept that I was.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_artois_SO_PreBattle_07_a</Key>
    <Value>Shut up and take one of my healing potions. You don’t deserve to die like this.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_artois_SO_PreBattle_07_b</Key>
    <Value>Shut up and take one one of my greater healing potions. You don’t deserve to die.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>artois_SO_PreBattle_08</Key>
    <Value>I...You’d...You’d actually help me? Even if I was actually willing to follow Victor’s orders to ruin everything? Why? By all accounts you have no reason to save me!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_artois_SO_PreBattle_08_a</Key>
    <Value>He’s a predator who was manipulating you. I blame him, not you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_artois_SO_PreBattle_08_b</Key>
    <Value>Even if I won’t forgive you, helping one another is the only way humanity survives.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>artois_SO_PreBattle_09</Key>
    <Value>I...You’re...You’re too kind, [PlayerName]. Thank you. If I survive... I won’t waste this second chance. If not...Tell Desy and your Immaculate that I’m sorry.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_artois_SO_PreBattle_09_a</Key>
    <Value>As soon as you’re able to move, get back to Harmattan, we’ll catch up later.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>artois_SO_PreBattle_10</Key>
    <Value>No...If I make it out of this alive...I’m not going back to Harmattan. I can’t go back after recognizing that Victor’s been using me all this time. Maybe I’ll...Go home to Berg, who knows. Anywhere’s better than here right now...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_artois_SO_PreBattle_08_c</Key>
    <Value>You know what, you’re right, I have no reason to help you. You’re on your own.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>artois_SO_PreBattle_11</Key>
    <Value>You’re...Cruel, [PlayerName]. But its no more than I deserve...Go on, people who actually deserve your help are waiting...I’ll...Try to manage on my own...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_artois_SO_PreBattle_07_c</Key>
    <Value>Shut your yap and get somewhere safe!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>artois_SO_PreBattle_12</Key>
    <Value>I’ll...try. If I don’t...Make it out of this...I’m sorry. Tell Desy and that...That Immaculate that I’m sorry.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_PreBattle_01</Key>
    <Value>Augh...Elatt dammit all, I didn’t want you to see me like this...That’s twice the damned Scourge have gotten the jump on me. My old crew would be ashamed. Has academic life made me soft?!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Desy_SO_PreBattle_01_a</Key>
    <Value>Desy! Are you alright?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_PreBattle_02</Key>
    <Value>No, I’m not alright! We’d hardly gotten the Golems and mercs into Old Harmattan before we got ambushed by the Scourge. If Henri hadn’t shoved me out of the way of that attack...I might not have made it this far. Artois is still trapped back there with them.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_PreBattle_03</Key>
    <Value>The hostile Immaculates have locked down a bunch of gates to try to corner our forces and split them up for easy killing. I barely managed to get out and lock this door behind me before the horde caught up with me!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Desy_SO_PreBattle_31_a</Key>
    <Value>Great. I have to try to save them all on my lonesome, then?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_PreBattle_04</Key>
    <Value>Y-yeah, I’ll be no help at this point. I don’t know what you can do to help, but at least try. The Golems are still up and fighting, I think you have a chance to turn this fight around. If you can &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;kill whatever is leading these Scourge&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, we might still eke out a win.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Desy_SO_PreBattle_04_a</Key>
    <Value>And what about you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_PreBattle_05</Key>
    <Value>Me? I’m going to drag myself somewhere safe and try not to die. I’ve got one potion in my bag, and I want to make sure it’s the only one I’ll need. I’ll see you back in Harmattan, if neither of us kicks the bucket in this mess.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Henry_SO_AfterBattle_01</Key>
    <Value>Phew...Well, what can I say, I think you might have just saved our lives. Dammit, I hate owin’ people. Especially people that I’m being paid to kidnap and hold for ransom!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Henry_SO_AfterBattle_01_a</Key>
    <Value>Uh...You’re welcome?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Henry_SO_AfterBattle_02</Key>
    <Value>Yeah yeah, I know. Here, a little thank you gift. Just keep your yap shut about this around Victor, alright? I’ve seen what happens if you get on his bad side and I never want to end up there.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Henry_SO_AfterBattle_03</Key>
    <Value>Maybe in a few years when that old feud blows over, you could come join us in the Wolfgang. You’ve certainly got the talent for it, [PlayerName]. In the meantime, try to stay out of trouble, alright? I’d rather avoid crossing blades with you as well.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Henry_SO_AfterBattle_04</Key>
    <Value>I can spare one of these weapons as a gift. Which one suits you better?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_REWARD_SO_AfterBattle_04_a</Key>
    <Value>I want the Tsar Bow.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_REWARD_SO_AfterBattle_04_b</Key>
    <Value>I want the Tsar Chakram.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_AfterBattle_01</Key>
    <Value>That was a much closer shave that I would have liked. I’m glad to see you weren’t on the wrong side all along, [PlayerName]! We may have taken some unfortunate losses, but at least the Scourge is beaten back once again!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Artois_SO_AfterBattle_01_a</Key>
    <Value>I hope you’re satisfied, Artois.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_AfterBattle_02</Key>
    <Value>I am. I know I’m in the right. I know that I’m a good person, serving a noble cause. And at the end of the day, this was a job well done.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Artois_SO_AfterBattle_01_b</Key>
    <Value>Fair enough. This isn’t optimal, but at least Harmattan is safe.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Artois_SO_AfterBattle_03</Key>
    <Value>Yes, Harmattan is safe. That’s all that matters. Hopefully someday you’ll open your eyes and see that Victor and I were right about this all along.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercenary_SO_AfterBattle_01</Key>
    <Value>Dammit...He’s gone. We were too late to save him. Well...At least he died a hero’s death. That’s some small comfort, at least.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Mercenary_SO_AfterBattle_01_a</Key>
    <Value>He was a mercenary, he knew the risks he was getting into.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Mercenary_SO_AfterBattle_01_b</Key>
    <Value>Whatever you say, mate.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercenary_SO_AfterBattle_02</Key>
    <Value>Well...The Scourge threat here has been eliminated. Mission complete, I guess. Well, guess we’ll be putting in more orders for the new Golems than we thought. We need all the firepower we can get right now.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>RunedImmaculate_SO_AfterBattle_01</Key>
    <Value>Thank you for coming to our aid, huma-...[PlayerName]. I knew it would be unlikely that I could convince disciples of the Butcher to stand aside and change, but I did not expect them to spring their trap so quickly and viciously.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>RunedImmaculate_SO_AfterBattle_02</Key>
    <Value>But those in my pack of Kin...They already feel the effects of Turnbull’s counter-spell, just by having stood by me and the runes I bear. For the first time since I awoke as Immaculate, I feel...Hopeful for the survival of our kind.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>RunedImmaculate_SO_AfterBattle_03</Key>
    <Value>You may not be a friend to me, [PlayerName], but I recognize your efforts and thank you deeply. Here, consider this a gift. From all those of my kind who will one day be free to choose what to do with their lives, free of their instinctual hate.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_RunedImmaculate_SO_AfterBattle_03_a</Key>
    <Value>What will you do now?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>RunedImmaculate_SO_AfterBattle_04</Key>
    <Value>I don’t know what I’ll do. I have many options I must consider...The runes I bear make of me an ambassador between humans and my Scouge Kin. Perhaps I should begin to consider how our species will live in Aurai with our newfound freedom.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_RunedImmaculate_SO_AfterBattle_03_b</Key>
    <Value>Well, I do consider you a friend, Immaculate. I hope we meet again.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>RunedImmaculate_SO_AfterBattle_05</Key>
    <Value>...Hah. Then I suppose we are friends, human.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>RunedImmaculate_SO_AfterBattle_06</Key>
    <Value>Take my gift and go forth as you have thus far, [PlayerName]. May our paths cross again in the future.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>RunedImmaculate_SO_AfterBattle_07</Key>
    <Value>Which of these treasures would bring you joy, then?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>LesserImmaculate_SO_AfterBattle_01</Key>
    <Value>...We could not save him. I am...So angry. He led us here with such promises of hope. And it was all for...Hmm...No, perhaps not for nothing.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>LesserImmaculate_SO_AfterBattle_02</Key>
    <Value>I feel different. The rage that has always filled my mind is...Quieter now. He was right. Just standing by him today, it was enough to change us as well. Then...Not everything is lost.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>LesserImmaculate_SO_AfterBattle_03</Key>
    <Value>Return to Turnbull, human. Tell him that this works. Tell him to free the rest of my kin. Because if this one died for nothing... I will come bring vengeance upon your kind, killing urge or not!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>LesserImmaculate_SO_AfterBattle_04</Key>
    <Value>You, however...You, I think, are not bad as far as humans go. There should be more like you, human.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_AfterBattle_01</Key>
    <Value>Phew. You showed up just in time, [PlayerName]. Those hostile Scourge were more powerful than anything I’ve faced so far. ...Well, except the Butcher. The Immaculates on our side even felt like they were unprepared for this level of ferocity.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_AfterBattle_02</Key>
    <Value>It’s a terrible shame he couldn’t live to see this victory. Even in his death, he proved that Scourgekind not only can be changed for the better, but that they deserve that chance as much as any human does. We’ve made history today, [PlayerName].</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_AfterBattle_03</Key>
    <Value>I’m glad our Immaculate friend survived this battle. I feel like his voice will be a great one in the years to come. We’ve made history today, [PlayerName].</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Desy_SO_AfterBattle_03_a</Key>
    <Value>That we have, Desy. I think we’ve earned a well deserved break, don’t you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_AfterBattle_04</Key>
    <Value>Absolutely. I’m not going outside the walls for a month unless I absolutely have to. This one battle was enough action for quite a while, thanks.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Desy_SO_AfterBattle_03_b</Key>
    <Value>Let’s hope this future we’ve created is a good one...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_AfterBattle_05</Key>
    <Value>Hey, no getting cold feet now! Not after this victory! If there’s any complications, we’ll cope with them as they come. We’re good at that!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Desy_SO_AfterBattle_03_c</Key>
    <Value>The taste of victory is sweet. Especially when shared with friends.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_AfterBattle_06</Key>
    <Value>Very true. And now we have a few more of those. If you’d have told me a year ago that I would feel this way about Immaculates, I’d have called you a liar. And yet, here we are.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Desy_SO_AfterBattle_07</Key>
    <Value>I’ll see you back home in Harmattan, my friend. Until our next mission together, fight safe, fight smart!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>HighClassInnNews_SO_Divided_01</Key>
    <Value>It’s such a shame that the Old Theater remains so inaccessible out there in the Antique Plateau. I hear that so many wonderful plays used to be held there back in the day. Not that the nobles cared, they thought it was the lowest form of art.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>HighClassInnNews_SO_Divided_02</Key>
    <Value>I wonder...If one tried to approach it from underground...Maybe you could get inside and see if any of Harmattan’s lost culture is still intact over there!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>LowClassInnNews_SO_Divided_01</Key>
    <Value>Some of my regulars haven’t shown up in a while...Then again, they were probably outlaws, so maybe that’s for the best.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>LowClassInnNews_SO_Divided_02</Key>
    <Value>One said she was trying to fill the boots of the old Fourwinds gang that used to run things in the east of ancient Harmattan. Talk about delusions of grandeur, huh?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Divided_01</Key>
    <Value>With the headmaster back I expected some peace and quiet! *sigh* Your Dean’s theory had better be correct!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercantile_SO_Divided_01</Key>
    <Value>Amba, my risk-taking friend! I will be watching this debate with VERY keen interest...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>HighClassInnNews_SO_Postgame_01</Key>
    <Value>I cannot believe this talk of pacifying the Scourge! No, peaceful or not, I will NEVER have Scourge stay at my inn! Not in a million years! My customers deserve peace and comfort and clean sheets!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>LowClassInnNews_SO_Postgame_01</Key>
    <Value>We live in wild times, my friend. And I’m not talking about just Harmattan either. Did you hear? The Queen of Levant has become a goddess! I feel like our world is wildly accelerating towards something, and I can’t help but be nervous.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GolemQuestStart_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>HARMATTAN! The punishment for your hubris is at hand! The Forge Master demands justice! Long have I languished in the chains Sorobor cast upon me, my sacrifices forgotten, their crimes unpunished! No more! </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GolemQuestStart_SO_Golem_02</Key>
    <Value>The wheels of my power are once more in motion! Your ancient factory is bent to my will! Surrender all who serve Sorobor Academy by the end of &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;60 days&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, or make your peace with the five winds!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GolemQuestStart_SO_Golem_03</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GolemQuestStart_SO_Golem_04</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GolemQuestStart_SO_Golem_05</Key>
    <Value>(There is a loud pop as the Golem’s Power Coil purposefully overloads, causing the Golem to collapse before your very eyes)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GolemQuestStart_SO_Golem_02_LongTimer</Key>
    <Value>The wheels of my power are once more in motion! Your ancient factory is bent to my will! Surrender all who serve Sorobor Academy by the end of &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;100 days&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, or make your peace with the five winds!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GolemQuestStart_SO_Golem_06</Key>
    <Value>(There’s a glowing &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rune&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; inside the Golem’s ribcage...You feel your skin vibrate as you touch the thing...It feels like &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;you’ve been attuned to something...Perhaps new doors will open for you&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, now.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GolemQuestStart_SO_Golem_07</Key>
    <Value>(There’s a series of labelled dials inside of the golem’s skull...The signal seems to have come from around the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ancient Bunker&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ruined Hippodrome&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, or the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ancient Turbine&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;...)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>LockedFactoryDoor_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>(&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Unknown Runes&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; line the doorframe...It would seem the door will not open for you right now...Perhaps &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;some event in the future will give you the means to open it&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;?)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>LockedTrain_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>(&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Unknown Runes&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; line the device...It doesn’t appear to respond to you right now...Perhaps &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;some event in the future will give you the means to use it&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;?)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>QuadKey_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>(There is an ornate key here. The engravings on the handle suggest &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;this is part of a set of 4&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, and the complex design and precious &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;gemstone&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; on the top suggests it was for something very important...You put it in a hidden pouch for safekeeping.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>RuneTrainConsole_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>Local Rune Train currently de-activated...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_RuneTrainConsole_SO_Golem_01_a</Key>
    <Value>(Flip the Switch to “on”)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>RuneTrainConsole_SO_Golem_02</Key>
    <Value>Re-activating Rune Rail enchantments...Success! &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Local Rune Train is now active&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>4-key device_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>The Asset has escaped containment. Quad-Key Lockdown Failsafe Mechanism has been activated. Beware of rogue Golems. Do NOT attempt to rescue anyone trapped inside.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>4-key device_SO_Golem_01-b</Key>
    <Value>The &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;4 Gemstone Keys&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; have been inserted into &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guardian-Class Golems&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, separate from the Asset’s control circuit. Keep all keys separate until control has been re-established...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>4-key device_SO_Golem_02</Key>
    <Value>(There are 4 slots for large and complex keys along the device...Each key is likely to be topped with a gemstone, judging by the look of this thing.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_4-key device_SO_Golem_02_a</Key>
    <Value>I think these 4 keys I have should work in this device...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_4-key device_SO_Golem_02_b</Key>
    <Value>Whatever this device is locking up seems quite important...I should find the keys.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>4-key device_SO_Golem_03</Key>
    <Value>(As the final key is inserted, the way forward opens ominously and the booming voice echoes through the halls, even louder than usual)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>4-key device_SO_Golem_04</Key>
    <Value>So...You’ve opened the path to reach me. I hope you’re pleased with yourself, trespasser. Your actions have allowed the Scourge to break into my own inner sanctum. They threaten the very safety of the city that you think you’re saving!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>4-key device_SO_Golem_05</Key>
    <Value>But it won’t matter. I will stop you, I will kill these Scourge, and I will have my vengeance. I can make as many Golems as I want now. Nothing that breathes will escape this place! What gives you the GALL to oppose my righteous fury?!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_4-key device_SO_Golem_05_a</Key>
    <Value>Someone’s got to try to protect the city from your vendetta!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>4-key device_SO_Golem_06</Key>
    <Value>Hah...Misguided fool. I am SAVING it. Saving it from those madmen who lead Sorobor!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_4-key device_SO_Golem_05_b</Key>
    <Value>Because I enjoy a challenge. Why do you think I adventure for a living?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>4-key device_SO_Golem_07</Key>
    <Value>Hah...Then you have a death wish. Continue to oppose me, and I will grant it for you!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_4-key device_SO_Golem_05_c</Key>
    <Value>Just for the inevitable reward. It’s nothing personal.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>4-key device_SO_Golem_08</Key>
    <Value>Greed remains a human value, I see. Well then...Once I’m done with you, I will bury what’s left of your corpse in gold!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>4-key device_SO_Golem_09</Key>
    <Value>Let this be your final warning, trespasser! I am the Forge Master, the Rust Lich! You stand no chance against my immortal power! Flee while I will still allow it!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>PowerConsole_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>Select Weapon Loadout for Titanic Guardian Mk-7...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_PowerConsole_SO_Golem_01_a</Key>
    <Value>Drilling Sword</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_PowerConsole_SO_Golem_01_b</Key>
    <Value>Serrated Halberd</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_PowerConsole_SO_Golem_01_c</Key>
    <Value>10 Ton Hammer</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ArmorConsole_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>Select Elemental Ward Matrix for Titanic Guardian Mk-7...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_ArmorConsole_SO_Golem_01_a</Key>
    <Value>Rusted Hive Impact Absorber</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_ArmorConsole_SO_Golem_01_b</Key>
    <Value>Ghostly Wendigo Armor Booster</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_ArmorConsole_SO_Golem_01_c</Key>
    <Value>Obsidian Scourge Repair Matrix</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>TrapConsole_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>Select Environmental Loadout for Titanic Guardian Mk-7...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_TrapConsole_SO_Golem_01_a</Key>
    <Value>Ice Vents</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_TrapConsole_SO_Golem_01_b</Key>
    <Value>Heat Vents</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_TrapConsole_SO_Golem_01_c</Key>
    <Value>Corruption Vents</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>BossUpdated_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>Titanic Guardian Mk-7 Golem settings updated, re-configuration complete...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>BossNoChange_SOGolem_01</Key>
    <Value>ERROR, Titanic Guardian currently deployed, modification no longer possible</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>AfterFirstBoss_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>(As the complex Golem fails and breaks down, various nearby machines shudder to a sudden and final stop...)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>AfterFirstBoss_SO_Golem_02</Key>
    <Value>No! Don’t...Bah! Very well. You’ve bought Sorobor a stay of execution. But this is merely a setback. I can start over using other sectors of the Factory to produce the means of my revenge.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_AfterFirstBoss_SO_Golem_02_a</Key>
    <Value>There’s no need for more violence! Let’s resolve this like reasonable adults!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>AfterFirstBoss_SO_Golem_03</Key>
    <Value>Have you ANY idea what you ask of me? If YOU had been turned into a monster, enslaved, and imprisoned for century...I doubt very much that mercy and forgiveness would be something you’d consider!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_AfterFirstBoss_SO_Golem_02_b</Key>
    <Value>Looks like my job isn’t done, then. I’m coming for you, whatever you are!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>AfterFirstBoss_SO_Golem_04</Key>
    <Value>Whatever I am?! I am Lord Duvernay, the glorious Forge Master! The last true high lord of Harmattan! You WILL respect me and the authority I wield!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>AfterFirstBoss_SO_Golem_05</Key>
    <Value>After all that has been done to me, there is no alternative. I WILL have my justice! I will see Sorobor Academy burned to the ground! I will restore the proper order of things!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>AfterANYBoss_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>My demands remain the same! Surrender all who serve Sorobor Academy by the end of &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;60 days&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, or reap the consequences!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>AfterSecondBoss_SO_Golem_00</Key>
    <Value>(As the Scourge Giant collapses, a bunch of the runic projections nearby flicker, vanish, then reappear. Various machines shudder to a stop...And never resume their work.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>AfterSecondBoss_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>Damn you! All my progress, lost! Although, I must also extend my gratitude...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>AfterSecondBoss_SO_Golem_02</Key>
    <Value>That beast entered this facility with the purpose of destroying it. It crawled though a crack and began to swing its weapons at anything that moved. I feared it would ruin all hope I had of getting justice...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>AfterSecondBoss_SO_Golem_03</Key>
    <Value>Then again, had this Scourge not tried to destroy this place, it would not have accidentally reactivated my connection to my Phylactery, and let me regain control. In a way, I owe this thing a great debt, even if it was accidental.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>AfterSecondBoss_SO_Golem_04</Key>
    <Value>So strange that the very monsters I was commanded to destroy have been the source of my freedom not once, but twice...Perhaps this is a sign...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_AfterSecondBoss_SO_Golem_04_a</Key>
    <Value>Your purpose was to fight the Scourge?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>AfterSecondBoss_SO_Golem_05</Key>
    <Value>Did you think that these Golems could wage war against the hordes of Scourge all by themselves? No. I controlled them. I am the one who saved Harmattan all those years ago...And what was my reward for my sacrifice? To be buried here, forgotten!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_AfterSecondBoss_SO_Golem_04_b</Key>
    <Value>You plan to ally with the Scourge, then?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>AfterSecondBoss_SO_Golem_06</Key>
    <Value>Hah, perhaps. Whatever lets me once more take my rightful place as a ruler of Harmattan and take my revenge. After all I sacrificed for the city...I deserve more than to be buried here and forgotten like this!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>AfterSecondBoss_SO_Golem_07</Key>
    <Value>And in my absence...The other great lords of Harmattan fled like cowards, died like cowards, and let that damnable Sorobor Academy create a city where our accomplishments and legacies were all but erased!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ScourgeGiantDoor_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>(Lethal levels of Corruption are coming from nearby vents... &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;You must eliminate the source if you want to proceed&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;!)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>SleepingGiant_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>(The Scourge Giant seems to still be breathing! But the skin has solidified to the point where further damage is impossible. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;The creature is still alive&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, in some form of deep hibernation...At least in this form, it’s no threat...)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>PreFinalFight_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>Not one step further, you vile, ignorant fool! In the name of the old lords, I, Lord Duvernay, command you to leave!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_PreFinalFight_SO_Golem_01_a</Key>
    <Value>You can’t order me around. I’m coming for you!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_PreFinalFight_SO_Golem_01_b</Key>
    <Value>Sounds like I’m getting near the source of the trouble. Time to end this!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_PreFinalFight_SO_Golem_01_c</Key>
    <Value>Please reconsider already! We don’t have to kill each other!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>PreFinalFight_SO_Golem_02</Key>
    <Value>You cannot understand my suffering, the injustice that I suffered! I was a noble, once. Of a powerful and storied house. Not once in the history of Harmattan did we lose our place on the ruling council. Even during the Scourge, I stayed to guide our people!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>PreFinalFight_SO_Golem_03</Key>
    <Value>And then those bastards from the Academy ripped my very heart from my chest, poured liquid metal in its place and chanted profane spells upon me! My soul was ripped from me and imprisoned in a device of gears and springs!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>PreFinalFight_SO_Golem_04</Key>
    <Value>They made me their prisoner, their slave! They turned me into this...This monstrous creature, a Lich, against my will! They used me, treated me like a tool, and saw to it that my entire legacy would be erased from history!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>PreFinalFight_SO_Golem_05</Key>
    <Value>But no more. No! More! I will send wave after wave of Golems to the city and bring Sorobor to its knees! And then I will take my rightful place as lord of the city, and as a hero who fought the Scourge!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>PreFinalFight_SO_Golem_06</Key>
    <Value>Turn back now, or die! I am an immortal Lich, far beyond anything a human is capable of! You stand no chance of victory! Flee if you value your fragile life!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_PreFinalFight_SO_Golem_06_a</Key>
    <Value>I’ve fought a Lich already. You don’t scare me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>PreFinalFight_SO_Golem_07</Key>
    <Value>Oh, have you? If you think you can crush me, I dare you to try! I’ve had nearly one hundred years to plan my vengeance, a small annoyance like you will be no trouble!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_PreFinalFight_SO_Golem_06_b</Key>
    <Value>Someone needs to put you in your place. I’m going to stop you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>PreFinalFight_SO_Golem_08</Key>
    <Value>Then YOUR place is a forgotten grave in this accursed maze of metal and smoke. Die and begone!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_PreFinalFight_SO_Golem_06_c</Key>
    <Value>Then there’s no point in talking anymore, is there?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>PreFinalFight_SO_Golem_09</Key>
    <Value>There never was, mortal. After all I’ve suffered, I cannot turn away from my path. Try to stop me, and you will face my judgment as well!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>AfterLichBoss_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>You...Have...Not...Won! ...&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;I will return. I am immortal&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. I am the Forge Master! The Rust Lich! All you do is delay the inevitable...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Phylactery_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>(There is a glowing Golem Gearbox here, vibrating with intense power...This must be the Rust Lich’s Phylactery. The legends say that &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;if a Phylactery is destroyed, the Lich it belongs to will become mortal again&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;...)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Phylactery_SO_Golem_01_a</Key>
    <Value>...Maybe I should leave it here...He doesn’t deserve to die.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Phylactery_SO_Golem_02</Key>
    <Value>(You leave the Phylactery be. You will likely need to keep coming back to stop the Lich from time to time, but he will live on. All you can do is hope that your act of mercy leaves an impression on him...)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Phylactery_SO_Golem_01_b</Key>
    <Value>This Lich needs to die. Let’s break this damn thing!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Phylactery_SO_Golem_03</Key>
    <Value>(You press the ominous red button labelled with a skull. An explosion rocks the container, sending gears and springs flying about inside. An agonized scream fills the room, echoing through your very blood...Then silence.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>DyingLich_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>You...You monster...My immortality...My life...You’ve ripped it from me...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>DyingLich_SO_Golem_02</Key>
    <Value>I did nothing wrong...Nothing you would not have done. Over a century of torment, enslavement, imprisonment...No one would have done any different.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_DyingLich_SO_Golem_02_a</Key>
    <Value>You chose this path, Lich. You have no right to complain about the consequences.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_DyingLich_SO_Golem_02_b</Key>
    <Value>Yes, I would have done different. Don’t pretend you know me, Lich.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_DyingLich_SO_Golem_02_c</Key>
    <Value>I’m sorry it came to this. But you gave me no other option. I had to protect Harmattan.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>DyingLich_SO_Golem_03</Key>
    <Value>Then end me already...Inflict your damnable false justice on me...I regret nothing...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_DyingLich_SO_Golem_03_a</Key>
    <Value>I’ll deal out justice myself!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>DyingLich_SO_Golem_04</Key>
    <Value>Then either kill me now, or walk away...I cling to life by a thread as it is.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_DyingLich_SO_Golem_03_b</Key>
    <Value>I’ll see you face justice for your crimes. I’m turning you over to the guards.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>TownGuardDungeon_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>Thanks for turning him in, [PlayerName]. Considering his condition... I don’t know how much time there will be for a trial, but...We’ll damn well try. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please go see the Headmaster of Sorbor Academy&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, he’ll want to speak with you about this!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Headmaster_SO_Golem_00_a</Key>
    <Value>I killed the Rust Lich that was threatening the city.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Headmaster_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>Yes, I’m aware. There was quite an impressive spike in local Mana when you destroyed his Phylactery. That must have been some fight he put up.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Headmaster_SO_Golem_02</Key>
    <Value>I wish it hadn’t come to his death. I don’t approve of what was done to him by our forefathers. It was a good idea, implemented wrongly...But I do understand why they did it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Headmaster_SO_Golem_02_a</Key>
    <Value>Why would the Soroboreans from a hundred years ago DO that to him?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Headmaster_SO_Golem_03</Key>
    <Value>The old elected nobles not only more or less rigged the elections to ensure power never truly slipped away from them, but Lord Duvernay was one of the worst. I suspect he didn’t care if people used as Golem commanders were actual volunteers or not.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Headmaster_SO_Golem_04</Key>
    <Value>From what I understand, he was the only noble who didn’t hide away in what is now Old Harmattan when the Scourge hit...But he thought that fact gave him the right to command everyone else, regardless of their consent, and regardless of the harm.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Headmaster_SO_Golem_05</Key>
    <Value>In the end...I suppose that makes his punishment fit his crimes.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Headmaster_SO_Golem_05_a</Key>
    <Value>Will you tell the citizens the truth about what happened?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Headmaster_SO_Golem_07</Key>
    <Value>I don’t see how we can, without causing serious and unnecessary harm to Sorobor’s reputation, or without seriously unbalancing our understanding of history. I’m afraid it’s for the best if the full truth remains buried, at least in the official sense.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Headmaster_SO_Golem_08</Key>
    <Value>You have earned a great reward for your deeds, [PlayerName]. Put it to good use. Thank you, for putting these ancient crimes to rest.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Headmaster_SO_Golem_09</Key>
    <Value>It’s only unfortunate that you weren’t able to stop this before he attacked the city. Thank you for putting these ancient crimes to rest.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>AcademyPlaza_SO_NPC_01</Key>
    <Value>You know, I wonder how they used to control the old Golems we used to fight the Scourge. I feel like a full-on war would require more precise control than the simple control methods we use these days.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>AcademyPlaza_SO_NPC_02</Key>
    <Value>Well, if there is any truth to that, it’s likely buried somewhere in all those ruins out there. I can only wait until someone uncovers it and lets me know.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>AcademyPlaza_SO_NPC_03</Key>
    <Value>That Golem...I can’t help but worry about what he said...Was that Golem alive? Was someone controlling it? ...And...What did Sorobor DO to anger it so?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>AcademyPlaza_SO_NPC_04</Key>
    <Value>Oof...We should not have disregarded that Golem’s weird ranting. About a dozen rogue Golems came bursting into the town from a hidden wall and laid into anyone near the Academy plaza!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>AcademyPlaza_SO_NPC_05</Key>
    <Value>One of those...Weird peaceful Immaculates that Turnbull was working on managed to fend them off. Saying thank you to a Scourge Beast was...Not something I thought I’d ever have to do!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>AcademyPlaza_SO_NPC_06</Key>
    <Value>If some of Victor Berthelot’s new, empowered Golems hadn’t been prowling the plaza...I shudder to think how many people would have been slaughtered.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>AcademyPlaza_SO_NPC_07</Key>
    <Value>They managed to kill a few unfortunate souls before the Engineering Dean shot them with some kind of lightning gun. He said it “de-charged” their power coils or something. I don’t care how he did it, I’m just glad to be alive!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>AcademyPlaza_SO_NPC_08</Key>
    <Value>I saw the execution of that Lich that threatened our town...Poor creature. I think it might have even been dead before the executioner did his work...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>AcademyPlaza_SO_NPC_09</Key>
    <Value>I hear some brave adventurer destroyed the Lich that threatened Harmattan! Whoever they were must have been quite skilled. A furious Lich is absolutely terrifying to behold!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Dungeon1Note_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>I have faith in the designs of the Golems. They can take a lot of punishment and really dish it out too. What give me pause is the control mechanism, sir.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Dungeon1Note_SO_Golem_02</Key>
    <Value>It jacks raw Mana intake directly into the puppeteer and keeps them comatose the entire time... This WILL kill anyone who controls the things for more than a few weeks, especially if they do not take frequent breaks.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Dungeon1Note_SO_Golem_03</Key>
    <Value>I understand that we need total control, and that the old command methods won't hold up. But we don't have enough people to keep throwing into that meat grinder. We can't keep grabbing people from the Lower Habitation district, it's not sustainable!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Dungeon1Note_SO_Golem_04</Key>
    <Value>Please, I beg of you.  Listen to Lord Duvernay’s idea about making someone who CAN handle the command mechanism long term...I know it seems like a long shot, but it's the best shot we have. I’ll even volunteer if I have to!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Dungeon5Note_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>It pains me to see my fancy designs put through such rapid, careless production. But at least I can be glad that, bastardized or not, my Golems are saving the region.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Dungeon5Note_SO_Golem_02</Key>
    <Value>We're just about tapped out of the local iron and palladium we need to keep up production, and with the rune train rails cut off as they are, we can no longer import what we need. If we don't break this siege soon, what's left of Harmattan is finished.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Dungeon5Note_SO_Golem_03</Key>
    <Value>I've heard rumors of some powerful being emerging from Monsoon, an actual god, they say. All I can do is hope that it's true and that they send us help. Because nothing short of divine intervention is going to break this stalemate at this point.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Dungeon7Note_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>I feel so much better using Troglodytes as live targets. The animals did nothing wrong, but Trogs? They're nasty mushroom monsters. Do they even count as living things? I consider them angry plants with teeny little brains, honestly.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Dungeon7Note_SO_Golem_02</Key>
    <Value>It also helps that they reproduce real quick. We have an endless stream of them coming out of that tunnel. Our downtime between testing phases is now effectively zero.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Dungeon7Note_SO_Golem_03</Key>
    <Value>It's also helpful that they're puny enough to pose no real threat to the lab. Seriously, even if they send a pack of Trog Knights at us, our Golems can make short work of them. If that's the strongest they can throw at us, we have nothing to worry about.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Dungeon8Note_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>I’ve managed to stabilize the Mana flow again. This is the maximum we can use to charge the Golems without risking the total collapse of the Ley Line...And yet, we still can't meet the demands of our Golem army. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Dungeon8Note_SO_Golem_02</Key>
    <Value>If only we were able to ask for help from the Electric Lab in the Abrassar Plains...We're going to have to send Golems out with less than maximum power, and hope that this is enough...And that extended maximum usage doesn't cause a leak.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ScourgeLab_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>Those tall Scourge creatures who wield weapons...The Corruption seems to have done more than just mutate them from some animal... They are intelligent, powerful, unyielding in the face of death.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ScourgeLab_SO_Golem_02</Key>
    <Value>They know no fear, and feel no pain. These monsters appear to almost be designed to be perfect killing machines.  They are, in a word, “Immaculate”.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ScourgeLab_SO_Golem_03</Key>
    <Value>I cannot avoid the conclusion that they must have once been human. Winds forgive us, and punish whomever did this to them, inflicting them upon us all. Nothing could have been worth this.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ScourgeLab_SO_Golem_04</Key>
    <Value>These “Sublime Shells” as we call them...They are far closer to the jungle apes that the “Shell Horror” species seem to be corrupted from... But even smarter. Some of them appear to even be capable of (extremely) limited speech...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ScourgeLab_SO_Golem_05</Key>
    <Value>“Illuminators”...They puzzle us all. They appear to be like mobile plants, with no head or mouth to speak of...But their feet...They’re shaped like human hands... Even the “Pure Illuminators” follow no sensible biology and appear to be strange amalgams...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ScourgeLab_SO_Golem_06</Key>
    <Value>These “Grotesques”...They are similar to Immaculates. But they lack intelligence of any kind, and hew closer to the plantlike Illuminators...Are they failed Immaculates? Or are Immaculates a superior version of the Grotesque?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ContainmentLab_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>Whoever was inspecting the Asset’s containment chamber before me was not performing the full checklist. I found at least 6 potential safety violations that could lead to a breach. Half the bolts on the Mana intake pipe are rusted!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ContainmentLab_SO_Golem_02</Key>
    <Value>I strongly urge you to sign off on immediate quarantine of the area until these issues are patched up and the Asset is moved to a containment chamber with ZERO metal! Make the pipes out of glass if you have to!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ContainmentLab_SO_Golem_03</Key>
    <Value>The Asset’s entire domain of power is over metal and machines! I understand that he is our only hope of fending off the Scourge, but if we do not take action immediately, we risk this immortal superhuman breaking free and slaughtering us all!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ContainmentLab_SO_Golem_04</Key>
    <Value>(The head supervisor’s signature is only half-completed. Something must have interrupted him...)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>LibraryCorpse_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>I’m trapped in here. That bastard let the Scourge tunnel into the place and catch us off guard. We didn’t realize our Golems had turned on us until it was too late. It’s only a matter of which kills me first, the Golems, or the Scourge.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>LibraryCorpse_SO_Golem_02</Key>
    <Value>I can still hear them fighting each other in here...Even with the factory shut down, the Golems continue to follow their last orders...And with all the exits sealed, there’s no way out for me...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>LibraryCorpse_SO_Golem_03</Key>
    <Value>All I can can do is catalogue the extensive list of horrible decisions that lead to this mess, so we won’t make the same mistakes agai-...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>MorgueLog_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>Report: Every dissection of expired Golem Puppeteers is the same. The process of controlling the Golems inevitably leads to such Mana overdose that it causes complete organ failure.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>MorgueLog_SO_Golem_02</Key>
    <Value>Please inform the commander to stop asking me to perform these dissections. It is a waste of time. We will gain no new information.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>SecretChamber_SO_Golem_01</Key>
    <Value>Attempt 1: Focal point – Mana Stone, Failure. The attempt to create a “Mana Lich” was a complete botch. Their organs completely burned to a crisp. I am unsure if it was a failure of the ritual, or if Mana is too general a focal point to create a Lich.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>SecretChamber_SO_Golem_02</Key>
    <Value>Attempt 5: Focal Point – Golem Gearbox, Failure. Even with the alterations to the ritual, the volunteer did not become a Lich. I think it was a failure of the subject, not the ritual, nor the focal point. The subject needs to be of stronger will...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>SecretChamber_SO_Golem_03</Key>
    <Value>Lord Duvernay flew into a rage at our failures, threatening to use US in the next ritual if we don’t turn out results. Winds-damned idiot. I don’t care if he’s the only noble who didn’t abandon the city, Harmattan would be better off without that fool.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>SecretChamber_SO_Golem_04</Key>
    <Value>In fact, if he’s so insistent on turning someone into a Lich, he should be the next “volunteer”!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>SecretChamber_SO_Golem_05</Key>
    <Value>Attempt 6: Focal Point – Golem Gearbox, Success! Who knew that Lord Duvernay had it in him! Then again, the self-righteous bastard is now an immortal, magically imbued creature with full control over our Golem army. This may not be an improvement.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>SecretChamber_SO_Golem_06</Key>
    <Value>For now, his sense of duty to protect Harmattan keeps him in line, but I have no doubt that the moment he sees his chance, he will slaughter us all for what we did to him against his will. We need failsafes. Lots of ‘em.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>SecretChamber_SO_Golem_07</Key>
    <Value>Success! The Lich can control the Golems just by keeping his Phylactery inside a control unit. At the suggestion of an aide, we’ve agreed to keep the Lich in an isolated containment unit, far away from his Phylactery.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>SecretChamber_SO_Golem_08</Key>
    <Value>He makes an awful racket in there, but so long as we keep it properly maintained and the Mana flow to the internal barrier spell steady, we should be able to keep him in check.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>SecretChamber_SO_Golem_09</Key>
    <Value>Finally, if the worst should happen, our failsafe will shut down the entire factory, and disrupt the connection between him and his Phylactery. Theoretically, this should prevent him from controlling the Golems or even moving his own body until we regain control...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>SecretChamber_SO_Golem_10</Key>
    <Value>“Theoretically” isn’t enough for me, but it’s all we have. All we can do now it hope we never have to flip that switch...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>MarketFood_SO_Sorobor_01</Key>
    <Value>The best food in Aurai, right here! From the Chersonese coast, to the Impasse mountains!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Task_SO_Sorobor_01_a</Key>
    <Value>Need help with anything?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>MarketFood_SO_Sorobor_02</Key>
    <Value>I’m running a little low on Manaheart Bass...Be a dear and bring me 2 of them, would you, please?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>MarketGeneral_SO_Sorobor_01</Key>
    <Value>Tools and gear, fit for hunting beast or Scourge! If it’s good enough for the warriors at the Gates of Catharsis, it’s good enough for you!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>MarketGeneral_SO_Sorobor_02_Task</Key>
    <Value>My Daughter’s been asking me for a Tourmaline for a while. If you came across some, I’d be most grateful!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>MarketCamping_SO_Sorobor_01</Key>
    <Value>It’s a harsh world out there! Be prepared for anything, with our excellent selection of camping equipment!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>MarketCamping_SO_Sorobor_02_Task</Key>
    <Value>I’ve heard tell of a delicious desert called Angel Food Cake! I’d love to try it, but I haven’t found anyone willing to share!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>MarketAlchemy_SO_Sorobor_01</Key>
    <Value>Whatever ails you, I can cure it. Whatever you’re fighting, I can tell you how to poison it. Either way, you’re in good hands with me!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>MarketWeapons_SO_Sorobor_01</Key>
    <Value>Weapons, made for the most serious of adventurers! Buy one, it’s dangerous to travel alone!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>MarketWeapons_SO_Sorobor_02_Task</Key>
    <Value>I was asked to make a weapon out of a Shield Golem Scrap for someone, but it’s so hard to source... If you happen across some, I’d reward you well for it!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>MarketArmor_SO_Sorobor_01</Key>
    <Value>The best defense is a good defense! What good’s a sword if you can’t live long enough to swing it?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>MarketArmor_SO_Sorobor_02_Task</Key>
    <Value>I’m trying to add some enchantments to something special I’m working on. If you happen across any Fire Elemental Particles out there, I’d trade for them!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>RansomBan_SO_Sorobor_01</Key>
    <Value>Ah, wait...I’m afraid I can’t serve you. Your name’s on my list of blacklisted customers. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Mercantile Provost, Sekiguchi Meiko&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, has a note here saying that until &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;you work something out with her, you can’t shop here&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Sorry!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>PrismaticTrainer_SO_Sorobor_01</Key>
    <Value>Train you, huh? Do you really think you have what it takes to learn the Prismatic Flurry? It asks you to bend magical boons with your fists, truly a merging of the physical and the spiritual. Only a few people are capable of it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>PrismaticTrainer_SO_Sorobor_02</Key>
    <Value>If you want me to teach you, prove to me your body can handle it. Return and show me a piece of Pure Chitin from an enhanced Scourge Beast, and I will believe you are capable!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>PrismaticTrainer_SO_Sorobor_03</Key>
    <Value>Elatt’s breath, you actually did it. Alright. Let’s begin...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>PrismaticTrainer_SO_Sorobor_04</Key>
    <Value>Hah! You’ve got it! It’s been ages since I’ve seen someone else use that technique without collapsing from the strain! You have no idea how happy you’ve made me today, [PlayerName]!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercantile_SO_Ransom_01</Key>
    <Value>By the way...You and I have something to discuss. You are aware I paid your ransom, securing your release from the Wolfgang, yes?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercantile_SO_Ransom_02</Key>
    <Value>I want to be repaid. Not in money. I want something more valuable than mere silver. Tell me, [PlayerName], have you ever hunted a &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Boozu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; before? Those &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;large hulking mammals&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; on the Plateau?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercantile_SO_Ransom_03</Key>
    <Value>They are considered a sort of “protected species”, due to how their bodies break down natural Corruption. Kill one and &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;bring me at least one piece of Boozu’s Hide&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Only then will I allow you to visit the marketplace again.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercantile_SO_Ransom_04</Key>
    <Value>Ah. Excellent. Consider your debt to me repaid. I will have your name removed from the market’s blacklist, effective immediately.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercantile_SO_Ransom_05</Key>
    <Value>Don’t let this happen again. If you do, however...We’ll find a similar arrangement. You will need to earn your right to the market again. Understand?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_SO_Purifier_01</Key>
    <Value>I found evidence that someone from Sorobor was involving in kidnapping and murder.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercantile_SO_Purifier_01</Key>
    <Value>Let me see that...Oho! VERY interesting. Yes, this will be quite profitable. Hand the evidence over to me, and I’ll see to it that everyone in the central market gives you a discount. Permanently.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_SO_Purifier_01_a</Key>
    <Value>And what about the culprit?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercantile_SO_Purifier_02</Key>
    <Value>I’m going to work that Nanzome, that Black-Heart, to the bone for the rest of his life. He knows that if the headmaster ever found out, he would likely “disappear”. It wouldn’t be the first time that happened to a traitor to the ideals of the Academy.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_SO_Purifier_02</Key>
    <Value>Deal, here’s the evidence!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_SO_Purifier_03</Key>
    <Value>...I think someone else might give me a better deal. I’ll think about it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercantile_SO_Purifier_03</Key>
    <Value>VERY good business, [PlayerName]. Now, if you’ll excuse me, I have a kidnapper to extort.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mercantile_SO_Purifier_04</Key>
    <Value>Oh, and that ransom repayment I have you working on? You’re off the hook this time.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Purifier_01</Key>
    <Value>What?! If this proof checks out, this is a huge deal. Sorobor’s reputation would take a considerable blow from this scandal... Hand the evidence over to me and I’ll open up my private shop of discount potions to you in exchange.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Purifier_02</Key>
    <Value>If he wants to play with Immaculates so badly, there are some very dangerous jobs we need done around the Gates of Catharsis. He can choose between doing those, or having his crimes made public and finding himself dangling from a scaffold.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Purifier_03</Key>
    <Value>A wise decision. I will see to it that he either redeems himself the long and difficult way, or dies in the process. Either one suits my mood. I’ll remember this, [PlayerName], don’t you worry.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Shop_01</Key>
    <Value>So, what kind of potions would you like? They’re 40 Silver per set.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Shop_01_Player_a</Key>
    <Value>Defensive Set</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Shop_01_Player_b</Key>
    <Value>Aggressive Set</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Academic_SO_Shop_01_Player_c</Key>
    <Value>Mage Set</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Headmaster_SO_Purifier_01</Key>
    <Value>What? Let me see...Ah, Jager. What have you done? Give me this proof, and I will see justice done. All of Sorobor Academy will owe you a great debt for your actions.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Headmaster_SO_Purifier_02</Key>
    <Value>A bounty will be put on his head for these murders. Whether he is slain in the field like a common bandit, or dragged back here in chains to face justice properly, I care not. There will be no blood price, only his death, for such unethical behaviour.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Headmaster_SO_Purifier_03</Key>
    <Value>The rest of the world must know that Sorobor Academy will not tolerate the use of mass kidnapping and murder as a tool of research. I will not have such a black mark on our reputation, after we have done so much to secure our prominence.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Headmaster_SO_Purifier_04</Key>
    <Value>Sorobor is in your debt, [PlayerName]. I will not forget it. I will be sure to repay the favor, if someday you are ever in great need.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>HexTrainer_SO_Purifier_01</Key>
    <Value>I do not regret giving up decades of mortal vitality to the Ley Line. After all, there is plenty of life to take from my foes. Sit down, and I’ll teach you to tap into the negatives of magic, the art of Hexes!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>SpeedTrainer_SO_Purifier_01</Key>
    <Value>You scoff at my appearance, but one training session with me could change your life! I’ll teach you to strike like lightning, and evade with the grace of a butterfly! Now put ‘em up!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>TownGuard_SO_Harmattan_01</Key>
    <Value>Welcome to Harmattan, home of Sorobor Academy! Behave yourself, we will tolerate no violent crime here! We didn’t survive the worst of the Scourge just to let troublemakers do as they please!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>TownGuard_SO_Harmattan_02</Key>
    <Value>North of town, you’ll find Golem Lake and Old Harmattan. Don’t try to get in there, we’ve sealed it off to keep the ghosts trapped inside. If they got out, they could seriously endanger the region!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>TownGuard_SO_Harmattan_03</Key>
    <Value>To the East, there’s the ruined cultural district, and just north of that is what was once known as the Fourwinds District, where that old gang once held power. It’s mostly wild animals and Golems around there nowadays.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>TownGuard_SO_Harmattan_04</Key>
    <Value>To the South, there’s the Vigil crystal in the old merchant’s district. And to the East of that you’ve got the old Cabal of Winds temple and the Mana Lake.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>TownGuard_SO_Harmattan_05</Key>
    <Value>To the West, there’s a few outlaw gangs trying to displace the Wolfgang Mercenaries. Be careful wandering into any of the ruined districts over there. You may find friends, or you may find a great deal of foes. Check, before you attack!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_TownGuard_SO_Harmattan_01_b</Key>
    <Value>Anything I should be careful about out there?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>TownGuard_SO_Harmattan_06</Key>
    <Value>Be wary of clouds of Corruption out there! The damage left by the Scourge was bad enough that even a century later, much of it has yet to fade. Exposure to too much malignant Corruption will leave you terribly ill.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>TownGuard_SO_Harmattan_07</Key>
    <Value>Keep your eyes peeled for large Scourge Beasts and malfunctioning Golems. We’ve heard reports of a Wendigo prowling about the South as well. Steer clear of them all unless you’re very well prepared.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>TownGuard_SO_Harmattan_08</Key>
    <Value>There are far too many to name, I’m afraid. You’ll find most of the important people either up in Sorobor Academy, around the central marketplace, or in the Military District on the east side.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>TownGuard_SO_Harmattan_09</Key>
    <Value>There are two inns in town that are good places to pick up recent gossip. One’s up on the West side of town, the other’s lower on the east side, near Justice Plaza. As for water, there’s a drinking basin by the Marketplace.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>TownGuard_SO_LowInnBlocker_01</Key>
    <Value>I’m sorry, this area is closed...Some Scourge erupted from a crack in a nearby alley, and rampaged through the city...The interior of this building is completely trashed. No one managed to get out in time, either... Poor souls...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>BloodMage_SO_SideQuest_01</Key>
    <Value>Free...Me...!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_BloodMage_SO_SideQuest_01_a</Key>
    <Value>What the...Voices in my head!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>BloodMage_SO_SideQuest_02</Key>
    <Value>Minions...They gather blood...Keep me immortal...&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Kill them&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;...Kill...Them...! Reward...You...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>BloodMage_SO_SideQuest_03</Key>
    <Value>(The image of a &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;stone gazeebo&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; floats into your mind...)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>BloodMage_SO_SideQuest_04</Key>
    <Value>(You see a flash of a &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;windmill up on a cliff&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;...)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>BloodMage_SO_SideQuest_05</Key>
    <Value>(A &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;crumbling temple&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; appears in your mind’s eye...)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>BloodMage_SO_SideQuest_06</Key>
    <Value>(You are gripped by the thought of a &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;fortress barracks&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;...)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>BloodMage_SO_SideQuest_07</Key>
    <Value>(The shriveled, twisted corpse of this old blood mage has a look of relief etched onto their face...)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>BloodMage_SO_SideQuest_08</Key>
    <Value>(A sudden shudder fills you, as forbidden knowledge leaks into your brain...)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>BloodMage_BOOK_SO_SideQuest_01</Key>
    <Value>Success! I have discovered the secret to immortality via blood magic. At last, a way to stay alive, without forsaking my humanity! I will share this gift with my apprentices, it should ensure they remain unquestioningly loyal to me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>BloodMage_BOOK_SO_SideQuest_02</Key>
    <Value>There is a problem...The longer I live...The more Corruption grows within me. Fortunately, my minions bring me the blood that I need to keep it at bay...But I was wrong about their loyalty...This requires more...Direct control...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>BloodMage_BOOK_SO_SideQuest_03</Key>
    <Value>I was a fool. Yes, I am immortal so long as I perform the ritual when needed, but every time that I do, the Corruption spreads in me faster and faster. My human body is dying faster than I can give it new life...My minions can barely keep up anymore...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>HouseSeller_SO_Harmattan_01</Key>
    <Value>Hey there! The owner of this house just moved to Monsoon, and has put the place up for sale! It’s yours if you want it, friend!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Travel_SO_Harmattan_01</Key>
    <Value>Ah, glorious Harmattan! It’s good to be home again!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Travel_SO_Random_01_Player</Key>
    <Value>Take me to {1} – {2} – {3} </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Travel_SO_CoopWarning_01</Key>
    <Value>You should tell your travelling companion to get closer. I can’t give you a lift if you’re not all here!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Travel_SO_NoTravel_01</Key>
    <Value>I’m afraid I’m not travelling anywhere at the moment.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Travel_SO_Cancel_01</Key>
    <Value>Very well. I’ll be here if you need me!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Travel_SO_OpenMenu_01_Player</Key>
    <Value>I want to travel with you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Travel_SO_MissingCost_01</Key>
    <Value>*tsk* I’m afraid you don’t have the money or rations. I’m sorry, friend, but I can’t do this for free.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Travel_SO_WhereTo_01</Key>
    <Value>Sure, I can give you a lift, for a small fee. And you’ll need to handle your own rations.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>WanderingImmaculate_SO_Antique_01</Key>
    <Value>I hate this accursed region...It is so full of blood and pain...But it bears so much significance to both our species...And so, I visit from time to time, so I never forget.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>WanderingImmaculate_SO_Antique_02</Key>
    <Value>I have no special gifts for you, friend. But...Allow me to freely share some knowledge with you instead.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
</ArrayOfDialogue>