<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ArrayOfDialogue xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_01</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName], there you are. The Chamberlords are gathering as we speak. I need you to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;make your way to the Blue Chamber itself&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. It’s the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;largest building in Berg, up near the fountain&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_a_01</Key>
    <Value>I'm on my way. What should I look out for while I'm there?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_02</Key>
    <Value>Anything suspicious, anyone acting out of place, especially anyone who has important business being discussed today.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_a_02</Key>
    <Value>What exactly are the Chamberlords meeting about? It'll help give me an idea of who to keep tabs on.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_03</Key>
    <Value>There are two main issues being debated at this Council Meeting. Old Levant's claims to the Abrassar region, and Sirroco's land negotiations with the Hallowed Marsh Region.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_04</Key>
    <Value>Old Levant are the remnants of the tribes that used to live in Abrassar before the Scourge. They wish to reclaim their land and to be considered the legitimate rulers of the region.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_05</Key>
    <Value>They are contending with the current "Heroic Kingdom" of Levant, who were granted the region by Elatt's decree as reward for purging the region of the Scourge. Particularly, one immense and vicious beast we called the Devourer.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_06</Key>
    <Value>King Simeon and Queen Calixa are both beloved, not just in Abrassar, but also across the entirety of Aurai. If Old Levant's claims are recognized, their dethroning could lead to war.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_a_06</Key>
    <Value>And what's the problem between Sirroco and the Hallowed Marsh?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_07</Key>
    <Value>The Sirroco region lies in the shadow of a volcano. As such, the land is wracked by earthquakes and unpredictable land shifts. I hear their primary settlement is at risk of tumbling into a fault line or somesuch.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_08</Key>
    <Value>The nearest habitable region is the Hallowed Marsh. However, given the hostility of the region and the fact that it is home to the Holy Mission of Elatt... Well, negotiations will be very delicate.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_09</Key>
    <Value>This is without mentioning that the Chamberlord of Monsoon is not affiliated with the Holy Mission that lives within his city, and he’s said not to hold any real power.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_10</Key>
    <Value>Sirroco must not be left to fend for itself, but the independence and sanctity of the city of Monsoon must be respected... It will be very difficult to reach an agreement that both will find acceptable.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_b_02</Key>
    <Value>Got it, I'll pay attention to the guests. Will I see you there?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_11</Key>
    <Value>Yes, I'll be there shortly. I have some important personal business to discuss with Julius first. Once I'm done I'll meet you at the Blue Chamber.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_b_01</Key>
    <Value>I still have things I need to do first.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_12</Key>
    <Value>We still have time, but please don't dally for too long. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_13</Key>
    <Value>Why are you still here? I need you to keep tabs on the other Chamberlords at the Blue Chamber!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_14</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_15</Key>
    <Value>Have you picked up on any relevant gossip, [PlayerName]?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_a_15</Key>
    <Value>Not yet, I'm going mingle a bit more.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_16</Key>
    <Value>Very well, come back once you have something.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_b_15</Key>
    <Value>Yes. There's a lot of unhappy people here who might spark a firestorm.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_17</Key>
    <Value>I agree. There is enough frustration in this room that I can’t tell where trouble might come from. And the delegation from Sirocco should be here by now. I’m concerned... Could you &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;check the Inn&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; to see if they’ve arrived in Berg, yet?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_18</Key>
    <Value>(The sound of an explosion rocks the air and makes the ground tremble beneath your feet. It came from the Blue Chamber! &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rissa might be in grave danger&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;!)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_19</Key>
    <Value>Thank you, [PlayerName]. Where is Gabriella?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_a_19</Key>
    <Value>She’s in Berg, trying to figure out who ordered the attack.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_20</Key>
    <Value>Good. It appears that she too has much faith in you. I’m certain these kidnappers took Balthazar too. Have you found him yet?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_a_20</Key>
    <Value>No, not yet.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_21</Key>
    <Value>Please find him, [PlayerName]. He is incredibly valuable to the Collective, and his health is not what it used to be.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_b_20</Key>
    <Value>I found his body. The kidnappers shot him and left him for the animals.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_22</Key>
    <Value>Ancestors take him. This is dreadful news! That man was more valuable to us than you know.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_a_22</Key>
    <Value>I’m still looking for whoever led the attack.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_23</Key>
    <Value>Make haste, then. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;I doubt they will be hiding here in Enmerkar for much longer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_b_22</Key>
    <Value>I found the one leading the attack. I’m certain he was a general in Levant’s army.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_24</Key>
    <Value>Then our worst fears are realized. Open war with them is unavoidable. We will need all the allies we can muster in the coming months.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_c_22</Key>
    <Value>I’m sure the one who led the attack is long gone…</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_25</Key>
    <Value>I don’t doubt that. Whoever organized this was a professional. They wouldn’t stay longer than they needed to. It’s a pity, but we’ll have to let that lead go.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_37</Key>
    <Value>I will make my way &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;back to Berg&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. We have much to prepare for the coming conflict.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_a_37</Key>
    <Value>May Elatt watch your back.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_38</Key>
    <Value>And yours, [PlayerName].</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_b_37</Key>
    <Value>Are you sure you can get back on your own?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_39</Key>
    <Value>I’m not a fragile flower, you know. I can make it back if I keep my wits about me and avoid getting into trouble.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_42</Key>
    <Value>I’m glad you made it back, [PlayerName]. You did fantastic work, bringing down the attackers’ leader and tracking down the hostages they took.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_26</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName], how goes the search for the leader of those thugs?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_a_26</Key>
    <Value>I'm still looking.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_27</Key>
    <Value>I wish you haste and luck. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;I doubt they will be hiding here in Enmerkar for much longer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_b_26</Key>
    <Value>I think we should give up on finding him. I've got no good leads. We should focus on more important things.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_28</Key>
    <Value>If you're certain, then I suppose we will have to let him go. We have much to do as it stands.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_c_26</Key>
    <Value>I’m sure the one who led the attack is long gone…</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_29</Key>
    <Value>I don’t doubt that. Whoever organized this was a professional. They wouldn’t stay longer than they needed to. It’s a pity, but we’ll have to let that lead go.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_30</Key>
    <Value>In any case, Gabriella pressed her informants. It looks like Levant, or at least a faction within Levant, is responsible for this attack.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_31</Key>
    <Value>Their primary objective appears to have been to render Old Levant's claims to the region null and void by any means possible.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_a_31</Key>
    <Value>Have they claimed responsibility? Or made some defense?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_32</Key>
    <Value>They claim innocence, but the evidence leads straight to them. They can’t point out any faction or group within them that would benefit from this either.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_33</Key>
    <Value>While the possibility that Levant's leadership didn’t order the attack is something I am willing to consider, the other Chamberlords disagree.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_34</Key>
    <Value>War is upon us. We must prepare as best we can. Give me a few days to plan our next move. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_35</Key>
    <Value>Here, you've earned this.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_40</Key>
    <Value>Don’t forget, Cierzo is still your home. You should &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;visit it from time to time&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, to see if there’s any help they might need.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Mix_Legacy_41</Key>
    <Value>We’re still waiting on the other Chamberlords to arrive so we can begin the council meeting. Until then, you’re free to do as you please. Take the time to get used to the Enmerkar region and buy the equipment you need here in Berg.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Mix_Legacy_01</Key>
    <Value>Keep your eyes peeled, [PlayerName]. If Rissa expects trouble, trouble will come! We just don’t know what form it will take yet.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Mix_Legacy_02</Key>
    <Value>I guess you weren’t as much of an asset as we hoped, [PlayerName]. Well, it can't be helped. Whoever planned this attack was a professional.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Gabriella_BC_Mix_Legacy_a_02</Key>
    <Value>You fought some of these thugs too?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Mix_Legacy_03</Key>
    <Value>Naturally. And I injured at least three and made them retreat. So what? I can defend myself, that’s all. We have bigger fish to fry right now.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Gabriella_BC_Mix_Legacy_b_02</Key>
    <Value>So, what now? Someone attacked the Blue Chamber itself, mid-session! We can’t let this go quietly!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Mix_Legacy_04</Key>
    <Value>No nonsense, good. I like you already.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Mix_Legacy_05</Key>
    <Value>This was planned by an expert. On top of any damage their explosives might have done, they've taken prisoners. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;I saw them kidnap Rissa and Balthazar and take them below the chamber&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; while I was dealing with these thugs.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Gabriella_BC_Mix_Legacy_a_05</Key>
    <Value>What do we do now?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Mix_Legacy_06</Key>
    <Value>We need to investigate. Get down to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;the archives room below the Blue Chamber and follow the attackers&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. I'm going to stay here in case they come back to take more hostages.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Mix_Legacy_07</Key>
    <Value>I've got the rest of the Chamberlords covered. You go take care of the Archives. Sagard and I will make sure any new attackers don't get farther than the door.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Mix_Legacy_08</Key>
    <Value>What's the situation down there, [PlayerName]?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Gabriella_BC_Mix_Legacy_a_08</Key>
    <Value>The corridor leading to the Necropolis has been blown to pieces. They blasted a tunnel under Berg to get in.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Mix_Legacy_09</Key>
    <Value>Dammit. Like I expected. Professionals. The evidence points to Levant right now. The attack damaged our historical archives and killed the ambassador from Old Levant, on top of taking hostages. Levant benefits most from all this...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Mix_Legacy_10</Key>
    <Value>Alright, [PlayerName], we’ve got work to do. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Follow them through the tunnel&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, and turn Enmerkar upside down until you bring &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rissa home safely&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. And if you can track down whoever led this attack, make them pay.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Gabriella_BC_Mix_Legacy_a_10</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Mix_Legacy_11</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Gabriella_BC_Mix_Legacy_b_10</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Mix_Legacy_12</Key>
    <Value>I need to follow some leads of my own before the tracks go cold. If, like I suspect, Levant is behind this... an attack like this will ignite a full blown war. I want to be certain before hostilities start and my information network is shut off from me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Mix_Legacy_13</Key>
    <Value>Rissa told me you can handle yourself in the wild. I feel comfortable enough leaving her safety in your hands while I work on finding out who ordered this attack. I wish you luck, [PlayerName] and I hope you don’t need it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Mix_Legacy_14</Key>
    <Value>Oh, by Elatt's name... Sagard is already rallying the other Chamberlords to launch a full-scale counter-offensive against Levant before all the proof is even accounted for. Typical. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Mix_Legacy_15</Key>
    <Value>What are you doing? Defend yourself!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Mix_Legacy_16</Key>
    <Value>Consider me impressed, [PlayerName]. Well done on bringing Rissa back.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Mix_Legacy_17</Key>
    <Value>My contact near the Abrassar border said he saw suspicious folk moving about. I’d wager that was our culprits, making their escape. It’s a pity we couldn’t find them in time.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>AttackerNote_BC_Mix_Legacy_01</Key>
    <Value>Be warned, Gabriella Sullivan is a suspected member of the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Krypteia&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. She will likely be forewarned by the Ancestral Memories that an attack is coming. The Krypteia has opposed the Lich of the Red Moon herself, so extreme caution is advised.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>AttackerNote_BC_Mix_Legacy_02</Key>
    <Value>Gabriella will likely have powerful magic, and her control over the Ancestral Memories will give her a great edge. Avoid her if possible and focus on the objective. If confrontation is unavoidable, use overwhelming force.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>NecroNote_BC_Mix_Legacy_00</Key>
    <Value>(This fallen note seems to contain orders for the attack on Berg. Perhaps it holds a clue for what they did with the hostages.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>NecroNote_BC_Mix_Legacy_01</Key>
    <Value>“Your first priority is the destruction of the archives room under the Blue Chamber. If you cannot ensure complete destruction of the room, at least ensure that it will be inaccessible for as much time as possible.”</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>NecroNote_BC_Mix_Legacy_02</Key>
    <Value>“Likewise, Alda, the ambassador representing Old Levant, is to be killed on sight. Use as much ammunition as you need to. She must not survive this meeting.”</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>NecroNote_BC_Mix_Legacy_03</Key>
    <Value>“If possible, capture and question the Blue Chamber historian, Balthazar Berthelot. If he shows any sign of supporting Old Levant’s position, kill him. Use the caves within the Old Burial Grounds. There are plenty of animals that will make short work of any evidence if he needs to be disposed of.”</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>NecroNote_BC_Mix_Legacy_04</Key>
    <Value>“If the opportunity arises to kidnap a chamberlord, do so. Hold them for ransom, and do not kill them unless it’s absolutely necessary. The &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;old cabin in the burned woods&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; to the south are equipped and prepared for such an event.”</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>NecroNote_BC_Mix_Legacy_05</Key>
    <Value>“If all goes well and you have the opportunity to capture Kirouac as well, do so. He is to be kept alive at all costs. Once war has been declared, he is to be returned home unharmed.”</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>NecroNote_BC_Mix_Legacy_06</Key>
    <Value>“All messages are to go through Commander Mantis at his &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;forest camp to the south of Enmerkar, near the stone steps&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. After his departure, all agents are to stick to their instructions to the letter.”</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>NecroNote_BC_Mix_Legacy_07</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>BalthaCorpse_BC_Mix_Legacy_01</Key>
    <Value>(This is Balthazar for sure. Or at least, what’s left of him. He appears to have been shot and left for the beasts to feed on. His eyes are frozen open in shock.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>BalthaCorpse_BC_Mix_Legacy_02</Key>
    <Value>(You close Balthazar’s eyes and move on. You can do nothing for him.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>BalthaNote_BC_Mix_Legacy_01</Key>
    <Value>“We understand that the old stone around the Necropolis is difficult to mine through, but the tunnel must be ready before the Council Meeting. We cannot risk the use of explosives so close to Berg until the final step.”</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>BalthaNote_BC_Mix_Legacy_02</Key>
    <Value>“If the tunnel is not completed in time, we may lose everything. Failure is not an option. Work double shifts if you have to.”</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>LeaderNote_BC_Mix_Legacy_01</Key>
    <Value>“Remember, our first priority is to ensure that the claims by Old Levant are quashed immediately. Once their “ambassador” is dead, do everything you can to tilt the Blue Chamber Collective into war with Levant.”</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>LeaderNote_BC_Mix_Legacy_02</Key>
    <Value>“If possible, try to capture Kirouac as well. Any additional confusion you can cause in the Levant government and military will help us maintain our covert status.”</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>LeaderNote_BC_Mix_Legacy_03</Key>
    <Value>“A second agent is making sure we uphold our end of the deal for our “friends” in Sirroco. Do not interact with her, she is not aware of our full plans and I want to keep it that way. Her loyalty to our cause isn’t certain.”</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_Mix_Legacy_01</Key>
    <Value>This meeting is a waste of time. Why drag all the Chamberlords here over issues that don’t matter? We should be discussing strategies to defend ourselves from Levant!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_Mix_Legacy_02</Key>
    <Value>Then again... If Old Levant’s claim is recognized, that might solve the issue entirely. At least they believe in the order and structure of the Blue Chamber’s laws. I'd trust them over those sand rats, Calixa and Simeon any day.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_Mix_Legacy_03</Key>
    <Value>Hah! I knew it! Levant has finally made their last mistake!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Sagard_BC_Mix_Legacy_a_03</Key>
    <Value>How can you even be sure that Levant did this?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_Mix_Legacy_04</Key>
    <Value>Amateur! The only ambassador they killed was the one from Old Levant, the one person who could have overturned their kingdom! They used firearms too!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_Mix_Legacy_05</Key>
    <Value>Now is not the time to debate the obvious. We gather our troops and strike NOW, before they strike us again! They likely have their whole army on the road for Berg as we speak!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Sagard_BC_Mix_Legacy_b_03</Key>
    <Value>I look forward to our revenge too, sir!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_Mix_Legacy_06</Key>
    <Value>Finally, someone who speaks my language! Everyone else is giving me toddler-speak about "waiting until we know for certain". These spineless politicians will get us all killed!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_Mix_Legacy_07</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_Mix_Legacy_08</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_Mix_Legacy_09</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>OldLevant_BC_Mix_Legacy_01</Key>
    <Value>When will the vote start? Old Levant’s claim cannot wait any longer!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_OldLevant_BC_Mix_Legacy_a_01</Key>
    <Value>What do you mean "Old" Levant? Was something there before the "Heroic Kingdom"?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>OldLevant_BC_Mix_Legacy_02</Key>
    <Value>Your ignorance doesn't surprise me. Records from before the Scourge can be difficult to find.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>OldLevant_BC_Mix_Legacy_03</Key>
    <Value>Abrassar wasn’t always a desert. It was once fertile and lush. The Scourge hit the region hard and scattered the tribes that called it home. One beast in particular had the entire region under its control for nearly fifty years. No one would dare venture out into the sands, day or night.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>OldLevant_BC_Mix_Legacy_04</Key>
    <Value>The current King and Queen of Levant led an army to kill it, and they succeeded. Elatt himself declared that they were to rule Abrassar as reward. And so they have, ever since.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>OldLevant_BC_Mix_Legacy_05</Key>
    <Value>Elatt gave away what he had no right to. I have proof that our clan is of the true tribe of Levant, and that we should be recognized as such. We deserve better than to be scavengers and bandits picking at bones.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_OldLevant_BC_Mix_Legacy_b_01</Key>
    <Value>You'll get your turn soon enough. Good decisions will take time and discussion.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>OldLevant_BC_Mix_Legacy_06</Key>
    <Value>No, not this time! The right decision is clear. Elatt gave away what he had no right to. Abrassar is our land. We should not lose the right to it simply because we did not have the manpower to defend it from the Scourge.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>OldLevant_BC_Mix_Legacy_07</Key>
    <Value>May the Five Winds favor us this day, and reverse the terrible decision of our new so-called "god".</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>OldLevant_BC_Mix_Legacy_08</Key>
    <Value>The Blue Chamber Council will recognize our claim. One way, or another.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>OldLevant_BC_Mix_Legacy_09</Key>
    <Value>(Fourteen bullet holes pierce her body. Just one would have been enough to end her life. This brutality was unnecessary)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Zephyr_BC_Mix_Legacy_01</Key>
    <Value>I’ve got no patience for those endless meetings. This armor’s not for decoration! I’d rather hunt manticores outside Berg than stand here as a... decorative diplomat!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Zephyr_BC_Mix_Legacy_02</Key>
    <Value>Oh, you wound me! How can you not have heard of the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;champion&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, Zephyrien? I don't suppose you've heard of my brother in arms, Soeran, either? You must have lived a sheltered life!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Zephyr_BC_Mix_Legacy_03</Key>
    <Value>Actually, it took me three. But that’s still more than most people can say, eh?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_BC_Mix_Legacy_01</Key>
    <Value>Oh. [PlayerName]. I wasn’t expecting to see you here.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_BC_Mix_Legacy_a_01</Key>
    <Value>Oliele? What happened to you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_BC_Mix_Legacy_02</Key>
    <Value>I... I don’t want to really talk about it. I had an incident on my first mission for Elatt. What you see is what he had to do to save me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_BC_Mix_Legacy_03</Key>
    <Value>Elatt isn’t quite what I thought he would be. I need answers. Answers by any means necessary.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_BC_Mix_Legacy_04</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_BC_Mix_Legacy_05</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_BC_Mix_Legacy_06</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Balthazar_BC_Mix_Legacy_01</Key>
    <Value>I do not look forward to this meeting. Both issues of the day are ugly indeed. The fate of two tribes in one hand, and a delicate land treaty in another. No one will walk away happy from this.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Balthazar_BC_Mix_Legacy_02</Key>
    <Value>On days like today, I wish I wasn’t the Collective’s greatest historian. Oh what I wouldn’t give to curl up in the archives and never come out…</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Balthazar_BC_Mix_Legacy_03</Key>
    <Value>Come to think of it, the delegation from Sirroco is running late. They were the ones who were desperate to come to an agreement about settling in the Hallowed Marsh, so I’m shocked they’ve not arrived.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Balthazar_BC_Mix_Legacy_04</Key>
    <Value>And then there’s Damian Lockwell’s absence. I would be shocked if he was boycotting the meeting...that would only prevent him from protecting the interests of his own region.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Balthazar_BC_Mix_Legacy_05</Key>
    <Value>Well, hello. Sorry, I’m still tired, I stayed up poring through the old archives through the night. Every other historian decided to pick up the research in the morning, but I can’t rest until I know I know the full story.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Balthazar_BC_Mix_Legacy_06</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Balthazar_BC_Mix_Legacy_07</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Balthazar_BC_Mix_Legacy_08</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Kirouac_BC_Mix_Legacy_01</Key>
    <Value>I don’t understand why the Collective is even giving the claims of Old Levant any attention. Calixa and Simeon were named rulers of Abrassar desert by Elatt himself. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Kirouac_BC_Mix_Legacy_02</Key>
    <Value>Old Levant abandoned Abrassar to the beasts of the Scourge. They have no right to demand to have it back after we did all the hard work of cleansing it of the scourge and re-settling it!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Kirouac_BC_Mix_Legacy_03</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Kirouac_BC_Mix_Legacy_04</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Kirouac_BC_Mix_Legacy_05</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyrene_BC_Mix_Legacy_01</Key>
    <Value>Keep walking. I’m on duty and have no time for you. Or anyone else for that matter. Shoo.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyrill_Turnbull_BC_Mix_Legacy_01</Key>
    <Value>Today really makes me nervous... Such immense shifts in the status quo are never good for business. I just hope our Headmaster knows what he’s doing…</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyrill_Turnbull_BC_Mix_Legacy_a_01</Key>
    <Value>I thought Soroboreans were supposed to have absolute faith in their leadership?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyrill_Turnbull_BC_Mix_Legacy_02</Key>
    <Value>Well... Yes. We’re supposed to. But we’re only human.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyrill_Turnbull_BC_Mix_Legacy_b_01</Key>
    <Value>Well, given the work you have to do to get that position, I’m sure he does.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyrill_Turnbull_BC_Mix_Legacy_03</Key>
    <Value>One can only hope…</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyrill_Turnbull_BC_Mix_Legacy_04</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Giants_01</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName], it’s good to see you. The war goes very poorly. Levantine forces are within miles of Enmerkar.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Giants_a_01</Key>
    <Value>What do you need for us to turn this around, Lady Aberdeen?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Giants_02</Key>
    <Value>What we need are allies. Strong allies. Allies who will make Levant pause merely at the sight of them.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Giants_03</Key>
    <Value>Tell me, [PlayerName], what do you know about the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ash Giants&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Giants_a_03</Key>
    <Value>Enough to know that they won't be interested in an alliance. They like their isolation.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Giants_04</Key>
    <Value>We have little to lose by trying, and much to gain if we succeed. It is a worthy gamble.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Giants_b_03</Key>
    <Value>Honestly, not much, other than that they're absolutely huge and breathe noxious fumes.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Giants_05</Key>
    <Value>Now you understand why I would like Levant to see a few on our side of the field. Just the sight of a few Ash Giants on our side might be enough to halt their offensive.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Giants_06</Key>
    <Value>Even in peaceful times, the Giants would be an incredible boon to the collective. Their craftsmanship is beyond compare. This would benefit us greatly, war or not.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Giants_a_06</Key>
    <Value>And what do you think they'd accept in return? An alliance goes both ways.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Giants_07</Key>
    <Value>You will need to make an effort to understand their culture. Find out what they will want or need, and try to fill that need. That’s really all we can do.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Giants_a_07</Key>
    <Value>I really don't think I'm qualified for this...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Giants_08</Key>
    <Value>You're all we can spare. I need Gabriella and Julius on their current assignments, and most everyone else with even a small amount of tact is doing essential work for the war effort.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Giants_b_07</Key>
    <Value>Huge smoke-spewing creatures. Make them allies. Got it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Giants_09</Key>
    <Value>I appreciate your cavalier outlook, but please, [PlayerName], take this task seriously. The last thing anyone wants is the Giants deciding the Blue Chamber Collective is their enemy.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Giants_10</Key>
    <Value>This is a long shot, and I have little hope it can be done, but it’s a risk we must take. Do what you can, [PlayerName]. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bring the Ash Giants to our side by any means possible&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Giants_11</Key>
    <Value>The nearest Ash Giant settlement is in the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hallowed Marsh region, near Monsoon’s Vigil crystal&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. I wish you the best of luck in winning them over.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Giants_12</Key>
    <Value>You’re back! How did it go?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Giants_a_12</Key>
    <Value>I'm handling some loose ends. I need to talk with Damian Lockwell and Cyril Turnbull.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Giants_13</Key>
    <Value>Damian Lockwell is the Chamberlord of Monsoon, you'll have to travel back to the Hallowed Marsh if you want to speak with him... Cyril Turnbull is here in Berg, though. I suspect he's at the Blue Chamber.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Giants_b_12</Key>
    <Value>Done. The Ash Giants are willing to join the Collective. They will likely send their leader or some other ambassador soon.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Giants_14</Key>
    <Value>I'm impressed, very impressed. This was a long shot at best, and you succeeded. I'm proud of you, [PlayerName]. You've come a long way.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Giants_a_14</Key>
    <Value>I may have angered a faction within the Giants to do it. We may run into large problems in the near future.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Giants_15</Key>
    <Value>All that matters to me are that you got results. As long as an alliance with the main group is secure, any short term problems are worth it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Giants_c_12</Key>
    <Value>I couldn't make it happen, I'm sorry.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Giants_16</Key>
    <Value>Well, it was a long shot at any rate. Thank you for your efforts.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Giants_d_12</Key>
    <Value>It fell apart. They don't want anything to do with humans anymore.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Giants_17</Key>
    <Value>Don't be too hard on yourself. This was bound to happen eventually. Bridging the gap between two cultures is never a simple thing.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Giants_e_12</Key>
    <Value>I... may have caused a major diplomatic incident.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Giants_18</Key>
    <Value>Did I not ask you to handle this with care and tact? I wasn't expecting success, but I was expecting better than this [PlayerName]. Still, I can't say I'm surprised. They are Giants, after all.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Giants_a_18</Key>
    <Value>How did things go while I was gone?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Giants_19</Key>
    <Value>Levant's aggressive looting of the eastern regions has roused many estranged tribes within the Collective. Tribes that have barely kept contact with us have sent us a flood of new warriors, all of them eager to fight.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Giants_20</Key>
    <Value>And with the Ash Giants now on our side, I think we will be able to rapidly turn this war around. Levant won't know what hit them!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Giants_21</Key>
    <Value>With the Ash Giants on our side, we could have turned this war around overnight. But even without them, I see our chances improving considerably.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Giants_22</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Giants_23</Key>
    <Value>I'm still planning our next move. Take this opportunity to rest or train. I need you to be ready when the time comes.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_01</Key>
    <Value>Haloo there my little friend! Welcome to our outpost! What can I do to make us both happy, hmmmm?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_GoldBelly_BC_Giants_a_01</Key>
    <Value>I’m here to negotiate an alliance between the Giants and the Blue Chamber Collective.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_02</Key>
    <Value>An alliance with your people, you say? Hooh... That will be tough business. You will need to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;speak with Highlord Cyr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Good luck. I do not think he is interested. He is very traditional.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_GoldBelly_BC_Giants_b_01</Key>
    <Value>Can I buy your goods?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_03</Key>
    <Value>You can! It makes me happy to see the silver come in, and the goods go out!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_GoldBelly_BC_Giants_c_01</Key>
    <Value>I don’t need anything right now.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_04</Key>
    <Value>Au! You make Gold Belly sad, small one!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_05</Key>
    <Value>How did it go, human?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_GoldBelly_BC_Giants_a_05</Key>
    <Value>Cyr will discuss an alliance. He told me to come back in a few days to negotiate it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_06</Key>
    <Value>Wonderful news! Maybe my goods will finally go all over the world. And maybe I will finally be rich! Oh, and it would be nice for humans to start to appreciate our culture, too, of course.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_07</Key>
    <Value>&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Do not keep him waiting too much.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; The Ashborn are very patient, but you do not wish to press us.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_GoldBelly_BC_Giants_a_07</Key>
    <Value>I have to notice... You are far better at speaking our language than Cyr is.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_08</Key>
    <Value>Yes. I do business with humans from time to time. I learned the language. Most other Ashborn know barely a few words in your tongue. Many are very embarrassed by it. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_GoldBelly_BC_Giants_a_08</Key>
    <Value>How do you handle government here? I need all the information I can get if I want to convince Highlord Cyr.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_09</Key>
    <Value>Position is decided at birth by the two heads of Giant government. There is the Highmonk who serves Dusk Father, and is master of the porcelain arts, and there is the Highlord, who serves Dawn Weaver and is master of the Ash-Silk.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_10</Key>
    <Value>The Highmonk has big influence over people, as Dusk Father is one who breathed the life into us when we were just clay and cinder. People listen to him, because the Dusk Father speaks through him and his porcelain.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_11</Key>
    <Value>The Highlord holds the real power. He speaks for the Dawn Weaver, who weaved the fabric of Ashborn society, and so he decides what is part of Ashborn society, and what is not.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_12</Key>
    <Value>... I will let you in on a secret, human. Highlord Cyr is not very.... What is the word? Popu... popular! Yes, he is not popular with most of our people here. They think he is too strict. Too afraid of new ideas... But he has big ambition and fears losing power.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_GoldBelly_BC_Giants_b_08</Key>
    <Value>Can you teach me your culture?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_13</Key>
    <Value>I am not the best teacher for this... There was a human who studied us many years ago, and gave us a copy of his book about us. But most Ashborn do not understand human writing. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;So we put it in the old storage shed.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_14</Key>
    <Value>It should be not too far from the village. It is &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;North-East, across a long stone bridge. There is a big stone building on an island in the swamp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_15</Key>
    <Value>Hah! You did it! You changed Cyr’s mind! Very good work, my friend! With this alliance, I will get all kinds of new and special goods here! </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_16</Key>
    <Value>You did great thing here today, human. Our people are already much happier with Cyr gone. Highmonk will now choose a new Highlord for us. And hopefully one who will listen.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_17</Key>
    <Value>That was a very ugly problem... I am glad it did not go worse. It will take years for the village to settle back to calm!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_GoldBelly_BC_Giants_a_17</Key>
    <Value>What happens to Cyr now?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_18</Key>
    <Value>He is an exile now. In twenty years, he can come back and beg for forgiveness from Dusk Father or Dawn Weaver. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_19</Key>
    <Value>I like you, human! I hope I see you more often! Here, something special for the road home!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_GoldBelly_BC_Giants_a_19</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_20</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_GoldBelly_BC_Giants_a_20</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_21</Key>
    <Value>You always welcome to trade with Gold Belly, my little friend! I hope to see you again many many times!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_22</Key>
    <Value>He ask you to go into Reptile Lair to fetch rare root, no? Be very careful in there. Try not to fight big nasty Tuanosaurs unless you have to. They trouble even for big tough giants!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_GoldBelly_BC_Giants_a_22</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_23</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_GoldBelly_BC_Giants_a_23</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_24</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_GoldBelly_BC_Giants_a_24</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_25</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_26</Key>
    <Value>Well, looks like things will not change much. But maybe someday we will work together. I’m glad you came, human. Feel free to visit and trade with me, eh?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_27</Key>
    <Value>Au! My little friend! Welcome back, what can I do for you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_28</Key>
    <Value>What is on your mind, small one?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_29</Key>
    <Value>These tough rules on trade that Highlord Cyr made are very hard on me. I want to trade with all people and all cities, but he tell me I can only sell to people who come here, and there are not many that do!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_30</Key>
    <Value>Au, you from human marsh city! You should not speak about this “Elatt” person here. Highlord Cyr get very angry if you do! He not like hearing about other gods.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_31</Key>
    <Value>You smell like sands! You must be from from desert city! I hope you brought many useful goods from there! I have always wanted to see it with my own eyes, someday!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_32</Key>
    <Value>Things are doing ok here. I am glad you came to visit!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_33</Key>
    <Value>Hooh, there was big Earth Beast attack not long ago. Beasts went running past village to attack marsh city! I hope you help to keep them all safe! I don’t want to lose customers like that!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>GoldBelly_BC_Giants_34</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_01</Key>
    <Value>A human, in my village? What brings you before the Ashborn of the Marsh, little one?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_a_01</Key>
    <Value>I'm just passing through.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_02</Key>
    <Value>Then pass through faster. You bring worry and change. If you visit, speak only to Gold Belly. Leave the rest of my people alone.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_b_01</Key>
    <Value>I'm here to learn about your people.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_03</Key>
    <Value>Oh, another curious one. I am Highlord Cyr, the leader of this village. I am master of the sacred ash-silk weaving, I weave cloth as a prayer in the name of the Dawn Weaver and I teach this art to the other highborns.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_04</Key>
    <Value>Our monks make the porcelain in the name of the Dusk Father, and fill it with his magic. Your people like the porcelain and silks and many come here offering much silver and gold for some of it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_05</Key>
    <Value>That is all there is to tell. Now, go, little human.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_c_01</Key>
    <Value>I'm here on behalf of the Blue Chamber Collective. We want to form an alliance with you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_06</Key>
    <Value>Oh, is that all? You want big nasty "Giants" to eat your enemies alive, don't you? You think you are bigger than you are, little speck!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_a_06</Key>
    <Value>The many leaders in my tribe all consider you very important and want to invite you to represent your people in the Blue Chamber Collective.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_07</Key>
    <Value>Oh, now they consider Highlord Cyr important? What changed, Cyr wonders... I think you just want to boss Ashborn around like silkworms! But I am generous Ashborn. You say for real I get to be a leader in this Blue Room Collection?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_08</Key>
    <Value>Then maybe we can discuss this. I want good things for my people, and if I can get them from little humans by just talking and not with war, that will help my people.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_09</Key>
    <Value>I make arrangements for the talk. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Come back before end of month&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. I hope discussion leads to new understanding.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_10</Key>
    <Value>I hope discussion leads to new understanding.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_11</Key>
    <Value>Hmm? You want to start alliance talk now?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_a_11</Key>
    <Value>I’m not ready just yet, I’m still preparing.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_12</Key>
    <Value>This is not problem for now. Don’t take too long.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_b_11</Key>
    <Value>Yes, I’m ready to begin.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_13</Key>
    <Value>You come at good time, human. We are ready too.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_14</Key>
    <Value>Human, you keep us waiting very long! I wonder if you even want to make alliance talk!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_a_14</Key>
    <Value>I’m not ready just yet, I’m still preparing.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_15</Key>
    <Value>Not ready after all this time, still? This make me mad. No. We have talk now, or we have talk never!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_b_14</Key>
    <Value>Yes, I’m ready to begin.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_16</Key>
    <Value>About time you ready! You show us great disrespect for making us wait!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_17</Key>
    <Value>Now, how you make this work, if Highlord Cyr join your Blue Room Collection? What means, exactly?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_a_17</Key>
    <Value>(Use the gossip you heard from Gold Belly to tempt Cyr’s ambition)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_a_17_b</Key>
    <Value>It means you become a chamberlord, helping decide on important issues that affect all the tribes. We debate to find a solution that works for everyone.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_18</Key>
    <Value>And you give this power to I? You welcome me like this? I like this respect.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_b_17</Key>
    <Value>You will still rule here as you please. But when there is a council meeting, you should come to Berg to help decide on matters that affect all the tribes.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_19</Key>
    <Value>So Chamberlords still rule home... but each has one vote on important things and can call council if can't resolve on own? Hmmm... This give me much power, but not too much more work. This is not bad.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_c_17</Key>
    <Value>It means you and your giants become part of the Collective, all of us work together and consult each other for major decisions.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_20</Key>
    <Value>So I should trust that humans care about what Ashborn need? Hah. I not stupid. Humans greedy and only work together to exploit each other!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_21</Key>
    <Value>What you expect from us if we join, hmm? You want us to be follow Blue Room laws?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_a_21</Key>
    <Value>(Use the gossip you heard from Gold Belly to smooth things over)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_a_21_b</Key>
    <Value>Chamberlords can rule their lands as they choose, although most follow our Tribal Laws. They've kept us alive for the past thousand years.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_22</Key>
    <Value>So... tribe laws just recommendation? As long as not causing major problems for other tribes, we is not in trouble? Hmm... this is not bad.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_b_21</Key>
    <Value>The Collective is family. If there is a conflict between our laws, I'm sure we can work something out.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_23</Key>
    <Value>Hmmm... I warn you that I not bend on this. Ashborn always follow Ashborn Law. It work out only if you come to our understanding of law. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_c_21</Key>
    <Value>If you join the Collective, you have to follow our laws.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_24</Key>
    <Value>And if in conflict with Ashborn laws, we have to give up our law and culture? I draw a line there. If we join, we still use our laws and government, and if you no like, too bad!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_25</Key>
    <Value>I not understand how human culture not fall apart. How you handle life, without the guidance of the Dusk Father and Dawn Weaver?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_a_25</Key>
    <Value>(Use the information you picked up from the historian’s book to smooth things over)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_a_25_b</Key>
    <Value>The entire Tribe is family. We look after one another and guide each other, with the advice and leadership of the Chamberlord.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_26</Key>
    <Value>Ah... So Chamberlord provides guidance, and then allows other to teach and guide tribe people too? This is not bad system for humans, I understand it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_b_25</Key>
    <Value>While individuals are on their own, the tribe and Chamberlord act as guidance for anyone who needs it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_27</Key>
    <Value>Hmm... This is chaos, but at least it is controlled chaos. We will not do this, but if it works for humans, I say let them.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_c_25</Key>
    <Value>We choose what to do with our lives however we want. We make our own future.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_28</Key>
    <Value>Madness! How can humans get anything done with no guidance and structure? No wonder you think you can just walk into Ashborn city and demand things!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_29</Key>
    <Value>Now, how you Blue Room people handle law? What you do if there is criminal?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_a_29</Key>
    <Value>(Use the information you picked up from the historian’s book to play up your culture’s similarities)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_a_29_b</Key>
    <Value>They are either exiled, or must repay the tribe for the harm done. We don't demand payment right away. Their family pays back the debt slowly over time.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_30</Key>
    <Value>Ohh... This... not bad idea. This way law breakers still help the tribe! This way, everyone get back what is theirs eventually... This is close to forgiveness ritual in Ashborn law!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_b_29</Key>
    <Value>The Blue Chamber believes that we must avoid killing unless it is necessary. Criminals are either exiled, or must repay the tribe.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_31</Key>
    <Value>This is like us too. I think you should let exiles back into tribe eventually, otherwise they just a waste to your people.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_c_29</Key>
    <Value>Those who break the law, and their descendants, are put to work to repay the debt, however many generations is takes.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_32</Key>
    <Value>Ashborn already tried that, much before come to this land. It not work well. Slaves never want to work forever. Slaves get angry at treatment. Cause more problems than solve. Humans must have teeny-tiny brains if they not realize by now.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_33</Key>
    <Value>I hear human worship other human named Elatt. Why they dare mock Dusk Father and Dawn Weaver? No living thing can be a god!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_a_33</Key>
    <Value>(Use the knowledge you got from the Holy Mission to defuse the situation)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_a_33_b</Key>
    <Value>He was a hero who stopped the "Earth Beasts" by making the Light Ray above Monsoon. We just honor his memory and his sacrifice.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_34</Key>
    <Value>Au! So this Elatt no threat to Dusk Father... Dusk Father accepts this human foolishness, it is no harm to him. We wondered why such a light had chosen to fly over a human city. If this true, then maybe hope for humans not to ruin this world, like we lost ours.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_b_33</Key>
    <Value>Elatt isn't so much a god. He is just living thought that exists after his body's death.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_35</Key>
    <Value>Karash naga! Dusk Father not pleased. No life survive past death, only porcelain and ash-silk does. You humans bow to fake tricks and empty god!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_c_33</Key>
    <Value>He is a lesser god that lives on this world. Not a creator, and not as powerful as Dusk Father or Dawn Weaver, but for us humans, he seems pretty big.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_36</Key>
    <Value>Au, cekta. He not create humans, but is lesser god that only matters to this world? ...As long as humans understand Elatt lesser than Dusk Father and Dawn Weaver, we will accept it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_37</Key>
    <Value>As long as humans understand Elatt lesser than Dusk Father and Dawn Weaver, we will accept it. Giants have no bother with him as long as it only matter to humans.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_38</Key>
    <Value>It only been short time in Ashborn time since Earth Beasts appear. Humans let them out into world, we sure. What you do about them, these enders of your world?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_a_38</Key>
    <Value>(Use the knowledge you got from the Holy Mission to reassure him)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_a_38_b</Key>
    <Value>We created crystal Vigils that keep them away from places where people live, and when we can, we destroy them. There is one protecting your village already.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_39</Key>
    <Value>Au, so that is why they stopped coming near out city. It seem you already do much for Ashborn about the Earth Beasts. This very good.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_b_38</Key>
    <Value>We destroy them whenever we can, and rely on the protection of Elatt's followers to keep our villages safe.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_40</Key>
    <Value>Then at least you know is a threat, and are working to stop it. There may be hope for humans if they see that!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_c_38</Key>
    <Value>They're not the end of the world. They're like any monster, as long as you know how to fight them, they aren't a problem.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_41</Key>
    <Value>Hah, you think that now, but when they bleed the ground and kill the world, you realize you wrong! We hoped you had better plan than that!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_42</Key>
    <Value>Enough, I think I am ready to decide.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_a_42</Key>
    <Value>Before you do, I found this stone on a dead ash giant. I think you should have it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_b_42</Key>
    <Value>I hope I convinced you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_43</Key>
    <Value>Au! That is a heart from Ashborn! Thank you for bringing home. Now can craft into lasting porcelain, and Ashborn's life will endure. You do good thing for his family.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_44</Key>
    <Value>Yes, I know what Dawn Weaver would like Ashborn to do about this alliance</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_45</Key>
    <Value>Hmm... My people like what you suggest, and I see we not completely different. I say yes. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;We will join Blue Chamber Collective&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. We already hear about your fight with desert men, and will help. We send you a few Ashborn to send them running away like little marsh lizards!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_a_45</Key>
    <Value>This is great news. Welcome to the Blue Chamber Collective, Chamberlord Cyr.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_46</Key>
    <Value>Hmmm... I not see benefit in closer connection. I satisfied with way things are now. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;I refuse alliance&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_47</Key>
    <Value>You mock our traditions and people with yours. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;I think we should close village from humans for good&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Your ideas ruin Ashborn culture and cause bleeding of the world!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_a_47</Key>
    <Value>I don't know about that... A lot of your people seem really disappointed about your decision.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_48</Key>
    <Value>I decide what is allowed in Ashborn society and what is not. If others not like it, too bad!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_a_48</Key>
    <Value>Well, I tried. I’m sorry you feel that way.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_49</Key>
    <Value>If stay any longer, you really will feel sorry. Get out now, or I throw you out myself!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_Giants_b_48</Key>
    <Value>Then maybe they need a new Highlord, one who actually cares about what they want! What do you say, everyone? Why don’t we get rid of Highlord Cyr?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_50</Key>
    <Value>CIN TARAK! You dare to turn people against me, puny thing?!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_51</Key>
    <Value>How is things, my ally?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_52</Key>
    <Value>Why you come back? No alliance! If you need anything, you deal with Gold Belly! You no waste my time!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_53</Key>
    <Value>You still allowed to visit, but you only deal with Gold Belly. You leave rest of people alone!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_54</Key>
    <Value>If you want alliance talk, you need to prove you have good will for us, even if it means danger for you. You &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;go to the cave where the swamp lizards live, and you bring back some Obsidiroot for us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, for medicine.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_55</Key>
    <Value>To get there, you go West, into belly of swamp, then you go South to cave with glowing flower on root above it. If you not willing to face giant lizard for us, you not worth being ally!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_56</Key>
    <Value>Au! You actually bring the rare root! You must be very strong! Maybe there is benefit in alliance with humans! Alright, &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;I am ready to make alliance talk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; with you. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_57</Key>
    <Value>To make alliance official, I make you honorary Ashborn. We mix our blood into wine, and drink from it, so that our strength will be shared!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_58</Key>
    <Value>(The mixture of your blood makes you gag and retch, but you feel some of the toughness of the Giants fill your body.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_Giants_59</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Culture_BC_Giants_01</Key>
    <Value>This appears to be a book written by an explorer who spent a year living near the giants... A lot of the pages are ruined, but many sections remain intact.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Culture_BC_Giants_a_01</Key>
    <Value>(Read about Giant family structure.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Culture_BC_Giants_02</Key>
    <Value>Giant Children are examined by the Highmonk and the Highlord when twenty years old, and their position in life is decided. Builders, merchants and craftsmen serve the Highmonk, and soldiers, artists and farmers are governed by the Highlord.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Culture_BC_Giants_03</Key>
    <Value>Families of deceased giants will give a heart from the dead to the local Highmonk, who will use their craft to merge the stone heart into their porcelain art, so that some part of the giant's life will endure beyond their death. The Highlord will then commission a silk banner to reflect that giant's deeds and knowledge.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Culture_BC_Giants_04</Key>
    <Value>Ash Giants believe that death is final, and that only the works that have been created in porcelain and ash-silk endure beyond death. They do, however, believe in passing down the wisdom of their ancestors via these crafts to educate and guide their descendants.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Culture_BC_Giants_b_01</Key>
    <Value>(Read about Giant law and punishment.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Culture_BC_Giants_05</Key>
    <Value>Giants who cause minor transgressions must make amends to the person they wronged, and must create a porcelain item or an ash-silk item for the wronged party, depending on their trade.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Culture_BC_Giants_06</Key>
    <Value>Larger transgressions carry the penalty of exile for twenty years. After that time, the giant may attempt to seek forgiveness and return to giant society. A giant may be forgiven only twice, once in the name of the Dawn Weaver, and once in the name of the Dusk Father.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Culture_BC_Giants_07</Key>
    <Value>After a third transgression, the giant may never return to their colony and is considered dead to them. However, returning an exile's heart is welcome, as even the worst giants are considered to have a place within their history.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Culture_BC_Giants_08</Key>
    <Value>The only crimes that are unforgivable across all of giant society are the murder of a silk-weaver or a porcelain-crafter. For every other offence, it is possible to seek forgiveness after the period of exile, although each giant tribe uses their own discretion for whether or not to forgive a crime.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Culture_BC_Giants_c_01</Key>
    <Value>(Close the book.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Culture_BC_Giants_09</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Culture_BC_Giants_10</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Culture_BC_Giants_11</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Religion_BC_Giants_a_00</Key>
    <Value>I need to learn about the Ash Giants and their religious views. The Blue Chamber is trying to form an alliance with them.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Religion_BC_Giants_01</Key>
    <Value>Ah... The Ash Giants... They're a very traditionalist and peculiar bunch. We tried sending messengers of our own when they first landed on Aurai. We did not get any real results.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Religion_BC_Giants_02</Key>
    <Value>They believe that long ago their ancient ancestors lived on the Scarlet Moon, but that they advanced too quickly and killed their world, causing the world's blood to stain the ground red. Their creation myth says that a single stone of ash and cinder escaped the Scarlet Moon and fell to our world.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Religion_BC_Giants_03</Key>
    <Value>Then, they say the Dusk Father forgave their crimes, and breathed life into the ash and cinder, and thus the giants were born. To stop them repeating the past, the Dawn Weaver taught them the art of weaving Ash-Silk, and how to create a lasting society.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Religion_BC_Giants_04</Key>
    <Value>They never forget the destruction of what they believe was their home, and are thus very slow to change. You will need a delicate touch.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Religion_BC_Giants_a_04</Key>
    <Value>What do they think of Elatt?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Religion_BC_Giants_05</Key>
    <Value>Sadly, I doubt they will ever accept Elatt. They do not believe that anything mortal could become divine. To them, the Dusk Father and Dawn Weaver are divine purely because they are not tainted by mortal concerns.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Religion_BC_Giants_b_04</Key>
    <Value>What about the defeat of the Scourge?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Religion_BC_Giants_06</Key>
    <Value>They call them the "Earth Beasts", and many believe their appearance signaled the beginning of the destruction of Aurai, just as they believe the Scarlet Moon was destroyed. They are, however, perplexed as to why it was stopped.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Religion_BC_Giants_07</Key>
    <Value>They noticed the ray of light above Monsoon, but I doubt they understand what it, or the Vigils are. As far as the more superstitious Giants concerned, the humans that started the end times managed to stop it, and they carried on with their lives.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Religion_BC_Giants_c_04</Key>
    <Value>Thank you, this should help my dealings with them.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Religion_BC_Giants_08</Key>
    <Value>Best of luck with that. Do not be too forceful with them. The Ash Giants are slow to change, and have a forceful temper.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Religion_BC_Giants_09</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_01</Key>
    <Value>There you are. I was hoping you’d return soon.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_02</Key>
    <Value>I know you're not the most resourceful person, but I'm out of options. I have an offer for you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_03</Key>
    <Value>You've been a great help to us, [PlayerName]. I had a feeling I'd be making you this offer.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_04</Key>
    <Value>I'm going to come right out with it. I need you to join the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Krypteia&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Bones_a_04</Key>
    <Value>The... what?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_05</Key>
    <Value>You have not heard of us? Good. Then we've been doing our job.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Bones_b_04</Key>
    <Value>Wait, the Krypteia actually exist?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_06</Key>
    <Value>Yes, we do, [PlayerName]. And you will keep quiet about our existence. We perform our duties far better if no one knows we exist.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Bones_c_04</Key>
    <Value>Wait... You’re the leader of the Krypteia? That explains a lot.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_07</Key>
    <Value>I hope there is no barbed meaning behind those words. We do what we do for the good of the Collective. All of Aurai, even.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_08</Key>
    <Value>I'm sure that even if you've heard of us, you'll have misconceptions about who we are and what we do. When the Collective was first formed, some of us wanted to ensure that detailed records were kept of everything we did. More than simple paper could cover.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_08-B</Key>
    <Value>Thus, we enshrined the memories of several of our members into an altar, creating the Ancestral Memories. We've been adding to it ever since. This collection of memories is the heart and soul of the Collective.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_09</Key>
    <Value>It’s how we've governed and guided our people for centuries.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_10</Key>
    <Value>Then, one of our members betrayed us. She became a Lich by devouring the memories of her ancestors. By anchoring her life to each of her descendants’, she became immortal. You may know her as the Scarlet Lady.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Bones_a_10</Key>
    <Value>The Lich that supposedly fled to the Scarlet Moon? Everyone’s heard that fairy tale.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_11</Key>
    <Value>I assure you, she is no fairy tale. If the Scarlet Lady were to gain control over the Ancestral Memories, it would be the end of the Collective. She could use them to guide our decisions as she pleased, or unleash a horde of undead on Enmerkar, or worse.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_12</Key>
    <Value>We oppose the Scarlet lady’s efforts to control the Collective. We consult the Ancestral Memories regularly to find her potential descendants and deal with them.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Bones_a_12</Key>
    <Value>You mean that you kill them.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_13</Key>
    <Value>Yes. It’s tragic, but it’s the only way to sever the Scarlet Lady's hold on the world. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Bones_a_13</Key>
    <Value>It's been ages and you haven't wiped out all of her descendants yet?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_14</Key>
    <Value>She has grown craftier at spawning and hiding new descendants over the ages. More than once, underestimating her intelligence has caused great harm to the Collective.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Bones_b_12</Key>
    <Value>And you want me to join... Why exactly?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_15</Key>
    <Value>The Memories warned me that the Scarlet Lady is moving against us. But most of our members are tied up with the war and I cannot reach out to them for help. All I have are Gabriella and Julius right now. I need new members.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Bones_a_15</Key>
    <Value>Members, you say? Sounds like you have more than just me in mind.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_16</Key>
    <Value>Yes. I've already asked Roland. He has agreed. As long as he remains with the Krypteia, I will make his Blood Price payments for him. He could not refuse.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Bones_a_16</Key>
    <Value>No, I don't see how he could. He lacks any way to pay the Blood Price on his own.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_17</Key>
    <Value>I know how to use my assets, [PlayerName]. Roland feels he has nothing to lose. I would be a fool not to leverage that.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Bones_b_16</Key>
    <Value>Roland? That's a mistake.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_18</Key>
    <Value>I hope not, but I am backed into a corner. And he is desperate to pay off his Blood Price. I think this will push him to be useful to the Collective for the first time in his life.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_19</Key>
    <Value>I know this is sudden, and that you might have doubts. I won't force you to remain with us afterwards, as long as you keep our secrets. But I desperately need help. The Collective depends on us.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_20</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Bones_a_20</Key>
    <Value>Fine, I'll help, but only until this crisis is dealt with. I'm not committing to more.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_21</Key>
    <Value>Very well. If you're not willing to remain with the Krypteia once this threat has passed, I understand.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Bones_b_20</Key>
    <Value>Protecting the people from an undead Lich? I accept.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_22</Key>
    <Value>I knew my faith in you was well placed. I hope you continue to prove helpful to us.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Bones_d_20</Key>
    <Value>I'm not interested.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_24</Key>
    <Value>Then I'll just have to pray that Roland is enough... Please, reconsider.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_24_RETALK</Key>
    <Value>Have you changed your mind, [PlayerName]?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_25</Key>
    <Value>I’ve already sent Roland to the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Conflux Mountain in the Chersonese&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; to open himself to Mana. I'm honestly worried if he'll be able to handle the journey. I need you to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;meet him inside there and keep him safe&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; until he can open up his magical potential.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_26</Key>
    <Value>If you haven't already unlocked the power of Mana within you, now is a good time. If you choose to remain a Member of the Krypteia, gaining the power of magic will make communing with the Ancestral Memories much easier.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_27</Key>
    <Value>Once you've finished &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;helping Roland at the Conflux Mountain, report to Gabriella Sullivan&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. She will direct your efforts to counter this crisis. Do whatever she asks of you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_28</Key>
    <Value>I just saw Gabriella. What happened down here?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Bones_a_28</Key>
    <Value>Take a look downstairs. We have a new friend.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_29</Key>
    <Value>I'm afraid I don't understand. Where is Roland? What happened here?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Bones_a_29</Key>
    <Value>He's turned into a Lich. And not a hostile one either. His spirit has merged with the Ancestral Memories. You should probably ask him... Well, “them” for the details.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_30</Key>
    <Value>I... Is this true? Roland, a Lich? And he has become part of the Ancestral Memories? This... this is a huge change. One that I pray is for the best.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_31</Key>
    <Value>If this Lich really is willing to help us, then we have levelled the playing field against the Scarlet Lady... I should hurry down and speak with them.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Bones_b_29</Key>
    <Value>We managed to save the Memories. Well, Roland did. He... didn't make it</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_32</Key>
    <Value>I’m glad to hear of his success, and I mourn his loss. May he rest in the arms of his ancestors.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_33</Key>
    <Value>I just saw Gabriella. What happened down here? An army of ghosts just ran screaming through Berg! What did you do?!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Bones_c_28</Key>
    <Value>A follower of the Scarlet Lady forced her spirit into the Ancestral Memories. Roland managed to cut her out of them. It was a disaster...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_34</Key>
    <Value>I was afraid it was something like that. Those ghosts must be corrupted memories that were severed from the group. Well, I suppose it can't be helped. If the Memories had been completely corrupted by the Scarlet Lady... The consequences would have been final!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_35</Key>
    <Value>I'm glad I confided this mission to you. Your actions made a great difference today, although no one in the Collective will ever know what you did for them.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Bones_a_35</Key>
    <Value>If the Krypteia ever needs me again, you know how to find me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_36</Key>
    <Value>I do indeed. Thank you for choosing to remain with us, [PlayerName]. Your continued aid is welcome.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Bones_b_35</Key>
    <Value>And that's all. I am done with this Krypteia work. You can handle this shady business on your own.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_37</Key>
    <Value>I'm disappointed, but I understand. As long as you keep what you witnessed here a secret, you're free to go. If ever you wish to help us again, come to me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_38</Key>
    <Value>I am proud to count you as family, [PlayerName] Aberdeen. Thank you for all you’ve done for us.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_39</Key>
    <Value>&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;There’s dire news from Cierzo&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Burac, our gate warden, says our town is being threatened by the bandit fortress along the beach. Apparently, the rabble there has found some solid leadership and is planning to attack Cierzo.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_40</Key>
    <Value>Could I ask you to go see Burac in Cierzo and help however you can, [PlayerName]?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Bones_a_40</Key>
    <Value>Alright, I’ll go check on Cierzo and talk to Burac. Farewell.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_41</Key>
    <Value>It may be some time before the situation changes. You’re free for now. Come back in a few days, and I will let you know if there is more you can do.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Bones_42</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_01</Key>
    <Value>(He is barely conscious)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_02</Key>
    <Value>Who... What... Oh. [PlayerName]. That was you who saved me? Thank you, I really owe you one. That rock mantis really had me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_a_02</Key>
    <Value>You're injured. Hang on, let me patch that up.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_03</Key>
    <Value>I have some bandages on me, I can handle it myself. You keep going.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_a_03</Key>
    <Value>Whoa whoa whoa, I'm coming with you. I don't want to have to bail you out again!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_04</Key>
    <Value>No. If I'm going to do this, I need to try to make it on my own. Give me a few minutes head start to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;get to the heart of the mountain&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, alright?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_b_03</Key>
    <Value>Fine by me. Don't get into any more trouble.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_05</Key>
    <Value>Right. I’ll try to avoid running into anything else lethal today. Thanks.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_06</Key>
    <Value>Oh, Elatt's name... Everything hurts. Everything. Hurts. I had no idea the Mana ritual was so painful.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_a_06</Key>
    <Value>Roland, exactly how much of your life did you sacrifice to tap into the Ley Line's Mana?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_07</Key>
    <Value>I don't know. I just kept pouring my life into the Ley Line, as much as I could bear... I wanted as much Mana as I could take.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_a_07</Key>
    <Value>Roland, you complete moron. Do you have a death wish?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_08</Key>
    <Value>You're asking? I honestly don't care what happens to me anymore. Rissa has me by the stones. If I don't work for her, I can't pay my Blood Price. If I do work for her, I face almost certain death. Either way, there's nothing to lose.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_b_07</Key>
    <Value>You must have gained a ton of magical power. How does it feel?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_09</Key>
    <Value>I feel worn and empty... but also full of power. For the first time in my life, I can actually reshape my future.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_10</Key>
    <Value>I'm already able to use Magic. See this sword? I made it myself out of my own Mana. I can make a blade whenever I need one!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_a_10</Key>
    <Value>That's a sword made of Mana? That's kind of impressive for a new mage. Do you know how to use it?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_11</Key>
    <Value>It might be made of Mana, but it's still a sword. The pointy end goes into the bad guys. How hard can it be to use?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_12</Key>
    <Value>Hey...[PlayerName]? While we're back here in the Chersonese... There's &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;somewhere I want to go&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. I'd feel better if you came along.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_a_12</Key>
    <Value>I don't have time for side trips, Roland. We're going back to Berg.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_13</Key>
    <Value>Alright, fine. Maybe I'll come back some other time, if I survive all this.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_b_12</Key>
    <Value>As long as it's not far.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_15</Key>
    <Value>When we were kids, Yzan and I went into the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Starfish cave on the beach near Cierzo&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. I... lost something there. Something that belonged to my father.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_a_15</Key>
    <Value>I'm not taking a detour for us to pick up an old trinket. We have work to do!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_16</Key>
    <Value>I suppose... It probably got destroyed or stolen years ago anyway. I’ll head back to Berg and to report to Gabriella, then.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_b_15</Key>
    <Value>Sure, why not. It's not that far out of the way.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_17</Key>
    <Value>Really? Thanks, [PlayerName]. It means a lot to me. The cave I'm talking about is the one right &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;near Cierzo's back door, on the beach where the tunnel from the storage tunnel comes out.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_18</Key>
    <Value>Gahh... I’ve made a terrible mistake... I gave up so much of my life to the Ley Line that my body is as frail as a spiderweb. I'll never shake this Blood Price. I'll never amount to anything.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_a_18</Key>
    <Value>What are you going to do about it? Just whine? Or are you going to actually try?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_19</Key>
    <Value>You're right. I have either get good or die trying. All I can do is just push ahead.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_b_18</Key>
    <Value>Roland, get your chin up. There's always hope if you keep at it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_20</Key>
    <Value>Oh, right. Hope. The little carrot you dangle in front of a horse to make it keep going. Life's already beaten me with the damn stick, why should I care about the stupid carrot? </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_a_19</Key>
    <Value>So, what was it we were looking for?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_21</Key>
    <Value>It's my dad's old compass. Yzan and I took it when we were kids to run around outside. You can imagine how that ended up. Stupid shrimp would’ve killed us if it wasn't for that old gate warden saving us. It's all I have left to remember my dad by.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_a_21</Key>
    <Value>I can see why you'd come back for this.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_22</Key>
    <Value>Thanks for helping me find it again, [PlayerName]. I won't forget this.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_b_21</Key>
    <Value>It looks broken, it’s probably not even worth 10 silvers.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_23</Key>
    <Value>Yeah, but to me it's worth a lot more than that. Thanks for helping me find it again.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_24</Key>
    <Value>I'm going to go report to Gabriella once I’ve caught my breath. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;I'll see you back in Berg&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, [PlayerName].</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_25</Key>
    <Value>Gabriella chewed me out over letting a rock mantis get the better of me. I should really pay more attention to my surroundings.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_26</Key>
    <Value>There's no way I'm ready to take down a shell horror! Those things are massive! I don't know how to work my Mana yet either...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_a_26</Key>
    <Value>I’m not prepared either. I need to take some time to get ready for this.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_27</Key>
    <Value>Yeah, great minds think alike. I’m going to keep training too.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_b_26</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_28</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_a_28</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_29</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_a_29</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_30</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_b_29</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_31</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_c_26</Key>
    <Value>What's wrong with your Mana? You're able to summon that sword just fine.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_32</Key>
    <Value>Yes, but... it bends a lot while I have it out. And it feels blunt half the time I swing it. My Mana reserves are huge, but I can’t seem to focus them properly.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_a_32</Key>
    <Value>I wonder... Maybe we can find someone to make you a tool that makes it easier to focus that thing?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_34</Key>
    <Value>I'm sure there's &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;a smith somewhere in this city&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; skilled enough. Could you ask him for me?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_d_26</Key>
    <Value>It’s time to kill that green horror! Meet me at the Cabal of Winds Temple.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_36</Key>
    <Value>Right. We'll never know unless we try. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;See you at the old temple&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. You’ve seen it, right? It’s that &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;large ruin on top of the mountain in Enmerkar&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_37</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_a_37</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_35</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_b_37</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_39</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_40</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_44</Key>
    <Value>We did it. We killed a damn shell horror! And I’m not dead!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_a_44</Key>
    <Value>You carried your weight there. Good work.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_45</Key>
    <Value>For the first time in my life, it really feels like I did. Thanks for everything, [PlayerName]. Let's &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;rip a trophy off this thing and show Gabriella&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, eh?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_b_44</Key>
    <Value>What do you mean "we"? I did all the work!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_46</Key>
    <Value>I... I guess you did, didn't you. I'm sorry. I shouldn't have... Let's just go &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;report this to Gabriella&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; and get on with stopping whatever is going on.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_46_B</Key>
    <Value>You’re the one who really handled that fight. You should be the one to report on all the juicy details.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_47</Key>
    <Value>I can't talk. I need to pay attention and make sure no more ghosts sneak up on Gabriella! </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_48</Key>
    <Value>Thank Elatt you made it. I really don't like the look of this mess. She already added her entire spirit to the Ancestral Memories. They're in agony! Can you hear them? Can you see them?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_a_48</Key>
    <Value>No, Roland, I can't. How bad is it?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_49</Key>
    <Value>Really? You can't see it? The Ancestral Memories are in a frenzied storm around that altar, and there's this huge streak of red winding around it...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_50</Key>
    <Value>Looks like we caught it early enough. That woman's spirit is still being resisted by the rest of the memories. We might be able to do something about this.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_51</Key>
    <Value>She's already done serious damage to them. So many of the Memories are tainted with red... It's hard to tell where she ends and where the Ancestral Memories begin.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_52</Key>
    <Value>I think... I think I might be able to use my mana sword to cut her spirit out of that mess. It's risky but if I jam the blade in just the right spot, we have a chance.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_52-b</Key>
    <Value>Stand back! Once I start cutting, memories and ghosts will start pouring out of that storm!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_a_52</Key>
    <Value>But you're going to get caught in that!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_53</Key>
    <Value>Yeah, I am... but I don't see any other option. Rissa said if we lose these Ancestral Memories, the whole Collective will suffer.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_a_53</Key>
    <Value>Are you sure you can handle this?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_b_52</Key>
    <Value>Oh great. Don't mess this up, Roland.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_54</Key>
    <Value>Yeah. Yeah, I'm sure. I can handle this. I know exactly what I have to do. Now stand back, and let me work.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_55</Key>
    <Value>I'm not sure... but it's the best shot we've got. Stand back. Here goes nothing.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_56</Key>
    <Value>(Roland stares ahead, empty and cold. His spirit has almost completely left his body, and it is starting to shut down.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_57</Key>
    <Value>(The Trinket you made for him falls from his hand, blazing with fragments of Roland’s soul. It burns at the touch, so you place it inside a fallen lantern for safekeeping)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_57-b</Key>
    <Value>(The Trinket glows steadily within the lantern...You feel safer with it around, almost like what’s left of Roland’s soul is trying to protect you from harm.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_58</Key>
    <Value>(With a jerk of a motion, he grips your arm, and then falls to the ground. He succeeded at his task, at the cost of his life...)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_59</Key>
    <Value>Honestly, I don't care. If we don't do something, this could destroy Berg. It could destroy the entire Collective. Even if I can't handle it, I have to try.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_60</Key>
    <Value>I... am... We are... I am Jarinda. I am... Why am I in this... body?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_61</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName]... I have her... I have her... I can't hold... Her here forever... &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Kill her&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;... Before she...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_62</Key>
    <Value>I will not... allow it! I must endure! I must survive! </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_63</Key>
    <Value>(As Roland plants his mana sword into the air around the altar, a violent burst of blue energy blinds you. Then, a woman’s scream breaks the air, and red energy rushes past you)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_64</Key>
    <Value>(As the brilliant light fades, Roland remains, his eyes glowing with a strange, fey light.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_65</Key>
    <Value>I’m sorry that I didn’t help you, I just... I couldn’t... I was scared, alright? There, I said it! I’m sorry! Let’s just... Let’s just go report to Gabriella.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_a_65</Key>
    <Value>You wouldn’t have been any help anyway. Go home, Roland, you’re not cut out for this stuff.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Bones_b_65</Key>
    <Value>It happens. Don’t let it get to you. Just do better next time. I’ll see you in Berg, yeah?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_66</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_67</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Bones_68</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_01</Key>
    <Value>Roland told me how you bailed him out at the Conflux Mountain. I'm glad Rissa sent you. At least one of you knows what they're doing. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_01_B</Key>
    <Value>If you want me to accept this, you need to prove you can handle a serious fight. I need you to prove you can stare death in the face and come out on top.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_02</Key>
    <Value>There's an &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;old temple&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; that belonged to the Cabal of Winds in Enmerkar that's been a lair for Scourge Beasts since they emerged. The other day I saw a &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;distinctive bright green shell horror&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; enter the place. I want you to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;go kill it&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; for me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Gabriella_BC_Bones_a_02</Key>
    <Value>You want us to slay a shell horror? Are you trying to kill us?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_03</Key>
    <Value>If you can't handle it, I don't see how you could handle anything the Scarlet Lady will throw at us. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Gabriella_BC_Bones_b_02</Key>
    <Value>Green shell horror, kill it. Got it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_04</Key>
    <Value>Have you even fought one before? You're either foolishly overconfident, or you've been up to things even I haven't heard about. I hope for your sake it's not the former.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_05</Key>
    <Value>The Temple is up &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;on the mountain in the South-West&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; of Enmerkar forest. You will know it when you see it. Come back here when that monster is dead. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Don’t forget to take Roland with you&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, he’s being tested too.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_06</Key>
    <Value>Did you kill that green horror yet?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Gabriella_BC_Bones_a_06</Key>
    <Value>Not yet. We’re working on it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_07</Key>
    <Value>Well, get on it already. You’re wasting my precious investigation time!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Gabriella_BC_Bones_b_06</Key>
    <Value>Yes, the monster is dead.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_08</Key>
    <Value>Really? Did you bring back proof?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Gabriella_BC_Bones_a_08</Key>
    <Value>Uhh... No... I must have lost it...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_09</Key>
    <Value>You couldn't have brought back a chunk of the monster? Fine. I'll go check, myself. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;I'll be back in about two days&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_10</Key>
    <Value>Well, I've confirmed that thing is dead. Pretty solid work, for both of you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Gabriella_BC_Bones_b_08</Key>
    <Value>Yeah, here’s a piece of its chitin. Is this enough to convince you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_11</Key>
    <Value>Hmm... Yes, this is from that monster alright, I can smell the blood on it. You must have done a bang up job on the thing.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_12</Key>
    <Value>Well, I'm satisfied that you know how to handle yourselves. I'll initiate you both the moment you're ready. The sooner both of you are connected with the Ancestral Memories, the better.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_13</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName], can you go &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;fetch Julius&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;? I'll need an experienced Krypteia mage for this. In the meantime, Roland, come with me. We're going to the Necropolis to prepare for the initiation.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Gabriella_BC_Bones_a_13</Key>
    <Value>Do you know where I can find him?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_14</Key>
    <Value>Julius has been &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;staying at the inn&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; during his investigation, if you can’t find him out and about, he’ll probably be there. Ask around.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_15</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName]! Thank the Ancestors! We're in a bad spot right now! Did you find Julius?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Gabriella_BC_Bones_a_15</Key>
    <Value>He’s dead. He tried to shank Sagard Battleborn on account of a girl in red who said she really needed to get into the Necropolis, or her mistress would kill her.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_16</Key>
    <Value>Lovely. I can see where that story is going. The damn fool let himself be manipulated by the enemy. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Gabriella_BC_Bones_a_16</Key>
    <Value>What happened to you two? You’re injured.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_17</Key>
    <Value>As soon as we got this far, ghosts started pouring out from the bottom of the necropolis. I think they're remnants that frayed off the Ancestral Memories. That damned Lich worshipper must have already started to corrupt them. I got taken by surprise... If it wasn't for Roland...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Gabriella_BC_Bones_a_17</Key>
    <Value>Wait, Roland saved you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_18</Key>
    <Value>It turns out he's got a knack for ghosts and spirits. He sensed them coming and drove them off.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Gabriella_BC_Bones_b_17</Key>
    <Value>Are you going to make it?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_19</Key>
    <Value>The injury isn't fatal but I won't be lifting a sword for a while. I'm going to have to count on you and Roland to stop her.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_20</Key>
    <Value>The ghosts are in a blind fury and sealed the way deeper. I need you to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;find the Altars for the Sutherland and Aberdeen families and make an offering there&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. If you burn some &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Greasy Fern&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; at those altars, it should calm the ghosts down enough that they'll recognize us.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_21</Key>
    <Value>Good work on the barrier, [PlayerName]. Roland went up ahead to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;deal with the altar and our unwelcome guest&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Go catch up with him and stop her!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Gabriella_BC_Bones_a_21</Key>
    <Value>You're injured! What happens if a ghost comes after you when no one is here to back you up?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_22</Key>
    <Value>I don't matter. But that altar, and the memories within? If they aren't cleansed of the Scarlet Lady's influence, the Collective and everyone in it will suffer greatly. Go!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_23</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_24</Key>
    <Value>If you don’t have any, scour the Necropolis. We use &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Greasy Fern&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; when communing with the ancestors, so there should be enough here.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_25</Key>
    <Value>Stay safe out there [PlayerName]. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_26</Key>
    <Value>Don’t worry about me, [PlayerName]. I’ll be out hunting again before you know it. If anything, I’m just upset Rissa didn’t see Julius’s betrayal coming. I think it’s time for her to retire as leader of the Krypteia!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Bones_27</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Taleron_BC_Bones_01</Key>
    <Value>You look like something is bothering you. Is it something a master smith can deal with?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Taleron_BC_Bones_a_01</Key>
    <Value>Maybe. Someone I know needs a tool or something that lets him better focus his Mana. Can you help?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Taleron_BC_Bones_02</Key>
    <Value>Focus mana, you say... Oh, you must mean Roland! He was here the other day, showing me that magic blade of his. Hmmm... Yes, I think &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;I could make a trinket&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; of some kind…</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Taleron_BC_Bones_03</Key>
    <Value>I'll need either an &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Emerald or Ruby&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, as well as some &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Blue Sand&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; and a &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mana stone&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Bring them here and I'll craft that trinket.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Taleron_BC_Bones_a_03</Key>
    <Value>I’m still looking for the materials you need. I’ll be back.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Taleron_BC_Bones_04</Key>
    <Value>I got you the materials you need for Roland's trinket.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Taleron_BC_Bones_05</Key>
    <Value>Yes, I think this is all I'll need, give me some time.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Taleron_BC_Bones_06</Key>
    <Value>HAH! It was tricky work, but I think this should do nicely. All Roland will have to do is clutch this trinket in his palm, and channel that blade through it, and it should always be sharp and solid.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Taleron_BC_Bones_a_06</Key>
    <Value>Do I owe you anything for this?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Taleron_BC_Bones_07</Key>
    <Value>It's on the house. It's not every day I get such an obscure request that lets me really try something new and exciting. Besides, I feel like the lad needs it. He’s got a lot of heart, but not the focus to use it. I want to see what happens when he can truly put his mind to a task.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Taleron_BC_Bones_08</Key>
    <Value>I'll make sure this gets to Roland. I’ll send a courier. He’ll bring the trinket to Roland within the hour.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Taleron_BC_Bones_09</Key>
    <Value>Greetings, friend. If you’re looking for quality equipment, I have you covered. I’ve forged just about everything this place has to offer.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Taleron_BC_Bones_10</Key>
    <Value>Did you find me the materials I need? Remember, I need &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Blue Sand&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, a &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mana Stone&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; and either an &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Emerald or a Ruby&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; to craft that trinket for Roland.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Taleron_BC_Bones_11</Key>
    <Value>Ah, you look like you’ve found all the materials I need for Roland’s tool. I’ll take them and I’ll get right to work.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Taleron_BC_Bones_a_11</Key>
    <Value>Here you go. Work your magic, Taleron.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Taleron_BC_Bones_b_11</Key>
    <Value>Not just yet. I’ll be back.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Taleron_BC_Bones_12</Key>
    <Value>Alright, I'll get started right away. Should I work with an Emerald or a Ruby?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Taleron_BC_Bones_a_12</Key>
    <Value>Use a Ruby.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Taleron_BC_Bones_a_13</Key>
    <Value>Use an Emerald.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_Bones_01</Key>
    <Value>Oy, you! Yes, you! Go fetch Rissa! One of her idiots just tried to stab me!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Sagard_BC_Bones_a_01</Key>
    <Value>Is that Julius's corpse behind you? What happened here?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_Bones_02</Key>
    <Value>He was talking with a girl in red, and it turned into an argument. She was telling him that there was something she needed to do, and he was refusing, telling her that he wouldn't let her "throw her life away".</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_Bones_03</Key>
    <Value>That's when your friend over there decided to try to take me with a dagger, and the girl grabbed something off his belt and bolted for the door!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Sagard_BC_Bones_a_03</Key>
    <Value>Julius, you idiot. This sounds like the oldest story in the book.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_Bones_04</Key>
    <Value>What are you blabbering about? One of Rissa’s goons tries to murder me and you’re concerned about the girl that ran instead?!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Sagard_BC_Bones_a_04</Key>
    <Value>You'll have to go get Rissa yourself. I need to catch up with that woman before she breaks something important in the necropolis.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_Bones_05</Key>
    <Value>Seriously, what is going on in my damn city?! Why is no one giving me a damn straight answer?!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_Bones_06</Key>
    <Value>Then she said &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;"If I don't get into that necropolis, my mistress will kill me"&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, and I decided it might be a good idea to ask them a few questions.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_Bones_07</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_Bones_08</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_Bones_09</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_Bones_10</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_Bones_11</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_01</Key>
    <Value>I... I... We... We are Whispering Bones. We thank you for saving us.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_a_01</Key>
    <Value>Roland? Are... you still in there?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_02</Key>
    <Value>Fear not, [PlayerName]. Roland is with us. He has saved us, and now he is one of us. We can show you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_a_02</Key>
    <Value>(A vision fills your sight. You see ghostly shapes swirling in a large, slow vortex. Roland is at the center, grinning. He seems satisfied.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_03</Key>
    <Value>As you can see, your companion is part of us now. Together, we will safeguard the Memories.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_a_03</Key>
    <Value>What are you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_04</Key>
    <Value>We are a Lich. We are Whispering Bones. We are the guardian of the Ancestral Memories. We will gladly work for the good of the Collective.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_b_03</Key>
    <Value>And I’m supposed to trust that? You’re a freakish monster that just took over someone’s body!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_05</Key>
    <Value>Roland offered his body freely to us. We just wish to continue serving the Collective, even if our appearance upsets you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_06</Key>
    <Value>We can grant you a boon. We have the knowledge of the most ancient of ancestors, we are the living history of the Collective. Please, tell us how we can help you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_a_06</Key>
    <Value>I want to expand my Mana.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_07</Key>
    <Value>Easily done. Close your eyes, and we shall share the memories of our greatest mage. He will show you how to tap into your hidden reservoirs of will.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_b_06</Key>
    <Value>I want to be better protected from harm.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_08</Key>
    <Value>We can grant this. We shall place a spirit within a lantern for you and fill it with the desire to protect you. So long as you hold it aloft, harm from magic or elements of all kinds will be reduced. Ghosts will find it especially hard to harm you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_c_06</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_09</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_10</Key>
    <Value>Is this boon acceptable?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_a_10</Key>
    <Value>Yes, It’s acceptable.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_11</Key>
    <Value>Then so it shall be.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_b_10</Key>
    <Value>No, I want something else.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_12</Key>
    <Value>Then choose, [PlayerName].</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_a_12</Key>
    <Value>(Memories of a great mage flow into you. You gain intimate knowledge of the wells of power within you.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_b_12</Key>
    <Value>(The Lich conjures a brilliant flame and gently places it into a Lantern. The spirit within will ward magical and ghostly harm away from you.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_c_12</Key>
    <Value>(You feel something bubble within you... A protective force... A caring sensation...You feel like something is looking after you...)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_13</Key>
    <Value>We hope you are pleased by the boon we have granted. You and the Krypteia are always welcome to speak with me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_14</Key>
    <Value>We have much to do, and think, and remember. Please, do not bother us at this moment, it is... difficult for us to get used to our new life. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Perhaps another time&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; we can help you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_15</Key>
    <Value>We welcome you, [PlayerName]. Is there something we can do for you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_a_15</Key>
    <Value>You’re one with the ancestral memories, what can you teach me?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_16</Key>
    <Value>Hmm... An exchange. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bring us Blue Sand&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, that we may extract memories from them and add them to our own, and we shall gift you with knowledge.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_a_16</Key>
    <Value>Here’s some Blue Sand. What can you teach me?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_17</Key>
    <Value>You probably already know that you can use a Spark spell to ignite the air in a Sigil of Wind... but these new Levantin firearms... they are like a Spark as well... It may work just as well. There may be more ways to use Magic in this kind of manner.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_18</Key>
    <Value>There is a spirit trapped in a grave in the valley beyond the Ghost Pass in the Chersonese. Give him what he needs to move on, and perhaps he will share his treasure with you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_19</Key>
    <Value>I see... Tsar Stones shining throughout Aurai. Their locations are hidden from my sight, but I can tell you this: There are not enough Tsar Stones in Aurai to forge a full set of armor within a single lifetime...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_20</Key>
    <Value>I see... an interesting chest that the Scarlet Lady has hidden in Enmerkar, beneath the Vigil crystal. Ignore the wooden chest and seek the lever behind it, then seek a path forward. That chest you will find and the treasure within will surely stand the test of time.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_21</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Bone_Lich_BC_Bones_22</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Altar_BC_Bones_01</Key>
    <Value>(The spirits bound to this altar are terribly agitated. Only a burnt offering of Greasy Fern will let you calm them down.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Altar_BC_Bones_02</Key>
    <Value>(The spirits finally recognize you and lower their guard.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Altar_BC_Bones_03</Key>
    <Value>(You sense no hostility coming from this altar. This family will not prevent you from entering the depths of the Necropolis)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Altar_BC_Bones_04</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ConfluxGuard_BC_Bones_01</Key>
    <Value>Welcome. This is the path to the Chersonese Ley Line that the Blue Chamber Collective maintains. If you seek the power of magic, make your way through it to the end, and speak to the Watchers at the heart of the mountain.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_ConfluxGuard_BC_Bones_a_01</Key>
    <Value>I’m looking for someone who came this way. He’s a Tramontane man, kinda clumsy?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_ConfluxGuard_BC_Bones_b_01</Key>
    <Value>Is it dangerous?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ConfluxGuard_BC_Bones_02</Key>
    <Value>Yes, indeed. The path ahead is a labyrinth, and you may easily find yourself lost. But, there are markers to guide you. Those who pay heed to the wisdom of the Blue Chamber’s ancestors will have little trouble navigating these halls.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ConfluxGuard_BC_Bones_03</Key>
    <Value>There are also a great number of Troglodytes that make their home here, many of whom have swallowed mana stones and been transformed into shamans of their kind. Be on your guard.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ConfluxGuard_BC_Bones_04</Key>
    <Value>Yes, he was just by here a moment ago. The damn fool took a wrong &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;turn to the left&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; almost immediately without even his sword drawn. There’s a damn &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;rock mantis nest&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; that way, and he blundered right towards it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ConfluxGuard_BC_Bones_05</Key>
    <Value>I can only hope he’s less careless than he looks, or he might already be that thing’s dinner. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ConfluxGuard_BC_Bones_06</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ConfluxGuard_BC_Bones_07</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_01</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName], the situation between us and Levant has just shifted. The war is coming to a close.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_01</Key>
    <Value>The war is ending? What happened?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_02</Key>
    <Value>The Holy Mission just sent a messenger. Elatt demands peace. A truce has just been declared. We will negotiate with Levant once we’ve &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;gotten the rest of the Chamberlords to agree&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; to peace talks.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_02</Key>
    <Value>Good, the war’s gone on long enough.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_03</Key>
    <Value>I agree. Levant doesn't bother taking many prisoners. If the war keeps going, there won’t be anyone left to enjoy the peace!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_b_02</Key>
    <Value>What?! But we're finally winning!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_04</Key>
    <Value>You speak like Sagard! The war was only meant to be defensive. Punishing them all for the attack on Berg will only lead to more violence.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_c_02</Key>
    <Value>Why should we obey him? Levant struck first, remember?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_05</Key>
    <Value>Maybe you'd like to be the one to tell a god that you disagree with ending the war? The messenger said Elatt "demanded" peace, understand?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_06</Key>
    <Value>I'll convince the main families to comply but there’s a few that I'll need you to deal with. Please, [PlayerName], try to use some tact here.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_07</Key>
    <Value>First, I need you to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;talk to Sagard Battleborn&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. He is aggressively opposed to peace with Levant and unless we deal with him, he’ll ignite another war on his own. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Make him call off our soldiers by any means necessary&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_08</Key>
    <Value>Then, there's the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Montcalm tribe in the North of the Chersonese&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, near the Ghost Pass. With the truce, they have suspended hostilities against other tribes for the time being. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Speak with their Chamberlord, Rastarte&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, and convince him to support the peace with Levant.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_09</Key>
    <Value>Finally, you have the most experience &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;dealing&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; with the Ash Giants. You should be the one to convince them to accept peace negotiations. You might want to speak with them last, as they’re the closest to Monsoon.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_09</Key>
    <Value>Why can't you handle these people?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_10</Key>
    <Value>Because Sagard won't listen to anyone who’s not a hardened warrior, and he's still furious at me over what happened with Julius. You'll have a better chance at changing his mind than l will.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_11</Key>
    <Value>And the Montcalm tribe still wants my head after I learned the Scarlet Lady had a pawn in their tribe. If Gabriella or I showed our faces there, they'd kill us on the spot.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_b_09</Key>
    <Value>Alright, I'll get on this.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_12</Key>
    <Value>Be wary around the Montcalm tribe. Our scouts said they hang enemies around their encampment, and that undead rise from tunnels beyond the Ghost Pass to feed on them.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_13</Key>
    <Value>&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;When you’ve convinced all of them to agree to the negotiations, meet me at Elatt's temple in Monsoon&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_c_09</Key>
    <Value>I can’t do this at the moment.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_14</Key>
    <Value>I can’t see what could be more important than this. Please finish your business quickly!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_15</Key>
    <Value>Remember, [PlayerName], you need to deal with Sagard here in Berg, and the Montcalm tribe in the North of the Chersonese. Finally make your way Monsoon in the Hallowed Marsh.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_16</Key>
    <Value>While you're in the Hallowed Marsh, make sure you &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;get the Ash Giants to agree to with the peace talks as well&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_17</Key>
    <Value>You're late! Negotiations were supposed to start already! At least tell me everything went well on your end!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_18</Key>
    <Value>You're right on time, [PlayerName]! Tell me, how did it go?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_18</Key>
    <Value>I got Sagard to agree to pull back his armies. He won't cause any more trouble.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_19</Key>
    <Value>Thank the ancestors. I don't know what you had to do to change his mind, but it can't have been an easy!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_b_18</Key>
    <Value>I couldn't convince Sagard. Is seems he's gone rogue with a large detachment of our army.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_20</Key>
    <Value>So, we face civil war... I can only hope his fear of Elatt will keep him from declaring war against Levant again. At least he abandoned his position. He won’t have the the political power he once held.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_21</Key>
    <Value>And the Montcalm clan? Did you speak with Rastarte?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_21</Key>
    <Value>They accept peace, but they'll need soldiers to protect them. They’ve been offering tribute to the undead from beyond the Ghost Pass for protection. The spirits will attack them once the offerings stop coming.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_22</Key>
    <Value>I'll see to it that they get the protection they need. I'm amazed you succeeded, [PlayerName]. I’d almost given up hope!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_b_21</Key>
    <Value>No luck. Their grudge is strong enough that they'd rather abandon us to worship ghosts as their protectors.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_23</Key>
    <Value>Then our feud with them can’t get any worse. If they acquired a legion of ghosts, we won’t be able to drive them out of the Chersonese to protect Cierzo from their raids.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_24</Key>
    <Value>And the Ash Giants? Did you manage to pacify them?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_24</Key>
    <Value>The Ashborn are eager for peace. They’re glad to return to working silk and porcelain without dealing with human conflicts.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_25</Key>
    <Value>I'm surprised. I would have expected them to be difficult to convince... I shouldn't have judged so quickly. They’re proving to be quite helpful to our cause.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_26</Key>
    <Value>Negotiations are beginning, and I’ll need you with me. The situation is very delicate. There was a coup in Levant. Queen Calixa was even poisoned! She's conscious for now, but I don't know how long it will last. I need backup if disaster strikes.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_26</Key>
    <Value>What in Ellat’s name happened there?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_27</Key>
    <Value>I don’t know, but she was exposed to an unknown toxin. A healer from the Holy Mission gave her antidotes but he said it can only postpone the inevitable. Our peace talk must happen now, or never.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_28</Key>
    <Value>I’ve been communing daily with the Ancestral Memories regarding the war with Levant. Come back in a few days, maybe we’ll have something by then.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_29</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_30</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_ANC_PEACE_31</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_ANC_PEACE_01</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_ANC_PEACE_02</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_ANC_PEACE_03</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_ANC_PEACE_04</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_ANC_PEACE_05</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_ANC_PEACE_06</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_ANC_PEACE_07</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_ANC_PEACE_08</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_01</Key>
    <Value>So, the little mouse from Cierzo sends her toy soldier to speak with me. I refuse to make peace with Levant. Not until we’ve broken their armies and replaced their king and queen with a lord loyal to the Blue Chamber.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_01</Key>
    <Value>I'll make you change your mind, believe me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_02</Key>
    <Value>Hah, I doubt that very much.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_b_01</Key>
    <Value>You owe me a favor, Sagard. I'm here to collect.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_03</Key>
    <Value>What? You think one measly personal favor is worth ending a war? Have you lost your senses, pup?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_03</Key>
    <Value>Do you really want everyone in the Collective to know that you don't honor your word, Sagard?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_04</Key>
    <Value>You’d attack me with words and not steel? Fine. My reputation means too much to me to stain it over this. I’ll call off my soldiers. But when Levant attacks again, everyone will remember that I was right to fear them!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_c_01</Key>
    <Value>(Hold out a Tsar Stone)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_05</Key>
    <Value>That's a Tsar Stone! With just two more of those, I could make armor that could deflect even a Manticore’s strikes! Don't you dare tempt me, pup!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_05</Key>
    <Value>It's yours if you call off your armies.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_06</Key>
    <Value>Damn you, [PlayerName]. A gem like this is worth any price. Fine. I'll call off my soldiers. You win. Now hand it over!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_b_05</Key>
    <Value>I just wanted to see your reaction.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_07</Key>
    <Value>Well,you’ve seen it. Satisfied? You know how priceless that gem is, don't you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_d_01</Key>
    <Value>Call off your armies, or I'll call them off for you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_08</Key>
    <Value>Is that a threat? Do you know what you're starting, you little weasel?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_08</Key>
    <Value>On second thought, never mind.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_09</Key>
    <Value>Smart choice, pup.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_b_08</Key>
    <Value>Oh, is the great Sagard Battleborn too pathetic to fight one puny little person?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_10</Key>
    <Value>You’ve just made a terrible mistake. I’ll enjoy breaking every bone in your body, weasel!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_11</Key>
    <Value>I don't believe it. How in Elatt's name did you beat me?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_11</Key>
    <Value>Call off your armies or this’ll be your last fight, Sagard!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_12</Key>
    <Value>You wouldn't dare kill me. You wouldn't bring such shame to the Aberdeen name!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_12</Key>
    <Value>I don't need to. I’ll just break enough of your bones to put an end to your career, miserable old man!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_b_12</Key>
    <Value>Your actions put the entire Collective in harm's way. I think it'd be worth it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_c_12</Key>
    <Value>If it means I’ll be known as the one who took down Sagard Battleborn? Very tempting.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_13</Key>
    <Value>You fight dirty, [PlayerName]. I respect that. I'll call off my armies. But mark my words, I’ll be proven right one day. The kingdom of Levant can never be trusted.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_14</Key>
    <Value>You fight well. You should’ve been on the front lines. You'd really have made a difference out there.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_15</Key>
    <Value>I don’t believe this. I can’t believe this. We let Levant gain a goddess? How could Rissa let that happen?! This will be our doom, mark my words. Mark. My. Words.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_16</Key>
    <Value>(You don’t have a Tsar Stone to offer)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_17</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_18</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_19</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_20</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_21</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_22</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_23</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_ANC_PEACE_24</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_01</Key>
    <Value>Why does someone from Cierzo dare come here? Be thankful we have a truce. We have nothing but hatred for your people after what you've done to us.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_01</Key>
    <Value>I need you to agree to the peace talks with Levant.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_02</Key>
    <Value>Why should we? Did the Blue Chamber consult us before going to war? Did they care when one of our own was poisoned? We know it was Rissa’s doing. The ghosts from the tunnels told us. They tell us everything, they keep us safe.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_03</Key>
    <Value>They tell us that Levant burns the eastern tribes. That the Blue Chamber suffers. I say good. We want them to burn until they understand what it's like to lose those you care for.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_03</Key>
    <Value>Your personal feud with Rissa is no reason to harm the rest of the tribes.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_04</Key>
    <Value>One of our people was murdered by your Chamberlady and nothing was done about it. The Blue Chamber Collective is supposed to be family, but when they attack us, they want us to pretend it was a tragic accident. How are we supposed to accept that?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_05</Key>
    <Value>It’s much safer to entrust our fate to the ghosts. They are devoid of ambition or deceit. As long as we offer them life to drink, they have no reason to turn on us.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_05</Key>
    <Value>You'd trust undead over living, breathing people? They’re monsters. They have no conscience!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_06</Key>
    <Value>Neither do the leaders of the Blue Chamber. At least the undead are honest about what they want. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_b_05</Key>
    <Value>You've enslaved yourselves. You talk about offering them life, while accusing us of murder. How many did you sacrifice to the undead?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_07</Key>
    <Value>Anyone who trespasses here forfeits their life. We've taken people from other tribes in raids too. Whatever amount it takes to satisfy the needs of our guardians.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_07</Key>
    <Value>So rather than trade one life for the safety of the whole collective, you'd rather trade everyone’s lives for some ghosts to protect you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_08</Key>
    <Value>You... You can't understand. Estelle was the heart of this tribe. Her songs brought joy and hope to us. How could her life be worth less than anyone else's?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_b_08</Key>
    <Value>And every corpse you hang out there to feed the ghosts? Couldn't they be the heart of another tribe?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_09</Key>
    <Value>Good. Then they'll understand our suffering, they’ll understand that everything the Blue Chamber promises is a lie. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_08</Key>
    <Value>And what happens when you aren't able to satisfy the ghosts with those you've kidnapped? Will you sacrifice your own people to feed them?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_10</Key>
    <Value>If that’s what we have to do to protect our tribe from needless deaths at the hands of the others, yes!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_10</Key>
    <Value>Think about what you said. To protect your people from needlessly dying, you're going to sacrifice your people yourself! Do you see the problem with that logic?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_11</Key>
    <Value>... I can't refute that. We can't put our fates in the undead if their hunger grows out of control. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;We agree to declare peace with Levant&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, but you must get the Chamberlords to send us help. The ghosts will come devour us if we stop feeding them.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_b_03</Key>
    <Value>You do know that if Levant’s army reaches your tribe, they'll burn you to the ground, right? A few ghosts won’t protect you from an army bristling with firearms.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_12</Key>
    <Value>You're trying to scare us. Why would Levant attack us? We haven't raised our weapons against them.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_12</Key>
    <Value>They need supplies, and you belong to their enemy. They don’t care about the details of your feud with Cierzo! They’ll destroy your tribe and pillage your lands.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_13</Key>
    <Value>We welcome them to try. Our guardians will feast on Levant's soldiers if they dare set foot on our land.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_b_12</Key>
    <Value>Even if they pass you over, they'll lay waste to all the surrounding tribes. Where are you going to get your tribute for the ghosts then? Your own people?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_b_13</Key>
    <Value>And you think the ghosts will protect you when Levant comes? They feed on life. They’ll let everyone kill each other and feast on the carnage!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_14</Key>
    <Value>That would be foolish of them. One banquet of lost lives is nowhere near as useful to them as regular tributes…</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_13</Key>
    <Value>Undead are addicted to whatever life they can get steal. Even if they wiped out Levant’s army, they’d be so high on stolen life that they’d attack you out of instinct.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_11</Key>
    <Value>I'll make sure you get the help you need.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_15</Key>
    <Value>Good. If you send us an army for protection, maybe, just maybe, we'll consider putting an end to our raids on other tribes. You had better come through, you hear me?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_16</Key>
    <Value>No, &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;we won’t negotiate for the Blue Chamber&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Scourge take you! Scourge take all the tribes! We don’t need them any longer. Leave now! Our truce is over! If you set foot in our lands again, you’ll be one more sacrifice for our guardians!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_17</Key>
    <Value>Begone from here! My patience has its limits, Cierzo scum.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ramza_BC_ANC_PEACE_18</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_ANC_PEACE_01</Key>
    <Value>Haloo, my ally. The war goes well. The desert people are no match for us!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyr_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_01</Key>
    <Value>I need you to help with negotiations, we’re going make peace with them. Please, come to Monsoon to settle this conflict.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_ANC_PEACE_02</Key>
    <Value>Oh? Peacetime already? This is...AHA! I know. Ashborn kick them down so hard they come begging for peace, is that it? This good thing. Giants think war with puny desert men is good sport, but we eager to get back to crafts and silks.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_ANC_PEACE_03</Key>
    <Value>&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;We accept peace&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Hmm... I want you to speak for us. You very good speaker. You represent us well, yes? Cyr would come, but Monsoon is Elatt city. Cyr not want to give Elatt people feeling that they equal to our gods.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_ANC_PEACE_04</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyr_BC_ANC_PEACE_05</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Belly_BC_ANC_PEACE_01</Key>
    <Value>Au, my little friend! What brings you here?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Belly_BC_ANC_PEACE_01</Key>
    <Value>I need the Ashborn to negotiate peace terms with Levant. Do you have a new Highlord yet?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Belly_BC_ANC_PEACE_02</Key>
    <Value>No, not yet. It might be months before we do. But everyone in our village will be &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;glad to have peace&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. War with the desert people is a good sport, but we Ashborn prefer to work in harmony on our crafts.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Belly_BC_ANC_PEACE_03</Key>
    <Value>You should be the one to negotiate for us, I think, if we don't have a Highlord to do it. I will speak with the Highmonk and tell him that the war will be over very soon. Au, I wonder how much the desert people will pay for good Ashborn goods once we have peace!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Belly_BC_ANC_PEACE_04</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Belly_BC_ANC_PEACE_05</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_01</Key>
    <Value>We gather here today under Elatt's eye to bring an end to the hostilities between the Blue Chamber Collective, and the Heroic Kingdom of Levant.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_02</Key>
    <Value>Get on with it. My wife is dying! Elatt promised us he could save her!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_03</Key>
    <Value>Seriously, the Blue Chamber took their sweet-ass time getting ready! How can we be sure that they even want peace?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_04</Key>
    <Value>(A voice like a thunderstorm rolls through everyone’s head. Elatt Himself speaks)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_05</Key>
    <Value>Enough squabbling! Too much blood has been spilled! Sit, and reach a peaceful conclusion like adults!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_06</Key>
    <Value>Are we even discussing terms with the full authority of the Blue Chamber Collective? I hear that your Collective is at each others throats over these talks!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_07</Key>
    <Value>The war broke many tribes. I assure you that the majority of the Collective will punish the minority that refuses peace, if they dare to violate our treaty.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_08</Key>
    <Value>That's not reassuring to me. Any faction opposed to peace, no matter how small, could reignite conflict easily.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_09</Key>
    <Value>Are we even discussing terms with the full authority of the Blue Chamber Collective? I've heard of at least one tribe refusing to even speak about peace with us.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_10</Key>
    <Value>Our current state is none of your concern. Anyone that opposes our treaty will be dealt with severely, I assure you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_11</Key>
    <Value>As long as you can assure us that you can maintain the peace, very well. We will treat this discussion as if it was with the entire Collective.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_12</Key>
    <Value>The entirety of the Blue Chamber collective stands united on this. We wish for an end to the war.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_13</Key>
    <Value>The entirety of the Blue Chamber collective stands united on this. Even the Ash Giants wish for an end to this conflict.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_14</Key>
    <Value>If we are to make peace, we require war reparations for the villages that were destroyed, as well as half your store of firearms and the knowledge to make more.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_15</Key>
    <Value>What, why? You want to cripple us? We need those weapons just to deal with the beasts of Abrassar! Do you expect us to just disarm ourselves and hand over our weapons to the enemy?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_16</Key>
    <Value>We don't want your disarmament. We simply wish to be on equal military footing. It will prevent future conflict.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_17</Key>
    <Value>Should we really arm you, knowing that your people may want revenge for their fallen kin? It’s hard to believe you’re negotiating in good faith, Lady Aberdeen.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_18</Key>
    <Value>Do not forget, Simeon, Levant started this war. Have you dealt with the one behind the attack on our city?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_19</Key>
    <Value>Don't you dare speak about this any further. The mastermind has been dealt with, and I will not bear anyone twisting that knife further!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_20</Key>
    <Value>Simeon, enough. I see their point. We should have been more vigilant. We allowed this war to erupt under our watch. We need to be active to prevent further violence. We will share our weapons with the Blue Chamber.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_21</Key>
    <Value>We need assistance in rebuilding our kingdom. Our food supplies and military are all severely damaged and depleted. We’re barely able to hold Levant together.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_22</Key>
    <Value>If food is what you need, we’ll provide our excess grain freely and see that it makes its way to Levant with all possible speed. In exchange, we want full compliance on your sharing of your firearms.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_23</Key>
    <Value>Good. I may not be long for this world, but I need to know that my kingdom will be left in capable hands.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_24</Key>
    <Value>Hey! Elatt! You said you could save her! Get on with it before she collapses again!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_25</Key>
    <Value>Fear not. Calixa has shown incredible strength of will, and an unwavering commitment to the needs of her people. She has sought progress and improvement with a zeal that rivals any I’ve ever seen.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_26</Key>
    <Value>Not only are these the traits that the Heroic Kingdom needs in order to thrive, but they are the keys to giving Calixa the power to survive her death and truly bring Levantine dream to life, as the newly arisen goddess of Levant.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_27</Key>
    <Value>I... do not understand what you just said. What do you mean you want me to become the "goddess" of Levant?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_28</Key>
    <Value>I will be blunt. The poison you were beset with contained very potent blood from a Scourge Beast. That Corruption still courses through your spirit. Though the poison itself has been cleansed, the Corruption will still claim you, and turn you into something less than human.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_29</Key>
    <Value>In order for you to survive, you must become more than what you are. You must become Living Thought, as I have. And I believe that once you ascend, you will be able to lead your people into prosperity. Not just in your mortal lifetime, but in every lifetime to come.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_30</Key>
    <Value>It is a drastic solution, but it is the only one that ensures the dream of the Heroic Kingdom will continue. Will you take on the mantle of godhood for your people, Calixa?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_31</Key>
    <Value>This...This is rather sudden, but if it's the only way I can continue to serve my people, then yes. I'll give up my humanity if I can keep the Levantine dream alive. What do I need to do?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_32</Key>
    <Value>What? This is beyond insanity, you can't just create a new goddess at the drop of a hat, especially not one who was just recently at war with us! This would destroy any semblance of a balance of power!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_33</Key>
    <Value>To any who wish to object, hold your tongues. I will not see this peace declared, only for Levant to crumble in its execution. This will bring further balance to Aurai. The Blue Chamber has me as their god. Calixa's ascension will only even the scales.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_34</Key>
    <Value>Further, you must understand that even I have my limits. With just one god present in Aurai, the Scourge will never be eradicated, and we will never progress past what we are now. We will never do more than just "survive" if I am the only god humanity can depend on.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_35</Key>
    <Value>Don't you have bigger concerns anyway, Lady Aberdeen? Like that army of ghosts marauding through Enmerkar forest? Don't think we haven't heard about that!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_36</Key>
    <Value>So, this is what Whispering Bones meant when they told me... Very well, I must voice my concerns about this turn of events, but I will not oppose them. The Blue Chamber recognizes and accepts Calixa as the goddess of Levant.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_36_A</Key>
    <Value>I know my place. I cannot argue with a literal god... but please, consider the implications of your actions.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_37</Key>
    <Value>So, are we agreed? Peace will be declared, Queen Calixa will be saved by ascending to divinity, Levant will share their weapons with the Blue Chamber, and they will send food to Levant for the foreseeable future. Is this acceptable to all parties?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_38</Key>
    <Value>I agree to these terms. Simeon?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_39</Key>
    <Value>I can live with these terms. This isn't the peace I want, but it's one I can accept.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_40</Key>
    <Value>I'm not happy about it, but yes, I agree as well. I don't see much room to wiggle here. But don't expect our guns to come cheap, Lady Aberdeen…</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_41</Key>
    <Value>Only if our weapons are shared exclusively with their official armies, and no one else. We're looking to balance the power of our factions, not to arm every mercenary with advanced weaponry.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_42</Key>
    <Value>You don't leave me much choice. I agree to those terms.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_43</Key>
    <Value>Not a chance. If the Blue Chamber wants peace, they'll need to foot the bill for all the men we've lost. If Calixa's life wasn't on the line, I'd be just about ready to flip this table over. You can't ask us to make peace on terms this unfavorable for Levant!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_44</Key>
    <Value>We will pay reparations in silver to Levant every month for twelve seasons, if that's what it takes. However much the Holy Mission deems fair. Will that do?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_45</Key>
    <Value>I can live with that. I can walk away considering this war a victory for us.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_46</Key>
    <Value>I have no choice, then. I don't expect the rest of the Chamber to be happy about these terms. There will be infighting over this for ages to come, but if this is the price of peace... I accept.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_47</Key>
    <Value>Then we’ve reached an agreement. The pact will be sealed with the exchange of gifts and by sharing a drink of Peacemaker's Elixir. Blessed by Elatt, it will grant health and long life to those who’ve worked so hard to obtain peace.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_48</Key>
    <Value>On behalf of the Blue Chamber Collective, I offer the treasure of our ancestors, freely given.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_49</Key>
    <Value>On behalf of the Heroic Kingdom of Levant, I offer an exquisitely cut Tsar Stone, a gemstone of unequalled beauty and power.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_50</Key>
    <Value>And on behalf of the Holy Mission of Elatt, I offer the Peacemaker's Elixir, which grants long life, endurance, and spiritual growth.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_51</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName], you should have this Peacemaker's Elixir. You deserve it. You'll make better use of it than me, I feel.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_51</Key>
    <Value>Thank you. I accept it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_b_51</Key>
    <Value>I think I'd actually prefer the treasure.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_52</Key>
    <Value>I'm fine with that. I have no use for something like that. I'll gladly trade it for your flask of Elixir.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_53</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName], I know of your deeds, and that you toiled long and hard to make this peace happen. I will give you my gift as well.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_53</Key>
    <Value>I’d like the Peacemaker’s Elixir</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_b_53</Key>
    <Value>I’d like the treasure.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_c_53</Key>
    <Value>I’d rather have that Tsar Stone.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_54</Key>
    <Value>May it bring you and your kin long life and prosperity.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_55</Key>
    <Value>Gladly. Use it well.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_56</Key>
    <Value>If that is your desire. May you craft it into something that furthers this peace.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_57</Key>
    <Value>Then Calixa's ascension must begin immediately. Leave the temple and gather your troops. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Prepare to defend the city&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_58</Key>
    <Value>Defend against what?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_59</Key>
    <Value>Yeah, didn't we just agree to peace terms?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_60</Key>
    <Value>The ascension ritual will magnify my presence here. It will attract any Scourge within the entire marsh. In their frenzy they will ignore even the agony caused by the Vigil crystal to attack Monsoon.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_61</Key>
    <Value>I cannot perform the ritual and hold off the Scourge at the same time. I must rely on all of you to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;protect our people&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; until Calixa's ascension is complete.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_62</Key>
    <Value>I bought some soldiers with me. I'll get them ready to fight.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_63</Key>
    <Value>Our troops will do the same. Simeon, for once, you have to be my shield!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_64</Key>
    <Value>I’m going to fight hard enough for both of us, love. You focus on your own ordeal.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_65</Key>
    <Value>Thank you. We will watch over Calixa. She will be safe in our care, I promise you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_66</Key>
    <Value>Monsoon’s safety rests on your shoulders. You all know what you need to do. Now go!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_74</Key>
    <Value>Having my wife speak inside my head like this is... I'm not sure how to feel.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_75</Key>
    <Value>I'm going to miss her at my side... but she's part of me now.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_75</Key>
    <Value>How is she doing?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_76</Key>
    <Value>She’s... adjusting. She says it’s like being a cloud passing through people’s minds. Calixa says she will be fine with her new form, given some time.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_77</Key>
    <Value>She’s also eager to begin her work as the goddess of Progress. Her concern for my safety is all that’s keeping her in the Hallowed Marsh for now. Once we return to Levant, the real work begins.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_78</Key>
    <Value>That was unexpected. I'm glad you came along.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_78</Key>
    <Value>Me too. It's not every day you get to be present for a divine ascension.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_86</Key>
    <Value>History was made here today. This will be the spark that ignites great change across Aurai. We will need to watch this situation closely.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_b_78</Key>
    <Value>After all I’ve been through, I need a vacation and ten barrels of wine.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_79</Key>
    <Value>Granted. You’ve more than done your part here.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_80</Key>
    <Value>You were a real asset out there today, [PlayerName]. I look forward to seeing what path you carve for yourself from here on out.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_81</Key>
    <Value>Your stalwart defense of Monsoon saved lives, [PlayerName]. Also, Simeon asked that I give this gift to you. May it serve you well.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_82</Key>
    <Value>Your defense of Monsoon bought us the time we needed for Calixa’s ascension to be completed. You’ve earned this.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_83</Key>
    <Value>Well done. I must thank you for your aid in defending Monsoon.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_a_83</Key>
    <Value>Are you alright? You don't look well.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_84</Key>
    <Value>Many of us gave a great deal to ensure that the Ascension went smoothly. My health isn't what it used to be... It was quite taxing.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_85</Key>
    <Value>You're free to do as you please, [PlayerName]. I trust your instincts. Do whatever you feel you need to do.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiate_BC_ANC_PEACE_87</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnKeeper_BC_Info_01</Key>
    <Value>Sorry, I haven’t heard any news recently. I’ll keep my ears open, though.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnKeeper_BC_Info_02</Key>
    <Value>I heard that the Chamberlords of the Blue Chamber collective are gathering in Berg for an important Council meeting! People are coming all the way from the Sirocco region for this one!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnKeeper_BC_Info_03</Key>
    <Value>I heard a bomb exploded in the Blue Chamber, and strange mercenaries took hostages and damaged the archives! I hope those fiends are brought to justice!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnKeeper_BC_Info_03-b</Key>
    <Value>Is it true that there was an attempted bomb attack on the Blue Chamber? This is terrible news! I hope they find the ones behind it and make them pay!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnKeeper_BC_Info_04</Key>
    <Value>Hmmm... Now that I think about it, I’ve heard of a band of people who set up camp somewhere in the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;burnt forest far to the south in Enmerkar.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; They must be crazy, that place is crawling with Burning Men!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnKeeper_BC_Info_05</Key>
    <Value>You’re planning to talk to the Ash Giants? You’re either very brave, or very foolish. The only Giant settlement I know about is the one in the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;North-East of the Hallowed Marsh&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnKeeper_BC_Info_06</Key>
    <Value>Roland? He had a drink here not too long ago. He said he was going to the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Conflux Mountain via the Blue Chamber’s path&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, to become a mage. He seemed really nervous too. I think he would appreciate your help. I don’t know if he could handle the rock mantises in there.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnKeeper_BC_Info_06-other</Key>
    <Value>Roland Argenson? I’ve never heard of him, certainly never seen him either. Sounds like someone from Enmerkar or the Chersonese, though.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnKeeper_BC_Info_07</Key>
    <Value>You’re headed to the Cabal of Winds Temple to fight that Green shell horror? You’re out of your mind! That place is crawling with the Scourge! If you have to go, don't pick any needless fights.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnKeeper_BC_Info_07-other</Key>
    <Value>I’ve heard tell that the old Cabal of Winds Temple in Enmerkar is still a Scourge lair. Even after the Holy Mission sent a champion to cleanse the place, the Scourge just keep coming back! It’s scary!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnKeeper_BC_Info_08</Key>
    <Value>I heard you killed the Green shell horror hiding in Enmerkar’s old temple! I’m very impressed. Not just anyone can take down a Scourge Beast that big.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnKeeper_BC_Info_08-b</Key>
    <Value>&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sagard Battleborn over there just got into a fight with Julius Sutherland&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;! He killed the poor boy! It was awful! Elatt’s name, what was Julius thinking, pulling a knife on the Chamberlord like that?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnKeeper_BC_Info_09</Key>
    <Value>I can’t believe this war is coming to a close so suddenly! Elatt’s influence is very great indeed... I wonder if these peace talks will work out or not...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnKeeper_BC_Info_10</Key>
    <Value>Is it true that Monsoon was attacked by the Scourge, and that Calixa is a goddess now? We live in strange times indeed!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_01</Key>
    <Value>I should also let you know. Oliele and Yzan are leaving Cierzo. You should &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;speak with them&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; before they go.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Prequest_a_01</Key>
    <Value>What do you mean, they're leaving? What's going on?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_02</Key>
    <Value>Oliele is leaving Cierzo permanently, to go join the Holy Mission of Elatt. Nothing I could say would convince her to stay.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Prequest_a_02</Key>
    <Value>Good. It's about time you let her go.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_03</Key>
    <Value>You cannot understand what it feels like to have your only daughter forsake her name and home. I may never see her again. She was born into such an advantageous family... And yet, who am I to argue with a literal god?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Prequest_b_02</Key>
    <Value>Damn. I'll miss her around here.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_04</Key>
    <Value>As will we all. I don't suppose you could convince her to stay? She is my only daughter, set to inherit the clan when I join the ancestors... No, I don't suppose you'd be able to convince her. Her mind is made up.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Prequest_a_04</Key>
    <Value>And Yzan? Why is he leaving? He can't be ready for another expedition already!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_05</Key>
    <Value>Listen, [PlayerName]. The shipwreck that killed so many of our people, and nearly took your life was the fault of Yzan’s brother, Roland. A Blood Price has been declared upon his bloodline.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Prequest_a_05</Key>
    <Value>What? How can you be so sure?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_06</Key>
    <Value>He was on duty at the Lighthouse the night of the shipwreck. He fell asleep on duty and let the light go out. He confessed as much to me himself. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_06-b</Key>
    <Value>His negligence cost twelve lives, and the tribe must be compensated. Under the laws of the Blue Chamber Collective, and thus, the laws of Cierzo, his bloodline must be held responsible!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Prequest_b_05</Key>
    <Value>Oh Roland... Why am I not surprised?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_07</Key>
    <Value>Roland always did have his head in the clouds. But to show such negligence... He must be held accountable. Twelve people are dead because of his actions.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_08</Key>
    <Value>Yzan bears responsibility as well. As captain, he should have known better than to approach the bay when the lighthouse was not lit. This tragedy would have been avoided if either of them had used their heads.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_09</Key>
    <Value>Roland accepts the consequences of his actions. Yzan refuses. He has chosen to exile himself from Cierzo forever rather than do his duty to the tribe and bear the Blood Price.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Prequest_a_09</Key>
    <Value>Good decision on his part, then.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_10</Key>
    <Value>Bitterness solves nothing, [PlayerName]. If all of us acted so selfishly, there would be no tribe. We would all be roaming cannibal bandits killing one another like animals. That is a far worse fate than a few individuals repaying the harm they've caused.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Prequest_b_09</Key>
    <Value>Dammit, I'm losing two friends in one day.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_11</Key>
    <Value>I know this can't be easy for you, [PlayerName]. But this is the way things have to be.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Prequest_c_09</Key>
    <Value>This isn't fair. I understand punishing Roland, but why Yzan?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_12</Key>
    <Value>The Blood Price must be levied against an entire bloodline. Otherwise, the one who bears it would be pushed to act selfishly rather than repay what is owed to the tribe. Against a line, it can be held for at long as it needs to. Against an individual, it promotes only bloodshed.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_13</Key>
    <Value>Never forget, the Blood Price is not a punishment. It is repayment for a wrong. It allows those who have suffered to get their fair compensation without violence. Without it, we would be ruled by revenge and mob rule.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_14</Key>
    <Value>Come back once you've said your goodbyes to them. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Once you’re done, we should discuss your future here in Cierzo&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, now that you can handle the world outside.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_14-b</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_15</Key>
    <Value>&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;You should say your goodbyes to Oliele and Yzan&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; before they leave. Our discussion can wait until then. Yzan should still be down on the beach, near the water purifier. Oliele will likely be at the blacksmith’s shop.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_16</Key>
    <Value>There you are. Urgent news just came in. I must be off. Immediately. I don't know when I'll be able to return.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Prequest_a_16</Key>
    <Value>Why? What happened?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_17</Key>
    <Value>There's trouble in Berg. An official Council Meeting has been called.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Prequest_b_16</Key>
    <Value>Then why are you still here?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_18</Key>
    <Value>Because I may need of you. Because your future is important to me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_19</Key>
    <Value>I’m going to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Berg&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, the main settlement in the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Enmerkar region&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. The home city of all of the tribes, birthplace of our Blue Chamber Collective. If you are able, &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;I’d like you to meet me there&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_19-b</Key>
    <Value>I did not want to spring this on you, but... I have an offer. If you pledge yourself to work with me, I will pay off the rest of your Blood Price and adopt you into the Aberdeen bloodline. Your name would be cleared, and your burden lifted forever.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Prequest_a_19-b</Key>
    <Value>My Blood Price is still worth thousands of silvers! Where is this coming from?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_19-c</Key>
    <Value>It’s... complicated. With Oliele abandoning the family, I need someone that I can rely on. Someone I think of as close to family. And I want to make sure you never have to face a mob like that again.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_19-d</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_19-e</Key>
    <Value>It’s your choice, [PlayerName]. I won’t force you. But my offer is open to you. Work with me, and I will adopt you into the Aberdeen family and clear your Blood Price permanently.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Prequest_a_19</Key>
    <Value>I have a choice?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_20</Key>
    <Value>I can’t very well drag you along, now, can I? You are an adult. Your life is in your hands. All I can hope to do is try to guide and shape you into someone who acts with the Blue Chamber’s needs in mind.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_20-b</Key>
    <Value>If you want to make the journey to another settled region of Aurai, you will need to prepare &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Travel Rations&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. If you try to travel between regions without enough Rations, you will starve before you arrive at your destination.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_20-c</Key>
    <Value>Here. I have some &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Travel Rations&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; to spare. If you need more, the stores in Cierzo sell some. Or can craft your own &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;with some Salt and most types of food&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_21</Key>
    <Value>I hope to see you in Berg, [PlayerName]. If you wish to commit to the protection of the Blue Chamber Collective, meet me there. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Take the road to the south east of the Chersonese&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_22</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_23</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName], I’m glad to see you. Have you given my offer any thought? Will you work with me, and be adopted into the Aberdeen family?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Prequest_a_23</Key>
    <Value>I’m thinking about it. Is there anything I need to do to make it happen?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_24</Key>
    <Value>The Aberdeen family is one of the oldest and strongest families in the Collective. To help the process go smoothly, &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;you should get the approval of another old family&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Either the Sutherlands, the Battleborns or the Sullivans would do.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_25</Key>
    <Value>Gabriella Sullivan and Julius Sutherland are close allies of mine, and Sagard Battleborn wields an especially large degree of power as the Chamberlord of Berg. It would do you good to introduce yourself to them.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_26</Key>
    <Value>Gabriella should be near the food stand along the road. Julius is on an assignment near the stairs to the Blue Chamber, and Sagard would be at the inn. They should all be in bright blue, it’s hard to miss them.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_27</Key>
    <Value>They may ask for a small favor, to prove that you can bring value to the Collective, and I’m certain they will all reward you in their own way. Once you have their approval, let me know, and I can begin the adoption process.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_36</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Prequest_b_23</Key>
    <Value>I’m not interested.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_35</Key>
    <Value>Reconsider, [PlayerName]. Remember, the Blue Chamber Collective is a family. Do not cast us aside so easily.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_28</Key>
    <Value>You’ve spoken to my associates, then? Good. My offer still stands. If you pledge to work with me, I will begin the steps needed to adopt you into the Aberdeen bloodline and free you from your family’s Blood Price.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_29</Key>
    <Value>The Aberdeens are one of the oldest families in the Blue Chamber Collective, and our name carries a great deal of weight. It comes with great responsibility, but also many advantages. I believe you’d do us proud.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_30</Key>
    <Value>Will you pledge yourself to the continued survival of the Blue Chamber Collective, and join clan Aberdeen, [PlayerName]?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Prequest_a_30</Key>
    <Value>Not just yet. I need to think about this more.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_31</Key>
    <Value>Reconsider, [PlayerName]. Remember, the Blue Chamber Collective is a family. Do not cast us aside so easily.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Prequest_b_30</Key>
    <Value>Yes, I commit myself to the well being of the Collective. What do you need?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_32</Key>
    <Value>(This is a turning point in my life... &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Am I certain I wish to pledge my life to the Blue Chamber Collective&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;?)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Prequest_a_32</Key>
    <Value>Yes, I commit myself to the well being of the Collective. What do you need?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_BC_Prequest_b_32</Key>
    <Value>Not just yet. I need to think about this more.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_38</Key>
    <Value>I knew I could count on you. Very well, listen. The other Chamberlords are on their way here for a council meeting. Two major issues are at stake, both of which could cause a major impact on relations with the Sirroco and Abrassar regions. It’s too big of an event to go smoothly.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_33</Key>
    <Value>I’m not sure what, or how bad it will be, but I’m convinced beyond all doubt that something huge will happen. Something that could jeopardize the entire Collective if we aren’t ready for it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_34</Key>
    <Value>It will be a few days before they all arrive, however. Take the time you need to get used to life in Enmerkar. And don’t forget, Cierzo is still your home.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_37</Key>
    <Value>Here, as the newest member of the Aberdeen Family, you should have this. It’s the key to Cierzo. It should open any lock in the town, as well as the small basement vault in our family home.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_42</Key>
    <Value>You remember what the Blue Chamber Collective stands for. Only by sharing our burdens as family can we hope to survive in Aurai. We are all bound together, no matter our origins or our chosen path.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_43</Key>
    <Value>The individual pales in importance to the family and to the tribe. We all give up a little of what we want, making sure that everyone has what they need to survive.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_BC_Prequest_44</Key>
    <Value>What can you tell me about the Blue Chamber Collective?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_BC_Prequest_01</Key>
    <Value>Oh, great. It's you. Come to make my day even more awful? Well, too bad. I’m leaving Cierzo to go join the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Heroic Kingdom of Levant&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Maybe there people will treat me with some damn respect!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_BC_Prequest_02</Key>
    <Value>I take it you've heard the news, [PlayerName]? Come to see your old pal off?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_BC_Prequest_03</Key>
    <Value>I've got one little fishing barge to my name, and by Elatt I'm going to use it. I'm leaving for the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Heroic Kingdom of Levant&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, never to darken this stain of a city ever again.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Yzan_BC_Prequest_a_03</Key>
    <Value>Why so far away?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_BC_Prequest_04</Key>
    <Value>Levant believes that everyone deserves a shot at what they're best at, and doesn't have these backwards Tribal Laws to deal with. It's the rational place for a fresh start.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_BC_Prequest_05</Key>
    <Value>And honestly, the farther away I am from my dolt of a brother and that tyrant Rissa, the better I'll sleep at night!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Yzan_BC_Prequest_b_03</Key>
    <Value>You have a duty to your tribe! You can't abandon it like this!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_BC_Prequest_06</Key>
    <Value>Make me. This entire notion of Tribal Duty is oppressive at its core. My individual life is important, asking me to willingly sacrifice my wants and needs for the "collective good" is impossible. I refuse to be chained that way!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Yzan_BC_Prequest_c_03</Key>
    <Value>Good choice. Go chase your own dreams!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_BC_Prequest_07</Key>
    <Value>That I will. I will chase the Levantine dream and make it my own. I'll take any risk over being trapped here by my brother's idiocy.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Yzan_BC_Prequest_a_07</Key>
    <Value>I take it you're not going to forgive your brother, are you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_BC_Prequest_08</Key>
    <Value>Not in a thousand years. Roland had one job, keep the lighthouse lit. And he couldn’t even manage that! This was preventable, dammit!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_BC_Prequest_09</Key>
    <Value>This is the last time I let his foolishness and clumsiness hurt me. He can go feed a hyena with his own hide for all I care. I’m done with him. Now and forever.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Yzan_BC_Prequest_b_07</Key>
    <Value>How do you plan on making it to Levant? The sea can only take you so close. I mean, it's in the middle of a desert!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_BC_Prequest_10</Key>
    <Value>We'll go by ocean as far as we can, then leg it across the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Abrassar desert&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; on foot. We'll be rationing water the whole way. If I could afford it, I'd have bought potions to help with the heat... but we'll have to try our luck without them.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Yzan_BC_Prequest_a_10</Key>
    <Value>Can I come along? I want out of this place too.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_BC_Prequest_11</Key>
    <Value>I'd take you if I could, but you can't swim, and on a barge that small, you'd be nothing but a liability. I'm sorry, [PlayerName], but that's just not going to happen. If you manage to get to the Kingdom of Levant on your own somehow, though, I'll do my best to look out for you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_BC_Prequest_12</Key>
    <Value>If you plan to make the journey to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Levant&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; completely on foot, be prepared for a &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;long, long journey&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. You’ll have to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;leave the Chersonese by going south east&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, then travel &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;east through the entire Enmerkar Forest&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, and then finally &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;south through the Abrassar Desert&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; itself.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Yzan_BC_Prequest_b_10</Key>
    <Value>I'm going to miss you, Yzan. Wind be at your back.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_BC_Prequest_13</Key>
    <Value>Likewise, my friend. I hope we meet again under better circumstances. Wind be at your back.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_BC_Prequest_14</Key>
    <Value>If you have the courage to face the Abrassar desert and come to the Heroic Kingdom of Levant... &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;I'll be waiting for you.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_BC_Prequest_15</Key>
    <Value>I'm not going to forgive you, [PlayerName]. But &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;if we meet again in Levant&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;... maybe we can start over.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_BC_Prequest_16</Key>
    <Value>(Yzan shoves off with two men on his little fishing barge. He doesn't give Cierzo a backwards glance.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_BC_Prequest_17</Key>
    <Value>The Heroic Kingdom doesn’t buy into the idea that we should only focus on survival. They believe in pushing progress to create an even better society.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_BC_Prequest_18</Key>
    <Value>It’s a place where you can do what you were meant to do, without having to answer to oppressive tribal laws and the misdeeds of your ancestors. You succeed or fail on your own merits, no one else’s.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_BC_Prequest_19</Key>
    <Value>What can you tell me about The Heroic Kingdom?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Prequest_01</Key>
    <Value>So, you know. Yeah, it was my fault the boat got wrecked. It's my fault Yzan's got a Blood Price to pay. It's my fault your investment went belly up. Because I was a careless idiot.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Prequest_02</Key>
    <Value>I don’t even know how Rissa found out. It’s like she has some kind of sixth sense.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Prequest_03</Key>
    <Value>You're here to take what little I have, like you did to my brother, I guess? I already gave Rissa every silver I had. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Prequest_a_03</Key>
    <Value>At least you deserve your Blood Price. I don't.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Prequest_04</Key>
    <Value>I can't imagine how that must feel. It's bad enough knowing that I deserve my own. How do you even cope?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Prequest_b_03</Key>
    <Value>Get to work and pay it back. Do your duty to the tribe.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Prequest_05</Key>
    <Value>I know my duty. And my future descendant's duties. We will pay our Blood Price for however many generations it takes. I won't run from this. This is my punishment, and I will shoulder it however I can, until I die. That's what's expected of me, right?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Prequest_c_03</Key>
    <Value>Grow up and stop whining. We all have burdens to bear.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Prequest_06</Key>
    <Value>That’s what Rissa told me. I guess this is just the way the world is. Shut up, give up on your life, and live for everyone else. Fine. I can try, at least.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Prequest_d_03</Key>
    <Value>You have no idea how much I want to kill you, Roland. I lost my home because of you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Prequest_07</Key>
    <Value>I know, I know. I'm sorry. I’ll try to save up to repay you. Somehow. After all, part of my Blood Price has to go to helping you, right?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Prequest_a_07</Key>
    <Value>How do you intend to pay your Blood Price?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Prequest_08</Key>
    <Value>I don’t know. I’m bad at everything I do. I don’t have the patience to fish, I’m not good with steel… Bah. I might just throw myself at the outside world and try to make it there.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Prequest_a_08</Key>
    <Value>You? Challenge the outside world? You’d be dead in a day.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Prequest_09</Key>
    <Value>Maybe. But maybe I don’t care. Either learn and succeed, or die and it’s not my problem anymore… Risks don’t scare me right now.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Prequest_b_08</Key>
    <Value>That’s the spirit. Make it work or die trying!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Prequest_10</Key>
    <Value>Ugh... Maybe I should beg Eto to teach me some of his personal &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;combat Skills&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; first... I don’t want to be torn to pieces by Hyenas or Troglodytes…</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Prequest_11</Key>
    <Value>Ugh... This latest attempt at fishing was a botch... How in Elatt’s name am I going to be able to live like this?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Prequest_12</Key>
    <Value>You’re leaving Cierzo, right? Hang on... Here, it’s not much but it should help a little. I’ll keep trying to make it up to you, [PlayerName], I promise.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Prequest_13</Key>
    <Value>I’m getting better day by day... It’s still hopeless, but at least I can survive like this, even if it’s just barely. I’ll keep trying to make it up to you, [PlayerName], I promise.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Prequest_14</Key>
    <Value>Oh! [PlayerName]! I found this on a hunter’s corpse not too far out from town. It’s still got his blood on it, but... It’s still usable!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Prequest_a_14</Key>
    <Value>Thanks, Roland.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Roland_BC_Prequest_b_14</Key>
    <Value>You should look after yourself Roland, keep it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Prequest_15</Key>
    <Value>I stumbled on a small cache of gems the other day. I know this should go to my Blood Price Payment, but... you lost your home because of me. You need this more than me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Prequest_16</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName]! It’s good to see you! I almost didn’t make it to Berg in one piece. Some metal golem dog things nearly got me! If a passing hunter hadn’t saved me...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Prequest_17</Key>
    <Value>He gave me some stuff to make traps and told me to use them and my brain if I’m not good at fighting. But I’d rather practice fighting than rely on these tricky things. I nearly impaled myself trying to arm one!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Prequest_18</Key>
    <Value>No. I insist. Take it. I want to make up for the shipwreck I got you caught in.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Prequest_19</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Roland_BC_Prequest_20</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_BC_Prequest_01a</Key>
    <Value>I guess this is goodbye, [PlayerName]. I’m leaving this place to join the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Holy Mission&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; and I’m not looking back.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_BC_Prequest_a_01</Key>
    <Value>Cierzo will miss you, Oliele.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_BC_Prequest_02</Key>
    <Value>I’ll miss it too. But I can’t come back. Not after what Mother and I discussed.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_BC_Prequest_b_01</Key>
    <Value>Did something happen? You’re scowling.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_BC_Prequest_03</Key>
    <Value>Mother and I had a talk. I didn’t like any of what I heard.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_BC_Prequest_04</Key>
    <Value>Rissa has... done some things I can’t agree with. I can’t talk about it. She wants me to follow in her footsteps and I... I just can’t. I already have no desire to be Chamberlady. And what she told me... I refuse to consider being part of it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_BC_Prequest_05</Key>
    <Value>It’s unlikely we’ll meet again, [PlayerName]. Unless, of course, you want to join me. Having someone I trust by my side would make me a lot less nervous.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_BC_Prequest_a_04</Key>
    <Value>I’ll think about it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_BC_Prequest_06</Key>
    <Value>I’m glad. I’d be happy to have you with me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_BC_Prequest_b_04</Key>
    <Value>And spend my life serving Elatt? No thank you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_BC_Prequest_07</Key>
    <Value>Is spending your life under Rissa’s thumb any better? At least with the Holy Mission, you’d be working for the good of all Aurai. We’d get to go to far off places, face the Scourge, help people. It’d be an adventure!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_BC_Prequest_08</Key>
    <Value>In fact... if you join the Holy Mission and give up your bloodline, you’d be free from ever making payments on your Blood Price as well. It’s the ideal clean slate.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_BC_Prequest_09</Key>
    <Value>If you do want to join us, meet me in &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Monsoon, in the Hallowed Marsh&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;The road you need to take to reach the marsh is in the east of the Chersonese&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_BC_Prequest_09-b</Key>
    <Value>Once you reach the marsh, follow the Pilgrim Road, &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;the trail of Sun-Pillars&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; towards the ray of light that flies over Monsoon.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_BC_Prequest_09-bZ</Key>
    <Value>Listen, I have to head off before Mother tries to convince me again. In case we don’t see each other again... It was nice knowing you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_BC_Prequest_10</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_BC_Prequest_11</Key>
    <Value>First, protect and look after those who are in need. Second, have discipline and mastery over yourself. And third, always seek to improve yourself so you can better help others to improve and help one another. It’s a good set of values to live by.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_BC_Prequest_12</Key>
    <Value>The Holy Mission is about more than working for a god or fighting the Scourge. It’s also about helping everyone regardless of tribe or family.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_BC_Prequest_13</Key>
    <Value>What can you tell me about the Holy Mission?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_Prequest_01</Key>
    <Value>Well, well, look at that, you're not completely useless. Alright, I'll spread the word that you have my approval. I hope to see you join our troops and show some of those runts what it means to be part of Berg’s army.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Sagard_BC_Prequest_a_01</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_Prequest_02</Key>
    <Value>You must be the one Rissa wants to adopt into her bloodline. I’m not too impressed, but I’ve been wrong before. So long as you’re working with the Blue Chamber’s goals in mind, we shouldn't have a problem.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_Prequest_03</Key>
    <Value>I’m the Chamberlord of Berg and handle the Collective’s armies. Note the plural there. Each village provides me with troops that I have to organize into something cohesive. It’s a nightmare only discipline can solve!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_Prequest_04</Key>
    <Value>Half of the runts I have to work with don't even know how to craft a simple Fire Rag! Show me that you can &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;make any kind of rag that will enhance a weapon&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, and maybe I'll consider lending my weight to Rissa's adoption announcement.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_Prequest_05</Key>
    <Value>Oh, and take this with you. It’s my personal recipe for Spiritual Varnish. If you’re fighting ghosts, this varnish’ll make your weapon highly effective against them. You’ll need an alchemy set if you want to make it, though.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_Prequest_06</Key>
    <Value>Move along. I have combat strategies to prepare for when those desert rats in Levant inevitably come after us. It’s only a matter of time before they get too big for their bloomers and try to take what isn’t theirs.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_BC_Prequest_07</Key>
    <Value>Unless we’re under attack or you’re here to drink with me, I don’t have much to say to you. Free time is hard to come by for a Chamberlord of such a big city and I intend to enjoy every moment I can snatch.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Prequest_01</Key>
    <Value>Ah, you must be the scout that Rissa mentioned. I’m Berg’s mistress of the hunt. If you need &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;training&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; in the art of hunting prey, my cousin near the entrance can teach you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Prequest_02</Key>
    <Value>If you want me to give you my family's approval, show me that you can handle the wild. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Show me that you can make a Fang Weapon&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; from the remains of your enemies. If you don't know how, the local blacksmith can teach you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Prequest_03</Key>
    <Value>Is that a Fang Weapon? Here, let me hold it for a moment... This handiwork isn’t bad at all, [PlayerName]! I feel comfortable lending my voice to your adoption. You'll make a great addition to the Aberdeen family.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Prequest_04</Key>
    <Value>Carry on, [PlayerName]. I’ll come to you if I need something.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_BC_Prequest_05</Key>
    <Value>Here, a little gift from one hunter to another. Use it well.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Julius_BC_Prequest_01</Key>
    <Value>Let’s keep this short, [PlayerName]. I’m Gabriella’s top informant. I can get into places she can’t. I can get places everyone can’t. If you see me, it’s because I want you to see me. Got it?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Julius_BC_Prequest_02</Key>
    <Value>If you want me to give my family's approval for your adoption, I'll need to know you can pull your weight. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Come back to me with the power of magic&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, and you'll have earned my respect.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Julius_BC_Prequest_03</Key>
    <Value>You’re blowing my cover. I’m on a case, and my mark might get away if you draw attention!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Julius_BC_Prequest_04</Key>
    <Value>You know how to unlock your control over Mana, right? You need to travel to the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Conflux Mountain in the Chersonese&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, and venture to the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ley Line&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; deep below it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Julius_BC_Prequest_05</Key>
    <Value>Well, well, well. You've unlocked the power of Mana. Your control is strong, too. Yes, I think you'll be helpful to us. The Sutherlands will approve of your adoption. Welcome, [PlayerName] Aberdeen.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Julius_BC_Prequest_06</Key>
    <Value>As a fellow mage, I think you’ll appreciate this recipe quite a bit. It’s saved my skin more than once.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
</ArrayOfDialogue>