<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ArrayOfDialogue xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_Questions_01</Key>
    <Value>My hands are full with important matters, missionary. Ellinara will give you work from now on.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Questions_01</Key>
    <Value>Blessings of Elatt upon you, [PlayerName]. It's time for your first mission.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Questions_02</Key>
    <Value>Before I give you your first mission, I want you to understand the lengths we must go to oppose the Scourge. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Burn greasy fern at the altar on the hill next to the Vigil Crystal just outside Monsoon&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, and tell me what you see.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Questions_10</Key>
    <Value>Before you go I need you to understand the lengths we go to to protect Aurai from the Scourge. Have you ever seen one of the Vigils before?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_Questions_a_10</Key>
    <Value>Those are the giant crystal tower things, right? The ones that protect us from the Scourge?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Questions_11</Key>
    <Value>Yes, exactly. There's one not far from Monsoon. I want you to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;go there and burn a Greasy Fern at the altar atop the hill beside it&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Breathe it in, and then tell me what you see there. Only then will you be ready for your first mission.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Questions_12</Key>
    <Value>If you don't have any Greasy Fern with you, the alchemist should have some for sale.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Questions_13</Key>
    <Value>Yes, [PlayerName]?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_Questions_a_13</Key>
    <Value>I burnt Greasy Fern at the Vigil's altar.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Questions_14</Key>
    <Value>And what did you see?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_Questions_a_14</Key>
    <Value>Spirits, trapped with a Scourge Beast in the crystal, stabbing it endlessly.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_Questions_b_14</Key>
    <Value>I saw why the Vigils work. It was... painful to look at.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_Questions_c_14</Key>
    <Value>I don't want to talk about it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Questions_15</Key>
    <Value>And what did you learn?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_Questions_a_15</Key>
    <Value>Sometimes, victory comes with great sacrifice.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Questions_16</Key>
    <Value>Indeed. Now you know why Elatt doesn't celebrate his victory against the Scourge. It came at grave cost.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_Questions_b_15</Key>
    <Value>Sometimes you have to do terrible things if you want to survive.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Questions_17</Key>
    <Value>Sometimes. But they are to be avoided at all costs. Or else we become the very monsters we fight against.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_Questions_c_15</Key>
    <Value>Even gods make mistakes.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Questions_18</Key>
    <Value>Perhaps. Now you see why Elatt fights the Scourge as much as he can. Should we someday eradicate them, it will mean an end to the suffering of those spirits.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Questions_19</Key>
    <Value>The Vigils are a necessary evil. Until the Scourge is purged from Aurai, those spirits keep us safe. They are a grim reminder of the evil we face, and our sworn mission.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Questions_20</Key>
    <Value>We can't depend on the Vigils and our warriors to defend us from the Scourge forever. We must find a way to free Aurai from them, permanently. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_Questions_a_20</Key>
    <Value>I understand. Whatever it takes.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_Questions_b_20</Key>
    <Value>Then we'd better hurry and get that done. The sooner we can free those spirits, the better.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Questions_21</Key>
    <Value>Oliele said much the same, although I can tell this revelation hurt her deeply.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Questions_22</Key>
    <Value>On that note, I have work for you. I sent Oliele on a mission before you left for the Vigil, and I would feel better if you joined her. Something about it sends chills up my spine.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Questions_23</Key>
    <Value>Are you familiar with the Montcalm tribe in the Chersonese?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_Questions_a_23</Key>
    <Value>Those lunatics who string up the corpses of their enemies all around their village? Yeah, I've heard about them. They've been hostile to Cierzo for years.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Questions_24</Key>
    <Value>They've been turning to the undead from the valley beyond the Ghost Pass for protection. While this is itself worrisome, things have taken a turn for the worse.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Questions_25</Key>
    <Value>Elatt can sense a huge growth of Corruption erupting underground. Whatever is down there has become dangerously tainted. It must be cleansed before it becomes a serious threat to the Chersonese.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Questions_26</Key>
    <Value>&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Go beyond the Ghost Pass in the Chersonese, delve deep underground in the valley beyond it, and find the source of the Corruption. Cleanse it by any means necessary&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Questions_27</Key>
    <Value>I’m here to report on the mission. We purified the altar. The Corruption under the Chersonese is back under control.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Questions_28</Key>
    <Value>Good work, [PlayerName]. Where's Oliele?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_Questions_a_28</Key>
    <Value>She'll be back soon. She needs time. She… Elatt saved her life by removing the corruption in her, replacing her limbs with pure light.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Questions_29</Key>
    <Value>Elatt's name… I understand. Something that drastic will take its toll, even on the most faithful believers. For a new missionary… I don't blame her for needing some time.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Questions_30</Key>
    <Value>You're free for now, [PlayerName]. I'll let you know when we need you again.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Questions_31</Key>
    <Value>Take your time getting familiar with the Marsh, [PlayerName]. You'll get your first task soon enough. Prepare yourself. In a few days and I will have something for you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_Questions_01</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Mofat_HM_Questions_a_01</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_Questions_02</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Mofat_HM_Questions_b_01</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_Questions_03</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_Questions_04</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_Questions_05</Key>
    <Value>I’m waiting on a delivery of Livweedi, sorry. I can’t chat until it arrives. It’s important.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Damian_HM_Questions_01</Key>
    <Value>I'm a busy man! Unless you have something important to say to me, I have no time for anyone who serves that freak in the temple.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Damian_HM_Questions_a_01</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Damian_HM_Questions_02</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Damian_HM_Questions_b_01</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Damian_HM_Questions_03</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Damian_HM_Questions_04</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_00</Key>
    <Value>Oh...[PlayerName]… I can’t really talk now. I… I have a mission to prepare for. I’ll see you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_00-b</Key>
    <Value>Hey, if Ellinara asks you to… Never mind… Forget I said anything.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_01</Key>
    <Value>Oh. Hi. I guess it's only natural they'd send you here too.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_a_01</Key>
    <Value>What are you doing here, Oliele?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_03</Key>
    <Value>I just... wanted to come back here before leaving for my first mission. Ellinara told you to burn Greasy Fern here too, didn't she? Tell me what you see. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_04</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName]... Did you see it? Those poor spirits... They'll never rest in peace.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_a_04</Key>
    <Value>That's horrifying.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_b_04</Key>
    <Value>No wonder the Scourge don't go anywhere near the Vigils.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_05</Key>
    <Value>I knew Elatt was only the god of discipline, not the force that created all of Aurai... But seeing this... What IS Elatt? How can he allow this? What did I choose to become part of?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_a_05</Key>
    <Value>You're having doubts about joining the Holy Mission?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_06</Key>
    <Value>Aren't you? After seeing this? Those spirits are trapped in that crystal forever, their only purpose for all eternity is to torture that Scourge Beast...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_a_06</Key>
    <Value>Well, it's an effective Scourge repellent, that's for sure.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_07</Key>
    <Value>How can you so easily justify this?! Those people's spirits are in torment, [PlayerName]! What if it was your parents trapped in that crystal?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_a_07</Key>
    <Value>Oliele, without the Vigils, the Scourge Beasts could attack our homes, our families. They're ravenous evil monsters. Would you take that chance?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_08</Key>
    <Value>You're right. I wouldn't. But still... This sacrifice is horrible...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_b_07</Key>
    <Value>We can't doubt Elatt. If he did this, it's because it had to be done.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_09</Key>
    <Value>He was human once... He may still be capable of human error. Is this really the best solution, or is it just a desperate plan that no one has bothered to question?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_b_06</Key>
    <Value>I'm having doubts too...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_10</Key>
    <Value>So it's not just me... I know Elatt isn't the answer to everything. But when I pledged myself to him, I believed he truly wanted nothing more than to protect others... Now I'm not so sure...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_a_10</Key>
    <Value>This does protect us, though. It keeps the Scourge Beasts away from us.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_11</Key>
    <Value>At what price...There must be a better way…</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_b_10</Key>
    <Value>All we can do is trust in Elatt…</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_12</Key>
    <Value>I... I suppose...I can only keep on hoping that this cruelty was necessary.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_13</Key>
    <Value>Either way, the fact remains that we need to destroy the Scourge once and for all. These poor spirits deserve to finally rest in peace.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_14</Key>
    <Value>I'm off. Ellinara gave me a task to perform and I intend to see that it's carried out. I'll be seeing you, [PlayerName].</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_15</Key>
    <Value>Oh! [PlayerName]! I wasn't expecting you! I guess Ellinara sent you to check on me?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_a_15</Key>
    <Value>Yes. She said something about this mission sent chills up her spine.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_16</Key>
    <Value>I'm fine, [PlayerName]. I'm not a child who needs supervision. Still, thanks for coming. A friendly face is always welcome.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_b_15</Key>
    <Value>I thought you might appreciate some backup.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_17</Key>
    <Value>I do. I’m not sure what has me more on edge. The undead hiding in the shadows, or being so close to a hostile tribe that would kill us on sight…</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_18</Key>
    <Value>The undead in this area bind their memories to an ancestral altar past this door. That's where the source of the Corruption is. But they've &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;locked the door with some kind of spell&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. It's taking me forever to remove it...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_a_18</Key>
    <Value>Maybe something in the cave is keeping the spell active?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_19</Key>
    <Value>Maybe. Can I ask you to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;go look for it&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;? Maybe if I keep casting counter-spells on this door, I'll manage to break through and we can get in, regardless.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_20</Key>
    <Value>Ugh. Whoever sealed this door had an inhuman amount of time on their hands!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_21</Key>
    <Value>The spell on the door just faded without warning. That was your doing, I suppose?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_a_21</Key>
    <Value>I killed the undead that was keeping it closed, yeah. What's the situation here?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_22</Key>
    <Value>Umm… So that skeleton came up and said you sent him to open up the door...What happened?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_a_22</Key>
    <Value>He's been trying to keep the undead here in check. He's trying to help.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_23</Key>
    <Value>I'm going to trust your judgment on this one. Most people would have finished him off purely on reflex. You're really something.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_a_23</Key>
    <Value>What's the situation down here?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_24</Key>
    <Value>We still have time before the damage is permanent. I'll try to purify this altar. Ellinara taught me the spell she uses for work like this.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_25</Key>
    <Value>Most of the memories that the ghosts have placed in this altar have been consumed by the Corruption. The ghosts are so far gone that they don't want to be purified. They're preventing me from even touching the altar.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_a_25</Key>
    <Value>We have to do something. It's only a matter of time before they're beyond saving.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_26</Key>
    <Value>I have an idea. It's insane, but I can't think of anything else. [PlayerName], I need you to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;pour some of your life into this altar&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. It'll pacify the ghosts while I cast the spell to cleanse it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_a_26</Key>
    <Value>You want me to give up some of my life to these things? Have you lost your mind?!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_27</Key>
    <Value>They're desperately addicted to fresh life now. They'll only drop their defenses if there's something to feed on. The spell will take all of my concentration, so it has to be someone else who makes the sacrifice…</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_28</Key>
    <Value>(You feel the the Altar suck at your very spirit the moment you approach... )</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_a_28</Key>
    <Value>(Give up Health)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_b_28</Key>
    <Value>(Give up Stamina)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_c_28</Key>
    <Value>(Give up Strength)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_29</Key>
    <Value>(Give up Endurance)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_30</Key>
    <Value>(Agony rips through you as the Ghosts greedily feed on your very essence! All you can do is trust Oliele.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_31</Key>
    <Value>(Oliele's eyes are red bleeding voids, her arms covered in quivering red lumps, her veins green and glowing...)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_32</Key>
    <Value>(A burst of light floods the room. As it fades Oliele stands before you, her eyes and arms replaced with pure light)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_33</Key>
    <Value>What... Elatt... What did you do to me?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_a_33</Key>
    <Value>Oliele! What happened to you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_34</Key>
    <Value>The Corruption lashed back against me! I thought I was going to die... My eyes... My arms... I felt them get consumed…</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_35</Key>
    <Value>Elatt told me it wasn't my time... He saved me. I think he replaced whatever the Corruption took with light. But what have I become?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_a_35</Key>
    <Value>You're still you, Oliele, just with body parts made of light.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_36</Key>
    <Value>Y-you say that like it's no big deal! I've lost parts of my body! </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_a_36</Key>
    <Value>Think of the new limbs like a crutch. A crutch that makes you stronger, rather than slowing you down.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_37</Key>
    <Value>I... You're right. I shouldn't worry. Elatt saved me. That's all that matters. He wouldn't save me if he had malicious intent... I hope.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_b_36</Key>
    <Value>You have body parts crafted by a literal god, Oliele. You should be excited!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_38</Key>
    <Value>I can't just casually shrug this off! My eyes... They're not mine anymore... How can I trust what I see if they're not my own eyes?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_b_35</Key>
    <Value>I don't know, but it looks powerful. That's an amazing blessing he gave you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_39</Key>
    <Value>Look at me! I'm... I'm not me anymore! What did he do to me?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_40</Key>
    <Value>Thanks, [PlayerName]. It's going to take time to accept this... But I guess the only thing I can do is keep moving forward.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_41</Key>
    <Value>Does Elatt know my doubts? Did he save me regardless? Will he take these away if I question him? I... I don't know anymore. The only thing I can do is just... keep moving forward, I guess.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_a_41</Key>
    <Value>Is the altar taken care of? It's still stuck in that mass of Corruption.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_42</Key>
    <Value>Yes, I've purified the Corruption afflicting the altar. That fleshy mass is no longer malignant. We've averted the crisis for now.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Questions_a_42</Key>
    <Value>What about when the Corruption builds up again?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_43</Key>
    <Value>I don't know. I don't think we can solve that problem... I only hope Ellinara or Elatt can think of something...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_44</Key>
    <Value>I'm… going to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;go back to Monsoon&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, [PlayerName]. I'll see you there… whenever I get there. I need time. Time to get used to… the new me, I guess.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_45</Key>
    <Value>I want to be alone, [PlayerName]. I need time. Time to get used to… the new me, I guess.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_46</Key>
    <Value>I’m going to need you to lay your hands on the altar and focus your thoughts on it. If both of us work on it it’s far more likely that things will go smoothly.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_47</Key>
    <Value>Alright, I’ll start the spell. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Stand back&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, [PlayerName]. Far back. There’s no telling what the Corruption will do once the spell hits it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_48</Key>
    <Value>Please, [PlayerName]. Unless we get the ghosts to lower their guard, I can’t purify the altar. You’ll have to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;pour some of your own life into it&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. It’s the only way.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Questions_49</Key>
    <Value>Looks like the only thing I can do is… keep moving forward.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Vigil_HM_Questions_01</Key>
    <Value>(Sorrow and pain, and a sense of duty linger around this altar)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Vigil_HM_Questions_a_01</Key>
    <Value>(Burn a Greasy Fern on the altar)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Vigil_HM_Questions_02</Key>
    <Value>(As you breathe in the aroma of the Greasy Fern, the memories of the buried ancestors floods your mind with vicious images.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Vigil_HM_Questions_03</Key>
    <Value>(You see an army of warriors fighting a massive Scourge Beast with spears… They are nearly wiped out, before one of them manages to cripple the beast. A ray of light falls from the sky and engulfs the monster, and it is trapped within shining crystal, surrounded by the dozens of people it killed.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Vigil_HM_Questions_04</Key>
    <Value>(As the memories fade and you return to your senses, you look up at the Vigil crystal and briefly see a swarm of ghosts trapped within the crystal with the Scourge Beast, endlessly stabbing it with their ghostly weapons.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Vigil_HM_Questions_05</Key>
    <Value>(You sense agony rippling from the crystal... The Scourge Beast within is still alive, endlessly tortured by the spirits of those it killed, the monster's pain a warning to keep other Scourge Beasts far, far away from Monsoon...)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Vigil_HM_Questions_b_01</Key>
    <Value>(Leave)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_01</Key>
    <Value>Hoy! You! Yes, YOU! Fleshbag! Over here! &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;The boxes on the side! Check the boxes on the side!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_02</Key>
    <Value>Finally! Hoy there! Name's Myriade! Sorry, as you can see, I've kin’of fallen to pieces.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Myriade_HM_Questions_a_02</Key>
    <Value>A talking skull. Now I've seen everything.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_03</Key>
    <Value>You're telling me! Fleshy people haven't been down here in ages!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Myriade_HM_Questions_b_02</Key>
    <Value>You have spoken your last, monster!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_04</Key>
    <Value>Oy oy! Monster? I ain’t a monster! Jus’ a pile of bones trying to get by! I ain’t no threat to nobody!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_05</Key>
    <Value>I'm the one who used to "lead" this merry band of undead cretins. And then the others got mad when I said not to eat the tasty offerings the living folk left outside...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_06</Key>
    <Value>So the other undead tore me apart and stuffed my pieces all over the darn cave. If I could jus’ get to the old altar, I’d get ’em back in line… &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;If you can put me back together, I’ll open the path there again&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_07</Key>
    <Value>I put a spell to seal the door, to try to keep anythin’ nasty from coming out. The only way I can lift it &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;is if I get in front of that door to undo the spell. Well, either that or I finally shuffle off this mortal coil&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Myriade_HM_Questions_a_07</Key>
    <Value>One thing at a time. First, tell me what's going on here before I decide to put you back together!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_08</Key>
    <Value>Alright alright! There was a lot of blood spilled in the old fort. The victims jus’ couldn’t go to the afterlife. It caused a lot of Corruption to spill out, you know?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_09</Key>
    <Value>I gave those victims a home here, where they can live the lives that were stolen from them. There's an ancestral altar they can tether their memories to, so they can remember who they were when they were alive.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_10</Key>
    <Value>There's also plenty of Corruption to feed on, to cope with the hunger for life. It's not great, but it's enough to keep us sane.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_11</Key>
    <Value>Then, those living people out there started stringing up dying people as tribute and my ghost pals stopped feedin’ on the Corruption, preferring fresh tasty dying life.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_12</Key>
    <Value>But using Corruption as food is like milking a deer. If you don't milk it often enough, it'll just build up until you have a major problem. The Corruption has burst all over the Altar now, and it's destroying the memories we've stored within.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_13</Key>
    <Value>If it's not dealt with, those ghosts will lose what little humanity they have left! Then they'll just devour everything around, including the living who've been feeding them so nicely.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Myriade_HM_Questions_b_07</Key>
    <Value>Alright, I’ll help you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_14</Key>
    <Value>Wha? Just like that? You're not curious about the old talking skeleton?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Myriade_HM_Questions_a_14</Key>
    <Value>Not really. I just want to get this mess fixed.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_15</Key>
    <Value>Not curious about the spooky, scary skeleton, and jus’ wants to help a fella! I like you, fleshbag!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Myriade_HM_Questions_b_14</Key>
    <Value>Actually, I do want to know what's going on down here.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Myriade_HM_Questions_c_07</Key>
    <Value>So I can just bash your skull in and the door opens up?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_16</Key>
    <Value>Hoy! You’re not seriously thinking about actually bashing my skull to pieces, are ya?!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Myriade_HM_Questions_a_16</Key>
    <Value>You're an undead. A life-eating monster. I'm doing Aurai a favor! (Smash the skull)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_17</Key>
    <Value>Hoy, wait a minute! You're pulling my bone, right?!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Myriade_HM_Questions_a_17</Key>
    <Value>(Despite the skull's protestations, you break it to pieces in one strike. A rush of mana pours out. The spell sealing the door to the Altar should be lifted)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Myriade_HM_Questions_b_16</Key>
    <Value>No, I'm just considering the possibility.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_18</Key>
    <Value>Un-consider it! Un-consider it! This half-life isn't too much, but it's all I've got!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Myriade_HM_Questions_a_13</Key>
    <Value>Sure, I'll help. Do you have any idea where to look for your body parts?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Myriade_HM_Questions_b_13</Key>
    <Value>Now I'm more tempted than ever to smash you and move on with my life.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_19</Key>
    <Value>Lemme feel for 'em...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_20</Key>
    <Value>Ok, my torso feels like it's propped up on something, in a lit up area... Feels like there's minecart tracks nearby... If you can bring my skull there, I can probably feel for the other parts.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_20-b</Key>
    <Value>(You pick up the skull and take it with you.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_21</Key>
    <Value>Ah, there we go! Already better! Let's feel for the others now...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_22</Key>
    <Value>Hoy there, need me to feel for the rest of my body parts?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Myriade_HM_Questions_a_22</Key>
    <Value>Yes, where are they?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Myriade_HM_Questions_b_22</Key>
    <Value>No, I'm fine.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Myriade_HM_Questions_c_22</Key>
    <Value>(Smash Myriade's skull and open the barrier to the altar)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_23</Key>
    <Value>One arm feels like there's a campfire not far away... If I really stretch it... There's crystalized Mana nearby...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_24</Key>
    <Value>One arm feels like it's someplace kinda high up... If I really stretch it... There's the sound of little things scurrying not too far away.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_25</Key>
    <Value>My missing leg feels like it's someplace low and open... If I really stretch it... There's water nearby with something swimming in it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_25-b</Key>
    <Value>(A badly cracked bone lies here... Whoever this belonged to must have died horribly.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_26</Key>
    <Value>(The arm waves at you. Clearly this belongs to Myriade.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_27</Key>
    <Value>(The leg stretches, as if to say "Here I am". This has to be Myriade's.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_28</Key>
    <Value>(The torso hops a little, presenting the neck stump... This has to be Myriade's.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Myriade_HM_Questions_d_22</Key>
    <Value>I brought back your... hmm... bones.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_29</Key>
    <Value>Great, time to pull myself back together!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_30</Key>
    <Value>Ah, it's great to be in one piece again! Thanks for giving us a hand! ... And a leg and a ribcage!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Myriade_HM_Questions_a_30</Key>
    <Value>Funny guy. Now open that door, would you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Myriade_HM_Questions_b_30</Key>
    <Value>I'll pretend I didn't hear that. Where's the Altar we need to work on?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_31</Key>
    <Value>&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;It's in the frozen cave back near the entrance. It should be near the bottom of the ramp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, where that nasty old Wendigo set up camp. I'll see you there!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_32</Key>
    <Value>(Myriade takes off at inhuman speed, his bones cracking loudly as he fades into the darkness...)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_33</Key>
    <Value>Things have gotten really bad while I was in pieces. The altar we’ve bound our memories to is smothered by the Corruption. It’s too much for me to eat away without losin’ my mind.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_34</Key>
    <Value>I really hope your lady friend there knows what she's doing. Corruption this thick takes on a life of its own.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_35</Key>
    <Value>I can help if you need me to. They'll tear what's left of my spirit to shreds, but it’ll distract ‘em for a bit. If it prevents you from ending up like ol’ Myriade, I'll do it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Myriade_HM_Questions_a_35</Key>
    <Value>No way. We need you in order to get these ghosts in order when we're done.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_36</Key>
    <Value>Well, that's true... I hope you can handle it, fleshy guy.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Myriade_HM_Questions_b_35</Key>
    <Value>Yes, help me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_37</Key>
    <Value>Well, here goes nothing...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_38</Key>
    <Value>Hah, thank you. It was a JOINT effort! Eh? Ehhh?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Myriade_HM_Questions_a_38</Key>
    <Value>Har har, you're killing me, Myriade.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Myriade_HM_Questions_b_38</Key>
    <Value>Stop! One more bad joke and I'll take you apart again!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_39</Key>
    <Value>You ain’t no fun. I'll keep my fellow undead on a tight leash from now on. I won't let them forget what they almost became.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_40</Key>
    <Value>Anyone who goes to nibble on tasty Montcalm Tribe tribute treats are no longer welcome to bind their memories here. I'm sure that threat will keep them from going bad again. A place where memories can stick is hard to come by.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_41</Key>
    <Value>Thanks again for your help. We're taking care to eat away at the Corruption regularly. It won't be a problem again, I promise!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_42</Key>
    <Value>I'll be back with your missing parts.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_43</Key>
    <Value>So, any luck?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Myriade_HM_Questions_a_26</Key>
    <Value>(Take Myriade’s body part)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Myriade_HM_Questions_b_26</Key>
    <Value>(Leave it be)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_44</Key>
    <Value>I. Ow. Mind. Memory. Can't. Think.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Myriade_HM_Questions_45</Key>
    <Value>(The blast of Corruption from the altar seems to have stunned Myriade. You should give him a moment to recover.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_Questions_01</Key>
    <Value>(You feel the warmth of a campfire fill you… Elatt speaks in your mind)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_Questions_02</Key>
    <Value>Well done, [PlayerName]! You brought peace to the tormented spirits under the Chersonese and established future safeguards for that region's safety.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elatt_HM_Questions_a_02</Key>
    <Value>At what cost, though?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elatt_HM_Questions_b_02</Key>
    <Value>What happened to Oliele?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_Questions_03</Key>
    <Value>As Oliele purified the altar, the Corruption clung to her. It would have left her an agonized husk of flesh. I did the only thing I could for her…</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_Questions_04</Key>
    <Value>Replacing her lost body parts with light is an extreme measure. She will bear those scars, and my blessing for the rest of her days. They are a part of her now.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_Questions_05</Key>
    <Value>The job is done, [PlayerName]. I fear that without proper care, the Corruption will only grow again under the Chersonese. I will have to think very long about how to resolve it... Even so, you did your duty.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_Questions_06</Key>
    <Value>You deserve a reward for your trials. I will grant a blessing to you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elatt_HM_Questions_a_06</Key>
    <Value>Thank you for your blessing. I'll make good use of it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_Questions_07</Key>
    <Value>(You feel warmth flood your body. You are filled with new strength)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elatt_HM_Questions_b_06</Key>
    <Value>Give Oliele the blessing instead. I think she'll need it more than I will.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_Questions_08</Key>
    <Value>Are you certain?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elatt_HM_Questions_a_08</Key>
    <Value>Yes, give it to her.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_Questions_09</Key>
    <Value>You are exceptionally kind, [PlayerName]. It is done. She is grateful.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_Questions_10</Key>
    <Value>Carry on, missionary. Continue your good work.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Zephyrien_HM_Questions_01</Key>
    <Value>If you ever find yourself facing ghosts, some Spiritual Varnish will make things a lot easier. Even someone as tough as me uses them when facing down the undead. No point taking needless risks, right?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Doubts_00</Key>
    <Value>Ah, there you are! I have an assignment for you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Doubts_01</Key>
    <Value>Chamberlords of the Blue Chamber are headed to Berg for a council meeting. One of the topics of discussion involves us. We need a presence there.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Doubts_02</Key>
    <Value>The tribes of Sirocco want to migrate most of their population to the Hallowed Marsh. Volcanic eruptions have put their primary settlement, Caldera, in grave danger. They're demanding we give up half our land so they can settle here.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_Doubts_a_02</Key>
    <Value>Half the marsh? That sounds unreasonable.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Doubts_03</Key>
    <Value>Obviously we would like to come to a fair arrangement, but Sirroco are being highly aggressive in their demands, and Damian Lockwell is rejecting the discussion completely. Things may get heated.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Doubts_04</Key>
    <Value>I've already sent Zephyrien and Oliele to Berg to watch over our representative, Mathias. I'd feel safer if you went as well.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Doubts_05</Key>
    <Value>&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Go to the Enmerkar forest, and make your way to Berg. There, look for the largest building, the Blue Chamber itself&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Zephyrien will brief you when you get there.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Doubts_06</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName], thank Elatt you're back! When news reached me that Levant attacked Berg and that Zephyrien was killed, I feared the worst.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_Doubts_a_06</Key>
    <Value>Wait, Zephyrien is dead?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Doubts_07</Key>
    <Value>Yes, Cardinal Bourlamaque announced it yesterday. He didn’t give me any details... this is a terrible blow against the Holy Mission...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Doubts_08</Key>
    <Value>The Cardinal announced that Zephyrien was killed, but didn’t give any details. What happened to him? Oliele said that he’d gone missing and you went to look for him.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_Doubts_a_08</Key>
    <Value>He was being consumed by Corruption from a poisoned bullet by the time I found him. Even Elatt couldn't save him.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Doubts_09</Key>
    <Value>Elatt's breath, why? Why would someone do this? I don’t want to believe Sirocco would stoop so low, but I don’t see anyone else with motive to attack the Holy Mission.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Doubts_10</Key>
    <Value>Things aren't well here in Monsoon either... Oliele was arrested as soon as she returned here. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lockwell has her locked up in a room in his home&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Details are thin at the moment, but he's accused her of murder.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_Doubts_a_10</Key>
    <Value>Oliele, a murderer? I doubt that very much.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_Doubts_b_10</Key>
    <Value>That seems suspicious.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_Doubts_c_10</Key>
    <Value>I knew she was trouble.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Doubts_11</Key>
    <Value>His refusal to speak with us about it is even more stern than usual. With the news that Zephyrien was assassinated... I have to wonder if Oliele's imprisonment is another move against the Holy Mission.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Doubts_12</Key>
    <Value>You knew Oliele from when she was in Cierzo. You can use that to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;make Lockwell listen to you&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Speak to him not as a member of the Holy Mission, but rather as a concerned friend and maybe you can reach him.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_Doubts_a_12</Key>
    <Value>Oliele is gone. Lockwell refuses to say anything.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Doubts_13</Key>
    <Value>This is serious trouble. The Cardinal asked Elatt to look for her, and even he can't find her. Her location is shielded from his sight, probably by Lockwell's magic. All we can be sure of is that she has not left the Hallowed Marsh region.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Doubts_14</Key>
    <Value>If she's not in Lockwell's house, and he refuses to say anything, you'll have to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;ask around, see if anyone has seen anything&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Doubts_15</Key>
    <Value>What news, [PlayerName]?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_Doubts_a_15</Key>
    <Value>I got Oliele out. She's running away to Abrassar for a while.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Doubts_16</Key>
    <Value>That may be for the best. Even if you managed to resolve things with Lockwell, I wouldn't trust the man's word at this point. Thank you for looking out for her.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_Doubts_b_16</Key>
    <Value>Nothing yet. I’ll let you know.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Doubts_17</Key>
    <Value>Some more of our people went missing in the swamp. I’m aware that there is an active bandit gang along the Pilgrim Road, but with this latest disappearance... I fear it may be something more sinister…</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Doubts_18</Key>
    <Value>Do you think you could look into it? &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mofat would be able to tell you more&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. He’s the old man in the pointed straw hat in the residential district. He's friends with one of the missing people.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_Doubts_a_18</Key>
    <Value>I’ll look into it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_Doubts_b_18</Key>
    <Value>Any news about Oliele?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Doubts_19</Key>
    <Value>I haven’t heard anything from Oliele yet. I’ll let you know the moment she sends word, [PlayerName].</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Doubts_20</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Doubts_21</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_Doubts_22</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Zephyrien_HM_Doubts_00</Key>
    <Value>I heard about how you handled yourself in that cave of undead. Keep this up and you’re in danger of earning my respect, missionary!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Zephyrien_HM_Doubts_10</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName]? Is that you? Dammit, I can barely see your face... my vision's going all blurry. I'm sorry you have to see me like this.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Zephyrien_HM_Doubts_a_10</Key>
    <Value>What happened?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Zephyrien_HM_Doubts_11</Key>
    <Value>It was a trap, like I thought. There weren't any hostages, just a bunch of guys with swords. As the fight began... Something hit me in the back... It blasted right through my armor... Sounded like one of Levant's firearms.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Zephyrien_HM_Doubts_12</Key>
    <Value>Whatever I was hit with is paralyzing me, I can barely move a muscle…If Elatt's blessing didn't shield me from pain, I don't know if I'd be conscious.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Zephyrien_HM_Doubts_a_12</Key>
    <Value>Zephyrien, the entire area around the bullet hole is covered with throbbing red lumps. There's glowing green veins in them too.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Zephyrien_HM_Doubts_13</Key>
    <Value>Corruption? My body should be able to resist it... Half my body is made of Elatt's light. Why isn't that enough to stop it? Hey, can you check my left arm? It's one made of light. What does it look like? How is it holding up?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Zephyrien_HM_Doubts_a_13</Key>
    <Value>Elatt's name. It's rotting. The light itself is crumbling away.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Zephyrien_HM_Doubts_14</Key>
    <Value>Elatt damn it all. What did that bastard woman hit me with?!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Zephyrien_HM_Doubts_a_14</Key>
    <Value>Who did it?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Zephyrien_HM_Doubts_15</Key>
    <Value>I don't know who she was. I could tell it was a woman with a shield, but she ran away too fast for me to see...And then the paralyzing dose kicked in and I couldn't get up to follow.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Zephyrien_HM_Doubts_16</Key>
    <Value>You have to report this! Get back to Monsoon. Tell Ellinara. Someone’s making a move on the Holy Mission. Tell Soeran... Tell him I'm sorry. Tell him to watch his back.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Zephyrien_HM_Doubts_a_16</Key>
    <Value>I need to get you help.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Zephyrien_HM_Doubts_17</Key>
    <Value>No. If I'm actually being consumed by Corruption, and even Elatt can't stop it, there's no hope for me. Do you know what happens if the Corruption really gets you? If you're lucky, it's a slow death as it overtakes your entire body.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Zephyrien_HM_Doubts_18</Key>
    <Value>If you're unlucky... You survive and end up some quivering monstrous mass of tumors and ooze. I'm a dead man either way. I’d rather die than become twisted into something monstrous like that.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Zephyrien_HM_Doubts_19</Key>
    <Value>Elatt... Let me go. If you can't save me, don't waste your energy. Just... make it quick...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Zephyrien_HM_Doubts_20</Key>
    <Value>(Zephyrien's eyes glow for a moment, then he goes completely still. The oozing lumps stop throbbing and immediately begin to rot away).</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Zephyrien_HM_Doubts_21</Key>
    <Value>(The corrupting rot has eaten most of Zephyrien's body. The Candle Armor itself is ruined. But there's something metal shining in the mass of twisted rotting flesh...)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Zephyrien_HM_Doubts_a_21</Key>
    <Value>(Pull it out)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Zephyrien_HM_Doubts_a_22</Key>
    <Value>(Leave it be)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Zephyrien_HM_Doubts_22</Key>
    <Value>(With great care, you pull it out. It's a sharp spike made of gemstone, with a glass bulb at the other end. Dark, thick liquid clings to the glass. It appears to be some kind of armor piercing poison bullet.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Zephyrien_HM_Doubts_23</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Zephyrien_HM_Doubts_24</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Zephyrien_HM_Doubts_25</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Zephyrien_HM_Doubts_26</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Zephyrien_HM_Doubts_27</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_00</Key>
    <Value>Hey, [PlayerName]. Zephyrien and I are on our way to Berg for a major council meeting. I wonder... Their archives are very detailed. Do they have books on Elatt’s human past, you think?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_03</Key>
    <Value>Thank you, [PlayerName]. I was worried things would get a lot worse.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_04</Key>
    <Value>You have no idea how welcome your face is, [PlayerName]. I couldn't have made it out of that mess alone.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Doubts_a_04</Key>
    <Value>Are you hurt?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_05</Key>
    <Value>No, thank Elatt. But I'm sure they were planning to.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_06</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName]? No. No, I'm just hallucinating...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Doubts_a_06</Key>
    <Value>Oliele, it's me! Wake up!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_07</Key>
    <Value>Really? I'm not... imagining this?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_08</Key>
    <Value>They drugged me with something. They tried to question me... I fought back... They used fire from through the bars... And steel... And...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Doubts_a_08</Key>
    <Value>Dammit, I'm sorry I didn't get here sooner.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_09</Key>
    <Value>I need... water... Clean water...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_10</Key>
    <Value>Ugh... My head is still pounding...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Doubts_a_10</Key>
    <Value>Are you better now? Can you think straight?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_11</Key>
    <Value>I think... I’ll be alright... Most of my torture was done to my arms... This light heals quickly. I think I'll be ok, eventually... I hope.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Doubts_a_11</Key>
    <Value>What happened?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_12</Key>
    <Value>I... I found something in the Berg Archives. I've always been taught that Elatt came from the Hallowed Marsh... He's actually from Abrassar. His family was from Old Levant. They were in very deep with the Cabal of Winds.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_13</Key>
    <Value>His ascension and the arrival of the Scourge... They were nearly at the same time. I think there may be a connection between Elatt and the Scourge and the Cabal of Winds.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_14</Key>
    <Value>I have to wonder if Elatt himself was the source of the Scourge. Is he even the same man he was before his Ascension? Or is he something else who took the man’s name?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_15</Key>
    <Value>I was speaking with some friends about it. Then, one of the older disciples attacked us. He said it was heresy to question Elatt's divinity.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_16</Key>
    <Value>I tried to defend my friends... I picked him up and threw him at a wall. These arms of light are strong. Too strong. I broke his neck. It was an accident, I swear!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_17</Key>
    <Value>I'm going to the Abrassar desert. I don't feel safe going back to Monsoon. Not with Lockwell and... Elatt there. I need to dig up more of Elatt's past…and maybe the truth…</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Doubts_a_16</Key>
    <Value>If you think you need to, go ahead. Let me know if you find the truth you’re looking for.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Doubts_b_16</Key>
    <Value>After revelations like that, I understand. That makes me wonder, too.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Doubts_c_16</Key>
    <Value>What about your duty to Aurai? People are going to die in the coming war. Now is not the time to go digging into Elatt’s past!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_18</Key>
    <Value>Well...I guess this is goodbye for now, [PlayerName]. I hope we meet again before long.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_19</Key>
    <Value>I’ll let you know what I find when I come back. Thank you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_20</Key>
    <Value>I can’t keep working under Elatt’s name with these questions hanging over me. I have to go. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tell Ellinara for me&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_21</Key>
    <Value>Oh! This is a surprise. I’m still looking, [PlayerName]. I’ll let you know when I have a promising lead.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_22</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName]? Thank Elatt. There’s been an attack. Some mercenaries from Levant used a bomb to blow their way into the Blue Chamber from the archives room below!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_22-b</Key>
    <Value>They took hostages and killed an ambassador in front of everyone! Sagard Battleborn just convinced the rest of the Chamberlords to declare war on Levant in retaliation!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Doubts_a_22</Key>
    <Value>I wish Elinara had sent me sooner. She had a feeling something might happen.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_23</Key>
    <Value>It gets worse. Just before the explosion happened, Zephyrien ran off. He said something about hearing that Sirocco’s Chamberlord had been kidnapped. He’s been missing for 3 days now!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Doubts_a_23</Key>
    <Value>What do we do? Someone has to bring this information back to Monsoon!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_24</Key>
    <Value>I know. I was going to go back myself, but someone needs to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;look for Zephyrien&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. I’m sure something has happened to him...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_25</Key>
    <Value>Can I ask you to go look for him, [PlayerName]? I’m a fast runner, I probably can make it back to Monsoon with this news faster than you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_Doubts_a_25</Key>
    <Value>Where should I start looking?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_26</Key>
    <Value>I think I heard Zephyrien say something about “&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bug-men&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; in the South” before he charged off. Maybe he &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;asked around at the Inn too&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, they may know more.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_27</Key>
    <Value>Well, I’m off. Good luck with your search, and watch yourself out there. The ones who committed this attack may still be out there and looking for trouble.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_Doubts_28</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>PrisonNote_HM_Doubts_22</Key>
    <Value>Extract any information about Elatt's weaknesses from the prisoner that you can. Failing that, test the durability of any part of her body that's made of light. In doing so, we may find out what Elatt is truly capable of.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyrill_HM_Doubts_00</Key>
    <Value>Well, a missionary from the Holy Mission! Keep the forest free from the Scourge for us, will you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyrill_HM_Doubts_04</Key>
    <Value>I can’t believe Levant would dare attack the Blue Chamber. And in the middle of a council meeting!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Alemmon_HM_Doubts_01</Key>
    <Value>Something on your mind, [PlayerName]?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Alemmon_HM_Doubts_a_01</Key>
    <Value>Lockwell had Oliele moved. Did you hear anything about what happened?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Alemmon_HM_Doubts_02</Key>
    <Value>Perhaps. I noticed Lockwell's guard coming back from the Marsh the other day, with an empty bag over his shoulder. I've seen him make other trips like this, usually to the old ruined city in the south-west of the swamp.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_Doubts_01</Key>
    <Value>Well done, [PlayerName].</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elatt_HM_Doubts_a_01</Key>
    <Value>How can you say "Well Done"? Zephyrien is dead and Oliele ran away to Abrassar!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elatt_HM_Doubts_b_01</Key>
    <Value>You're fine with Oliele just leaving like that?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_Doubts_02</Key>
    <Value>Oliele must find her own answers. And though I worry what she might discover, I have faith that the best interests of Aurai are in her heart. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elatt_HM_Doubts_a_02</Key>
    <Value>You put your faith in her even though she doubts you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_Doubts_03</Key>
    <Value>Doubt is the first step to understanding. Understanding is the first step to trust. As long as she acts with Aurai's good in mind, that's all that matters to me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elatt_HM_Doubts_b_02</Key>
    <Value>What about the Disciple she killed?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_Doubts_04</Key>
    <Value>Some of them have become complacent in their faith. After I chose Richard to become a Disciple, he became... dogmatic. He preferred to follow the letter of the faith but not the heart... Despite my repeated warnings, his pride grew too large, and it cost him his life.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elatt_HM_Doubts_a_04</Key>
    <Value>Couldn’t you just take away his promotion, if he was no longer worthy of it?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_Doubts_04-b</Key>
    <Value>If only I could. Once I bestow my power on someone, I can no longer take it back. Not without killing them. Even gods are capable of mistakes, and when we do, the consequences are never pleasant.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_Doubts_05</Key>
    <Value>Such is the curse of divinity. I can impact the world greatly, but every move is dangerous the moment it's out of my hands. With Zephyrien gone, things will only get harder.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elatt_HM_Doubts_a_05</Key>
    <Value>Couldn't you have saved Zephyrien, like you saved Oliele?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_Doubts_06</Key>
    <Value>The poison that he was struck with contained more than just venom. It held Corruption so strong that even I could only slow its progress through Zephyrien's body. It was all I could to do keep him alive until you arrived.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_Doubts_07</Key>
    <Value>There is great danger in our future. I will bestow upon you a blessing, to better protect you, and those you care for. Take which you believe will make you most effective.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_Doubts_08</Key>
    <Value>Choose between two blessings. My Spiritual Communion increases the power of your Ethereal, Decay and Light abilities. Or, gain my Divine Assistance, which shall let you fight and cast spells with more ease.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elatt_HM_Doubts_a_06</Key>
    <Value>I will receive the Spiritual Communion.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elatt_HM_Doubts_a_07</Key>
    <Value>I request your Divine Assistance.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_Doubts_09</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_Doubts_10</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_Doubts_01</Key>
    <Value>I’m shocked to hear about what happened to Zephyrien. He was an impressive fighter, and a friend to all. To hear that he was slain...This is a grave blow to all who follow Elatt.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Mofat_HM_Doubts_a_01</Key>
    <Value>This was the bullet that killed Zephyrien. What can you tell me about it?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_Doubts_02</Key>
    <Value>Give me a moment. I'll get my alchemy set and I'll let you know what I find out.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_Doubts_03</Key>
    <Value>This is a puzzle, [PlayerName]. The liquid is a mixture of Assassin Bug venom, and carefully distilled blood from an Immaculate, one of the man-like Scourge Beasts that can think and reason. I think the venom is designed to paralyze the victim, while the Immaculate's blood is the real killer.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_Doubts_04</Key>
    <Value>Assassin bugs only live in Abrassar desert, and only Sorobor would have the knowledge and equipment to distill something as dangerous as Scourge Beast blood to this level.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_Doubts_05</Key>
    <Value>To make things more complicated, this tsar stone bullet casing was clearly forged in the magma forges in Sirroco. Nothing else could have penetrated Zephyrien's Candle Armor so cleanly.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_Doubts_06</Key>
    <Value>So that's the Kingdom of Levant, the Immaculates, Sirroco, and Sorobor all possibly tied to the killing bullet…</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_Doubts_07</Key>
    <Value>Any of them or all of them. Watch your back, my friend. Either someone has begun to make a move against the Holy Mission, or we’re being used as pawns in someone’s game.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_Doubts_08</Key>
    <Value>I’ve been alive for a very long time, and I never seen a Council meeting that could harm the Holy Mission’s interests so much…</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_Doubts_09</Key>
    <Value>The fact we have our own Chamberlord, Mathias, in Berg almost full-time does reassure me. I just hope he’s adept enough at playing politics to help us sidestep this crisis.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Lockwell_HM_Doubts_01</Key>
    <Value>If this is about that woman I locked up, I’m not changing my mind. Until my investigation is complete, she does not leave that cell.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Lockwell_HM_Doubts_a_01</Key>
    <Value>I'm here as her friend. We grew up together. I’m worried about her treatment here.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Lockwell_HM_Doubts_02</Key>
    <Value>Ah. I understand. Unfortunately, that doesn’t change the fact that she’s here under suspicion of murder. You’ll just have to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;wait until we’re done our investigation&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. If it turns out it really was self-defense, we’ll let her go.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Lockwell_HM_Doubts_a_02</Key>
    <Value>How about I speed that investigation along with some silver?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Lockwell_HM_Doubts_03</Key>
    <Value>Are you trying to bribe me? I suggest you think very hard about that decision.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Lockwell_HM_Doubts_a_03</Key>
    <Value>Here, I think 500 silvers should hire you a few more investigators.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Lockwell_HM_Doubts_b_03</Key>
    <Value>Think of the improvements to Monsoon you could make with 200 silvers.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Lockwell_HM_Doubts_c_03</Key>
    <Value>100 silvers should cover her bail, right?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Lockwell_HM_Doubts_d_03</Key>
    <Value>How does 50 silvers sound?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Lockwell_HM_Doubts_04</Key>
    <Value>Have you lost your mind? Why would I agree to this? Out with you, before I have you arrested for trying to bribe an official!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Lockwell_HM_Doubts_05</Key>
    <Value>My my, she must really mean a lot to you... Alright, I'll take it. I know a good deal when I see one.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Lockwell_HM_Doubts_06</Key>
    <Value>Hmm... alright, I'll take it. I'll forget that you bribed me, this time. But I won't forget you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Lockwell_HM_Doubts_b_02</Key>
    <Value>You owe me, Lockwell. Let her go. It's not worth starting trouble over a self-defense case.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Lockwell_HM_Doubts_07</Key>
    <Value>Well, I am a man of my word. Fine. The evidence was clear enough anyway.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Lockwell_HM_Doubts_c_02</Key>
    <Value>Let her go. Now. Or else.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Lockwell_HM_Doubts_08</Key>
    <Value>Or else what? Do you honestly think you can threaten a Chamberlord?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Lockwell_HM_Doubts_a_08</Key>
    <Value>If you threaten a member of the Holy Mission, you threaten all of us.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Lockwell_HM_Doubts_09</Key>
    <Value>Excuse me? This is my city. Not Elatt's. He's just squatting here. I am the one who rules Monsoon!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Lockwell_HM_Doubts_b_08</Key>
    <Value>Do you really want to anger the god that was able to destroy the Scourge?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Lockwell_HM_Doubts_10</Key>
    <Value>And do you really believe that he would dare ruin his precious image by harming to me? All for one lowly missionary?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Lockwell_HM_Doubts_a_10</Key>
    <Value>We are all important to him. Punishing one Chamberlord for overstepping his bounds wouldn’t be out of line for him.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Lockwell_HM_Doubts_11</Key>
    <Value>And I don't think he would. I'll take my chances, thank you. Consider your bluff called.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Lockwell_HM_Doubts_a_11</Key>
    <Value>He doesn't need to. He could use this incident as a reason to revoke his protection over Monsoon and let the Scourge punish you instead.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Lockwell_HM_Doubts_12</Key>
    <Value>Tch. I can’t take that chance. The people will not come to harm by my hand while I rule Monsoon.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Lockwell_HM_Doubts_a_12</Key>
    <Value>Someone killed one of his champions, and now you're holding a missionary on flimsy charges. This makes you look mighty suspicious, Lockwell.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Lockwell_HM_Doubts_13</Key>
    <Value>I don't care. Someone is dead in my city, and I'm not going to let the culprit go until we've had a proper investigation. End of story. Even Elatt should understand that.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Lockwell_HM_Doubts_b_12</Key>
    <Value>We respect your right to rule Monsoon... but if you keep pushing us like this, you will find that all of Monsoon will turn on you. Elatt will see to it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Lockwell_HM_Doubts_14</Key>
    <Value>I can’t take that risk... but don’t think your precious “god” can get away with this extortion forever. If he thinks he can just eliminate our free will, he will find that Aurai will prove him wrong.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Lockwell_HM_Doubts_15</Key>
    <Value>Fine. You win, you ruthless bastard. I won't forget this degrading talk, [PlayerName].</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Lockwell_HM_Doubts_16</Key>
    <Value>Your threats don't scare me. I'm not going to let her go. And I'm not going to forget what you said to me. You’ve made a very powerful enemy today.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Lockwell_HM_Doubts_17</Key>
    <Value>&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Take her and get out&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. The evidence was pretty clear anyway. She killed that disciple in self-defense.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Lockwell_HM_Doubts_18</Key>
    <Value>Oliele? I'm afraid I don't know what you're talking about. I let her go already. Perhaps you just missed her?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Lockwell_HM_Doubts_a_18</Key>
    <Value>I'll go look for her, then.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Lockwell_HM_Doubts_b_18</Key>
    <Value>You and I both know that you're lying.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Lockwell_HM_Doubts_19</Key>
    <Value>Making accusations without proof? How very like someone serving that freakish spectral fiend. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Oliele isn't here, you can see for yourself&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>HouseGuard_HM_Doubts_01</Key>
    <Value>What's with that look, priest?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_HouseGuard_HM_Doubts_a_01</Key>
    <Value>Missionary, actually. Where's Oliele?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>HouseGuard_HM_Doubts_02</Key>
    <Value>The girl with the glowing arms and eyes? No idea. Nope. She’s not serving her sentence here anymore.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_HouseGuard_HM_Doubts_a_02</Key>
    <Value>Will 50 silvers jog your memory?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>HouseGuard_HM_Doubts_03</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>HouseGuard_HM_Doubts_04</Key>
    <Value>Alright, you didn't hear this from me. There's &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;the ruins of an old city in the swamp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. It's kind of to the South West. I just dropped her off...from there some other guys took her. They can't gotten that far…</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_HouseGuard_HM_Doubts_b_02</Key>
    <Value>With 90 silvers jog your memory?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>HouseGuard_HM_Doubts_05</Key>
    <Value>Oh... That's a lot of silver. Alright, listen. There's &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;the ruins of an old city in the swamp along the Pilgrim Road&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. It's kind of to the south west. There’s this &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Flooded Cellar&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; that Lockwell sometimes asks me to move prisoners to.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>HouseGuard_HM_Doubts_06</Key>
    <Value>Look, I do this with prisoners from time to time. Lockwell pays me extra to drug the prisoners and make the transfers as long as I don't ask too many questions. I don't know what happens at their destination and frankly I don't care.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>HouseGuard_HM_Doubts_07</Key>
    <Value>Sorry, I’m not allowed to let anyone talk to the prisoner. Shoo, would you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_HouseGuard_HM_Doubts_a_08</Key>
    <Value>You look like you haven’t eaten well for a while. Lockwell not paying you enough?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>HouseGuard_HM_Doubts_09</Key>
    <Value>I broke my mace on the last trip I made into the marsh. When you have to choose between self-defense or rationing dinner, self-defense always wins. I could really use a pay raise...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>HouseGuard_HM_Doubts_10</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>HouseGuard_HM_Doubts_11</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>HouseGuard_HM_Doubts_12</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>CrimeSceneGuards_HM_Doubts_01</Key>
    <Value>Keep your distance, an investigation is in progress!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>PlayerCrimeSceneGuards_HM_Doubts_a_01</Key>
    <Value>What’s going on?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>PlayerCrimeSceneGuards_HM_Doubts_b_01</Key>
    <Value>I’ll leave you to it, then.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>CrimeSceneGuards_HM_Doubts_02</Key>
    <Value>There was a murder. A missionary from the Holy Mission killed a disciple in broad daylight. Until the matter is resolved, the accused will remain in the custody of Damian Lockwell. If you have further questions, &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;speak with Ellinara&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>PlayerCrimeSceneGuards_HM_Doubts_a_02</Key>
    <Value>Who is the suspect?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>CrimeSceneGuards_HM_Doubts_03</Key>
    <Value>That woman with body parts made of light. Oliele, I think her name is.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>PlayerCrimeSceneGuards_HM_Doubts_b_02</Key>
    <Value>Who was the victim?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>CrimeSceneGuards_HM_Doubts_04</Key>
    <Value>Richard. He was one of the newer disciples of the Holy Mission. Wouldn’t stop being a preachy git at the inn ever since he got promoted. He’d just gotten back from a trip to Sirroco before this happened.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>PlayerCrimeSceneGuards_HM_Doubts_a_04</Key>
    <Value>Wait, Oliele?! I don’t believe that.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>CrimeSceneGuards_HM_Doubts_05</Key>
    <Value>We have about 8 witnesses who testify that she did it. Most of them claim that it was self-defense, but Damian Lockwell has ordered us to treat it like a murder while we investigate.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>CrimeSceneGuards_HM_Doubts_06</Key>
    <Value>Again, if you have any questions, &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;speak with Ellinara&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. We are just doing our job here!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>CrimeSceneGuards_HM_Doubts_07</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>NoteforZeph_HM_Doubts_01</Key>
    <Value>“Zephyrien has been eliminated. We’ve left him in the old crypt under the tree on the island on the lake.”</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_TRUTH_01</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName], Elatt needs your strength again.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_TRUTH_02</Key>
    <Value>He needs you to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;go find Oliele in the Abrassar desert&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. He believes she is on the verge of an important discovery, and that she will need your help to complete it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_TRUTH_a_02</Key>
    <Value>Why me?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_TRUTH_03</Key>
    <Value>Because she trusts you. She would see anyone else from the Holy Mission as a threat.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_TRUTH_b_02</Key>
    <Value>Why should we care about her? She left us.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_TRUTH_04</Key>
    <Value>Even a lost sheep is still one of the flock. Elatt says she needs help. So we will help her. That's how it goes.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_TRUTH_c_02</Key>
    <Value>Alright, I'm on it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_TRUTH_05</Key>
    <Value>&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Oliele should be in the slums of Levant&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, in the Abrassar desert. It's a difficult journey. Prepare yourself for the desert heat.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_TRUTH_06</Key>
    <Value>You've accomplished a lot in such a short time, Missionary. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cardinal Bourlamaque wanted to see you&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. I think you'll be working under him from now on. Congratulations on your promotion!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_TRUTH_07</Key>
    <Value>You need someone who can translate the Old Language for you? I remember that &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sorobor recently unearthed something that could be of use...And Mofat was alive back before the Scourge&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, so it’s likely he remembers the Old Language.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_TRUTH_08</Key>
    <Value>You’re looking for some of our members who have doubts? I do know there was a group that was talking a lot recently... I think they went out to a cave connected to one of the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;giant lotus plants&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; in the Marsh.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_TRUTH_09</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_TRUTH_10</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_TRUTH_11</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_01</Key>
    <Value>Even far out here, I feel Elatt's eyes fixed on me. Nowhere feels safe for me anymore.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_02</Key>
    <Value>Elatt sent you, didn't he, [PlayerName]? To keep an eye on me?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_TRUTH_a_02</Key>
    <Value>I'm here to help you with your search. Ellinara said you were close to discovering something.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_TRUTH_b_02</Key>
    <Value>Don't think I'm happy about this long trip either, Oliele. How goes the search?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_03</Key>
    <Value>I've managed to dig up three leads on Elatt's origins. An ancient Garden, the Old Levant Ruins, and the Stone Titan's cave. Any of them might have what we're looking for.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_04</Key>
    <Value>The ancient Garden is within sight of Levant itself. It's the only place where anything still grows out here. If it's the only place the devastation didn't touch... There must be a reason.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_05</Key>
    <Value>Secondly, there are the ruins of Old Levant, where Elatt was born. They may still have records of his mortal life. Abrassar's Vigil was built above it, so there's an easy landmark for us to use to get there.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_06</Key>
    <Value>Finally, there's the Stone Titan's Cave. The giant stone statues that the cave is named for only appeared around the time the Scourge happened. It's too strange to be a coincidence.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_06-b</Key>
    <Value>Where should we check next?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_TRUTH_a_06</Key>
    <Value>Let's check the garden.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_07</Key>
    <Value>I'll meet you there, then. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;You can see it from the front gate of Levant, it's not too far&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_TRUTH_b_06</Key>
    <Value>Old Levant sounds like the best lead.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_08</Key>
    <Value>I agree. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;It's right next to Abrassar's Vigil&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, so it shouldn't be too hard to find. The soroborean merchant said the front gate should be unlocked now too! See you there!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_TRUTH_c_06</Key>
    <Value>I'm mighty curious about the Stone Titan's Cave.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_09</Key>
    <Value>Yes, me too. It's not too far from Old Levant. When you &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;start seeing enormous stone statues, you'll know you're in the right place&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Well, I'm off.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_10</Key>
    <Value>This is interesting... Elatt actually has nothing to do with this Garden. There was a Lich that used to live here. His protective spells are what keep the Garden growing after the great river of Abrassar was diverted away.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_11</Key>
    <Value>This Lich left records suggesting that he used to feed on a Ley Line that crossed under the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Stone Titan's Cave&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; , but that it was destroyed around the time the Scourge appeared. That might be a good place to explore…</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_12</Key>
    <Value>I had no idea Sorobor was excavating these ruins. Although there’s plenty of evidence there were bandits recently camping here... Either way, I found some historical information here.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_TRUTH_a_12</Key>
    <Value>What did you find?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_13</Key>
    <Value>Elatt lived a pretty interesting life. He changed a lot from from his younger days. He abandoned his powerful family over some... frankly tragic business and that was the last anyone here saw of him.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_14</Key>
    <Value>These records show that there used to be a Ley Line under where the &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Stone Titan’s cave&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; is now. The day that the Scourge happened, mages from Old Levant felt the Ley Line swell and then be destroyed...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_15</Key>
    <Value>The coincidences just keep piling up around that cave. For an entire Ley Line to vanish... Something powerful must have happened there. It might be a good place to go examine next.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_16</Key>
    <Value>I think we've really hit it big, [PlayerName]. Something terrible happened here, I can sense it in the air. And I've found this tablet. It's in the Old Language. I can't read it. But right there... that's Elatt's name in the text, I think. Dammit, if only we could read the rest!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_TRUTH_a_16</Key>
    <Value>Do we know anyone who can translate this?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_17</Key>
    <Value>Let's take this &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;back to Monsoon&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. I'm positive someone can get it done there. I’ll meet you back there.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_18</Key>
    <Value>If anyone's got a way to &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;translate this, it would be a Soroborean... or if we knew someone extremely old... Mofat&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;! He said he knew Elatt when He was still human, right?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_TRUTH_a_18</Key>
    <Value>You're right, the man is ancient. He might know how to translate the Old Language.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_18-b</Key>
    <Value>If Mofat won’t do it for us, we can try the local Soroborean merchant, although I can’t imagine they’d sell any solution to our problem for cheap.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_19-a</Key>
    <Value>You’ve got what we need? Wonderful, let’s find out what this tablet has to say!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_19</Key>
    <Value>I don't understand. The Scourge destroyed so much of Aurai... If it was supposed to kill only Elatt, then how come it didn't? How come it caused the very ground around him to explode and give birth to the Scourge Beasts, and ascended Elatt to godhood?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_20</Key>
    <Value>Elatt... Did he cause this calamity on purpose? Did the spell fail? Is Elatt himself part of the Scourge? What happened? I wish I could just ask him.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_TRUTH_a_20</Key>
    <Value>Then why don’t we? He wanted to hear what we discovered either way.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_21</Key>
    <Value>Yes. I think we should. I think we have enough to question him about. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;I'm going to his Altar in the temple&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_22</Key>
    <Value>Elatt, what are you? The Cabal of Winds used a spell to kill you. Designed to fill your spirit with Corruption and turn it against you. And yet you live on as a god, and the Scourge struck Aurai instead. Are you really the man that was struck by that spell?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_23</Key>
    <Value>I understand. I'm sorry I doubted you, Elatt. I shouldn't have questioned your motives.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_24</Key>
    <Value>I'll find them, Elatt. I'll set them straight again. [PlayerName], let's split up, we'll cover ground faster.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_25</Key>
    <Value>I'm having trouble convincing them on my own... We need your voice, [PlayerName].</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_26</Key>
    <Value>I'm glad we were able to talk sense into them. The more people who can understand and accept the truth, the better. You're a pretty good speaker, [PlayerName].</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_27</Key>
    <Value>It's a shame they didn't see eye to eye with us. I'm sorry to see them go. Still, it is their decision to make.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_TRUTH_a_27</Key>
    <Value>What will you do?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_28</Key>
    <Value>I'm going to stay with the Holy Mission. The end goal for me is the complete destruction of the Scourge, and I feel like we just got a few steps closer. This revelation doesn't change that.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_29-A</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_29</Key>
    <Value>So, this is the true face of the Holy Mission. Words and hopes and dreams... and if you don't accept them, you're put to death. I can't stay here. I'm done.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_TRUTH_a_29</Key>
    <Value>You're leaving the Holy Mission?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_30</Key>
    <Value>Yes. I joined Elatt's cause to help and save others. I wanted to put an end to the Scourge. After today... I think I can do far better on my own..</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_31</Key>
    <Value>Here. Take my sword. You'll make better use of this than I will.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_32</Key>
    <Value>You've been a true friend to me, [PlayerName]. Thank you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_33</Key>
    <Value>Here. I want you to have this. I think I’ll make myself a new one in commemoration of my rebirth. I want to start over now that I’m certain of my path in life.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_34</Key>
    <Value>The cardinal wanted to promote me to Templar for what we did. I told him to wait. I’m no longer sure if I want to pursue the martial path or the philosopher’s path.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_35</Key>
    <Value>On one hand, I want to change the world with my words. On the other I want to destroy the Scourge with my own two hands if I can... It’s a hard decision to make.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_TRUTH_d_06</Key>
    <Value>Let’s regroup in Levant, I need supplies.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_37</Key>
    <Value>Good idea. I’ll &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;meet you back in the Levant Slums&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, [PlayerName].</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_38</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_39</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_TRUTH_40</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_TRUTH_00</Key>
    <Value>Ach, the old ache in my neck is acting up again. I suppose even Elatt’s many blessings can’t cure all the symptoms of extreme old age.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Mofat_HM_TRUTH_a_00</Key>
    <Value>You’ve been around since before the Scourge, right? Do you still know how to read the Old Language? Oliele and I found this ancient tablet we need translated.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_TRUTH_01</Key>
    <Value>I'm a little rusty, but I can probably help with... Elatt's breath... Are you sure you want to know what this thing says? It's... terrible.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Mofat_HM_TRUTH_a_01</Key>
    <Value>Oliele and I need to know.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_TRUTH_02</Key>
    <Value>I don't know if I'm comfortable sharing this knowledge with someone I barely know. I'm sorry, you'll have to find someone else to do it for you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_TRUTH_03</Key>
    <Value>Alright. I trust that you wouldn’t be asking if it wasn’t important. Give me a minute.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_TRUTH_04</Key>
    <Value>There. Done. I suggest &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;you and Oliele sit down when you read this&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; and brace yourselves for some ugly ancient history.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_TRUTH_05</Key>
    <Value>I’m worried about those younger missionaries... They were attacked not long ago by another disciple for daring to doubt Elatt, and now they’re missing.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_TRUTH_06</Key>
    <Value>Even though I’ve spoken to the older disciples about keeping their personal beliefs in check, I fear that someone may have gone after them again.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_TRUTH_07</Key>
    <Value>I don’t understand them. Elatt does not want dogmatic believers, he wants results! He does not measure worth by one’s beliefs, but rather by one’s actions.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorobor_HM_TRUTH_01</Key>
    <Value>Hey there, looking for something specific?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Sorobor_HM_TRUTH_a_01</Key>
    <Value>Do you have anything that might let us translate the Old Language?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorobor_HM_TRUTH_02</Key>
    <Value>Old Language, eh? Actually, I think I do. An explorer recently turned in an ancient peace treaty that was made about 80 years ago. It's written in the Old Language on one side and a rough form of the New Language on the other.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorobor_HM_TRUTH_03</Key>
    <Value>I've got a parchment copy of it right here, actually. You can use this to translate from one language to the other. It's yours for 150 Silver.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorobor_HM_TRUTH_04</Key>
    <Value>Deal! &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Good luck with your translation job&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorobor_HM_TRUTH_05</Key>
    <Value>Well, that's the price that the Headmaster decided, and he said not to adjust it. Sorry, but I can't give you a better deal than that.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorobor_HM_TRUTH_06</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Tablet_HM_TRUTH_01</Key>
    <Value>(You and Oliele sit and begin to translate the tablet... As you work, the truth becomes eerily clear.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Tablet_HM_TRUTH_02</Key>
    <Value>“Elatt must be stopped. People turn from our teachings, believing in the power of mankind over the Five Winds that have guided us since before the first dawn. They elevate him above his mortal self. This folly must be brought to heel. Only we have the right to guide humanity, as the Winds decree.”</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Tablet_HM_TRUTH_03</Key>
    <Value>“We cannot stop Elatt in the physical realm, he is too strong and too well guarded. The High Priestess has woven a spell that will deal with him from a distance, something he cannot defend against. A divine lesson, that no mortal can be greater than the Winds that blow within us all.”</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Tablet_HM_TRUTH_04</Key>
    <Value>“We will force his Inside Wind to turn against him, and put his spirit at war with itself. It will be a Scourge against his entire being, as his spiritual agony fills him with Corruption that will utterly consume him.”</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Tablet_HM_TRUTH_05</Key>
    <Value>“To forcibly twist someone's self in such a way will require an incredible amount of Mana. We will need to divert the entirety of Abrassar's Ley Line into the focal point of the spell. With the very essence of Aurai fueling the spell, I foresee only success.”</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Tablet_HM_TRUTH_06</Key>
    <Value>“He will either die immediately from such Corruption, or he will be turned into a mad, monstrous beast that all will rally to destroy. May the Wind of Fury guide our effort, so that none forget that no human should be considered more than mere flesh at the mercy of the Winds of Aurai.”</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_TRUTH_00</Key>
    <Value>(You and Oliele reach out to catch Elatt’s attention. He responds surprisingly swiftly.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_TRUTH_01</Key>
    <Value>I sense great urgency in your hearts. Speak. What is your need?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_TRUTH_02</Key>
    <Value>Ah... So things are finally made clear to me... The Cabal of Winds was fearful. As I read your mind, I feel the sorrow that pushed the Cabal to slay me with such a powerful ritual.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elatt_HM_TRUTH_a_02</Key>
    <Value>Wait, you didn't know?!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_TRUTH_03</Key>
    <Value>I knew that the Cabal of Winds tried to kill me. I suspected why. But I did not know their method. So, they used the strength of a Ley Line to twist Aurai’s Mana into a weapon to turn my spirit against itself...This is the last piece of the puzzle I was missing.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_TRUTH_04</Key>
    <Value>All I knew was that as I travelled through the place we now call the Gates of Catharsis, I was struck with great pain. I withdrew into myself, felt myself be consumed from within by my own spirit. I meditated and stood my ground against the spell, believing that I could unite myself again.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_TRUTH_05</Key>
    <Value>I refused to die. My mind expanded and escaped its mortal shell and I was turned into what I am now. Living Thought. My body, however... It was truly and utterly destroyed, and from it burst a flood of Corruption that devastated the land around me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_TRUTH_06</Key>
    <Value>All manner of plants and animals were bathed in that Corruption and they became twisted monsters. The Scourge Beasts. Imbued with one single purpose. My death. But... I could no longer die. So they rampaged against all life, desperate to accomplish their purpose.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_TRUTH_07</Key>
    <Value>If I had known that by surviving their spell I would have unleashed such horror on Aurai, then I would have gladly chosen death. But now... knowing what they did... It helps me to understand why I am what I have become. Why I feel like I am part of Aurai itself now.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_TRUTH_08</Key>
    <Value>So, the key to Divinity is an unbreakable will in the face of death, fueled by an incredible source of Mana. To resist the very end of your spirit, and to transcend oblivion. I wonder...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_TRUTH_09</Key>
    <Value>We should try not to let this knowledge spread too far, too quickly. It would rock the very foundations of Aurai. Knowledge this dangerous should be revealed very carefully.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_TRUTH_10</Key>
    <Value>Do not be sorry. Only from doubt and questions can we learn. And only from learning can we reach understanding. Thank you for unearthing this truth. Now, there is something you must put to rest, Oliele.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_TRUTH_11</Key>
    <Value>The priests with whom you shared your doubts are &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;gathering in a lotus in the swamp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Soeran seeks them. I sense danger... You should &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;hurry to find them&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Help them to understand, as you have.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_TRUTH_12</Key>
    <Value>Welcome, Champion.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elatt_HM_TRUTH_a_12</Key>
    <Value>I'm a Champion now? Straight from Missionary? Just like that?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_TRUTH_13</Key>
    <Value>I see no reason for you to waste your time as a Templar, when the rank of Champion suits you better. You are not only a worthy fighter, but one who knows when you can win a conflict without the need for force.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_TRUTH_14</Key>
    <Value>Your grasp of the Three Pillars is strong. Continue to live by them, and you will be more than worthy of your title, [PlayerName]. Now go forth, Champion. Aurai has need of you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_TRUTH_15</Key>
    <Value>(The warmth of a bonfire roars within you. The power of a Champion is now yours!)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_TRUTH_16</Key>
    <Value>The loss of Oliele is a deep one. She had such potential... However, it is not my place to judge her decisions. She has chosen her path and will serve Aurai in her own way.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_TRUTH_17</Key>
    <Value>My cause needs strong people, capable of handling the violent world we find ourselves in. May you continue to rise to the challenge, Templar.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_TRUTH_18</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorean_HM_TRUTH_01</Key>
    <Value>They're too far gone for me to reason with. I'm worried they might become violent. We've been discussing their unfounded beliefs for hours now. If you can convince them, please, do it. I don't want bloodshed here today.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorean_HM_TRUTH_02</Key>
    <Value>And so we had to resort to violence. May they find their ancestors and rest in peace.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorean_HM_TRUTH_03</Key>
    <Value>You have a silver tongue, [PlayerName]. I’m impressed that you managed to make them see reason. We could use someone like you to fill the gap that Zephyrien left behind!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorean_HM_TRUTH_04</Key>
    <Value>I’m glad we could avoid bloodshed. It’s a shame that they felt they had to leave, but such is their choice.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rebels_HM_TRUTH_01</Key>
    <Value>Another one? Are you gathering an army to put us down before we spread this "heresy" any further? Is that it?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rebels_HM_TRUTH_a_01</Key>
    <Value>We're not here to hurt you. We just want to talk.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rebels_HM_TRUTH_02</Key>
    <Value>Then start talking. The world needs to know about Elatt and his connection to the Scourge. We think he may have caused it himself. Why else would they originate from the same place he was travelling?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rebels_HM_TRUTH_a_02</Key>
    <Value>The Cabal of Winds saw Elatt as a threat, and tried to kill him. In doing so, they unleashed the Scourge.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rebels_HM_TRUTH_03</Key>
    <Value>Well, it's awfully convenient that the people he’s accusing of causing the Scourge are his primary competition for believers! And you expect me to believe that the Scourge only appeared because the Cabal tried to kill him?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rebels_HM_TRUTH_b_02</Key>
    <Value>The Scourge is a plague that corrupts Aurai itself! He was just in the wrong place.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rebels_HM_TRUTH_04</Key>
    <Value>Do you really think you can lie to me? I refuse to believe that this was a coincidence. Elatt either caused the Scourge himself, or he did not do enough to prevent it! He should have protected us even if it meant his mortal death!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rebels_HM_TRUTH_c_02</Key>
    <Value>The Scourge spell was designed by Elatt's enemies specifically to kill only him. By refusing to die, he became Living Thought, and the Scourge burst from him.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rebels_HM_TRUTH_05</Key>
    <Value>You believe that the tribes that feared his influence would go that far? ... Actually, I do believe they might. Fear of change spurs us to do terrible things. But even so, you're saying that Elatt's refusal to be killed by the Scourge spell is what unleashed them?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rebels_HM_TRUTH_06</Key>
    <Value>Then why didn't he let himself die, rather than unleash the Scourge upon us all?! </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rebels_HM_TRUTH_a_06</Key>
    <Value>If you were attacked with a spell designed to kill you, wouldn't you fight back? </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rebels_HM_TRUTH_07</Key>
    <Value>Elatt was the wisest human to walk Aurai, and you think he wouldn't think of the consequences of his actions, even when in danger? I refuse to believe he’d be that careless.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rebels_HM_TRUTH_b_06</Key>
    <Value>Remember, Elatt was human. He still thinks a lot like one. Humans make mistakes. We act on instinct when we're in danger.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rebels_HM_TRUTH_08</Key>
    <Value>Instinct does control us all in our most desperate moments. I suppose even gods-to-be can make mistakes when they face a life-threatening crisis.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rebels_HM_TRUTH_c_06</Key>
    <Value>How was he supposed to know that by resisting, it would blow up half the region? Have you ever heard of spell with that kind of power?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rebels_HM_TRUTH_09</Key>
    <Value>Elatt was a master spellcaster, he should have easily understood the nature of the spell he was struck with…</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rebels_HM_TRUTH_10</Key>
    <Value>And what about the Vigils? I used to believe that they were a necessary cruelty, but if Elatt and the Scourge are connected like this, why can't he just drive the beasts away?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rebels_HM_TRUTH_a_10</Key>
    <Value>The only connection that remains is their desire to kill him. Forcing them to flee by using the Vigils is the only thing he can do.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rebels_HM_TRUTH_11</Key>
    <Value>He's destroyed Scourge before using his own light...I find it hard to believe that he's suddenly lost the ability to do that! He should be doing more to stop the Scourge!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rebels_HM_TRUTH_b_10</Key>
    <Value>He may be a god, but his powers are not unlimited. The Vigils are a temporary fix until he finds a permanent way to end the Scourge.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rebels_HM_TRUTH_12</Key>
    <Value>His powers are... limited? I suppose even as a god, he did come from a human spirit. It would explain why he does not see everything all the time, and why he rarely contacts anyone personally. I can believe that.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rebels_HM_TRUTH_c_10</Key>
    <Value>Self-improvement and discipline. We need to overcome the Scourge ourselves or we’d depend on him for everything.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rebels_HM_TRUTH_13</Key>
    <Value>I lost my father to a Scourge Beast, am I supposed to accept that it was anything other than senseless? I refuse. Suffering is senseless, and if Elatt doesn't agree, then he's just full of himself!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rebels_HM_TRUTH_14</Key>
    <Value>I'm... willing to rethink my stance. We've gone from being certain we were right about Elatt's true nature, back to doubts again... Until we find our answers, I think I'm willing to go back to the Holy Mission.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rebels_HM_TRUTH_15</Key>
    <Value>I can't accept this. If this was the truth, Elatt should have told us all from the beginning. I can't put my faith in a god who keeps secrets this important from us all. We're done with him and his web of lies.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rebels_HM_TRUTH_16</Key>
    <Value>All I hear from you is how Elatt is truly the one responsible for the Scourge! Don't you see that we're worshipping a monster?! This madness ends now, today! It's time to tear down this false god and all of his false disciples!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rebels_HM_TRUTH_17</Key>
    <Value>We’re going to return home to Monsoon shortly. We’re going to camp here for now.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rebels_HM_TRUTH_18</Key>
    <Value>You just stay back. We’re done with Elatt. Just leave us be.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_TRUTH_01</Key>
    <Value>Word of your deeds has reached me, Missionary. A lesser person would have resolved that ideological conflict with force. You, however, used your heart, and succeeded.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_TRUTH_02</Key>
    <Value>Word of your deeds has reached me, Missionary. While we wish that force could have been avoided, you still managed to prevent a spark from becoming a firestorm. Thank you for protecting Monsoon from these rebels.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_TRUTH_03</Key>
    <Value>You have done a great deal of good, [PlayerName]. As Elatt commands, we elevate you to the rank of Champion. In Elatt's name, I bestow upon you this reward, so that you may become a guiding light for all Aurai. May your great deeds only grow greater.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_TRUTH_04</Key>
    <Value>Your efforts are recognized, [PlayerName]. With Elatt's recommendation, we elevate you to the rank of Templar. May your deeds grow ever greater.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_TRUTH_05</Key>
    <Value>From now on, you will report to me, [PlayerName]. Continue your good work.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_HaPeace_01</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName], we have urgent business to discuss. Our neutrality in the war between the Blue Chamber Collective and Levant is at risk.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_HaPeace_02</Key>
    <Value>Soeran discovered a pair of spies from Levant in our inn and took them into custody for questioning. The plan was to release them once we were done, but...They've since gone missing. Elatt can't find them either. Someone is shielding them from our sight.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_HaPeace_03</Key>
    <Value>There was a group of warriors from the Blue Chamber Collective staying at the inn that night, and they too have gone missing. I worry that the war may have finally come to our city.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_HaPeace_04</Key>
    <Value>I can only guess that someone took them into the swamp. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please, find those spies and warriors&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, before either group does something tragic.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_HaPeace_05</Key>
    <Value>All of us felt Elatt's fury over what happened. Making this peace a reality is now our top priority.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_HaPeace_06</Key>
    <Value>I've sent messengers to Levant already. You must &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;journey to Berg in Enmerkar Forest. I need you to make the Chamberlords of the Blue Chamber see reason. Speak with Rissa Aberdeen&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, she has connections to everyone else.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cardinal_HM_HaPeace_a_06</Key>
    <Value>Why did you wait for me and not send someone immediately?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_HaPeace_07</Key>
    <Value>Convincing Rissa Aberdeen to support peace talks is our best chance of success, and she continues to speak well of you even now. You have leverage no one else does.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_HaPeace_08</Key>
    <Value>Go, [PlayerName]. Things get worse the longer we delay.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_HaPeace_09</Key>
    <Value>I will gladly give my life to prevent a second Scourge! I have no doubt that most of us are willing. Tell us what we must do, and we will see it done, Elatt.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_HaPeace_10</Key>
    <Value>&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;See to the defense of Monsoon&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, [PlayerName]. Protect our city well!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_HaPeace_11</Key>
    <Value>Ah, good, you’ve arrived. We were just beginning the peace talks.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_HaPeace_12</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_HaPeace_13</Key>
    <Value>Greetings, Champion [PlayerName]. Elatt does not require your immediate assistance. You are free to pursue justice however you desire. Return in a few days, and I will inform you of any change.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_HaPeace_14</Key>
    <Value>Greetings, Templar [PlayerName]. There are no tasks that require your attention. Do what you need to do to prepare for your next task, and return here in a few days.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_HaPeace_15</Key>
    <Value>Elatt has given you a task, [PlayerName]. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;See to it that the leaders of both warring factions come here to discuss peace terms&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. May Elatt light your path.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_HaPeace_16</Key>
    <Value>W-well done, [PlayerName]. I am glad you came to join the Holy Mission when you did...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cardinal_HM_HaPeace_a_16</Key>
    <Value>Cardinal, how are you feeling?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_HaPeace_17</Key>
    <Value>N-not...Very well. The light of Calixa’s soul keeps the worst of the Corruption at bay, but it’s only a matter of time before I am overcome. Know that it was a pleasure to work with you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cardinal_HM_HaPeace_a_17</Key>
    <Value>Who will guide the Holy Mission with you gone?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_HaPeace_18</Key>
    <Value>Most likely it will be Mathias, although Alemmon is also a possibility. It will take time before to refill the ranks of our disciples, let alone find one with the strength to become Cardinal.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_HaPeace_19</Key>
    <Value>Go now. Protect Aurai as you see fit. The rest of the Holy Mission trusts in you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_HaPeace_20</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_HaPeace_21</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_HaPeace_22</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_HaPeace_23</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_HaPeace_24</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Galira_HM_HaPeace_01</Key>
    <Value>Something on your mind?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Galira_HM_HaPeace_a_01</Key>
    <Value>Have you seen any unusual movements? I’m trying to find some missing prisoners.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Galira_HM_HaPeace_02</Key>
    <Value>The agents from Levant, right? They were moved in the dead of night, I don’t think anyone saw where they went. But &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;I saw Damian Lockwell’s bodyguard cleaning swamp stains off his armor the morning after&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. It could be coincidence, or it could be a connection.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Galira_HM_HaPeace_03</Key>
    <Value>I can’t believe that Sagard Battleborn sent thugs to spill Levantin blood in our marsh. If I ever cross paths with him again, I will be sorely tempted to introduce him to my fist!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Galira_HM_HaPeace_04</Key>
    <Value>Those invading Scourge were tough. I haven’t had a battle that intense in quite a while! I know my place is here, teaching the next generation of missionaries and templars, but Elatt’s name do I miss the thrill of adventure.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>LockwellGuard_HM_HaPeace_01</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_LockwellGuard_HM_HaPeace_a_01</Key>
    <Value>I’m [PlayerName], a Champion of Elatt. Where are those prisoners? I know Lockwell’s got something to do with it. Talk. Now.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_LockwellGuard_HM_HaPeace_b_01</Key>
    <Value>I’m a Templar. You know, the people Elatt sends when things need breaking? Where are the missing prisoners?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>LockwellGuard_HM_HaPeace_02</Key>
    <Value>M-missing prisoners? I’m afraid I don’t quite remember who you're talking about…</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_LockwellGuard_HM_HaPeace_a_02</Key>
    <Value>Do you know what a Champion of Elatt does to liars? I have ways to make you talk.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_LockwellGuard_HM_HaPeace_b_02</Key>
    <Value>Will 50 Silvers and the promise not to have Elatt smite your lying tongue jog your memory?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>LockwellGuard_HM_HaPeace_03</Key>
    <Value>I’ll talk! Please don’t smite me! I was just following orders! Lockwell had me transfer them over to his hidden cellar in an old ruined city! It’s in the south-west of the Marsh!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>LockwellGuard_HM_HaPeace_04</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>CaughtSpy_HM_HaPeace_01</Key>
    <Value>Phew, thank you! I thought I was a goner for sure! These thugs that Sagard Battleborn sent were planning to torture me for information if you hadn't shown up!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_CaughtSpy_HM_HaPeace_a_01</Key>
    <Value>It's time we ended this war. Elatt demands peace.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>CaughtSpy_HM_HaPeace_02</Key>
    <Value>Listen, I don't know if you'll ever need to know this, but there's this entrance to the city of Levant from under the slums. There's a cave to the south of Levant that you can use to get in discreetly.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>CaughtSpy_HM_HaPeace_03</Key>
    <Value>I’ll be fine, I can get out on my own. I’m seriously in your debt!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>CaughtSpy_HM_HaPeace_04</Key>
    <Value>Forget me for now! Deal with Sagard’s thugs before they kill us all!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_HM_HaPeace_00</Key>
    <Value>I hear you’re making a name for yourself within the Holy Mission. I’m proud that you’ve found your calling, [PlayerName].</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_HM_HaPeace_01</Key>
    <Value>It's been some time, [PlayerName]. How go things with the Holy Mission? How is Oliele?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_HM_HaPeace_a_01</Key>
    <Value>Elatt demands an end to the war. He wants you to come to Monsoon to negotiate peace terms.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_HM_HaPeace_02</Key>
    <Value>I wish I could promise we would be there. But Levant has burned and pillaged our land and towns, and the tribes have vowed revenge. To call off the war will require an enormous effort. I don't know how much I can do unless we &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;compensate them well&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_HM_HaPeace_a_02</Key>
    <Value>I’m invoking a Tribal Favor. Remind them that we are all family, and that war and death is not the Blue Chamber’s way.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_HM_HaPeace_b_02</Key>
    <Value>I will offer 150 silver coins to help pay for damages Levant has done, to ease their anger.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_HM_HaPeace_03</Key>
    <Value>I cannot argue with that. Very well, I will do what I can to organize peace. I need you to convince &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Gabriella Sullivan&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, our mistress of the hunt, and &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sagard Battleborn&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, Berg’s Chamberlord as well.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_HM_HaPeace_a_03</Key>
    <Value>Can't you do that?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_HM_HaPeace_04</Key>
    <Value>Gabriella has grown distant from me lately, and Sagard won't listen to anyone who can't hold their own in a fight. They will respond better to you than to me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_HM_HaPeace_05</Key>
    <Value>As soon as I hear back from Gabriella and Sagard, I will make the journey to Monsoon. I wish you luck, [PlayerName].</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Rissa_HM_HaPeace_c_02</Key>
    <Value>You have to find a way!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_HM_HaPeace_06</Key>
    <Value>I wish I could, I really do. But without something tangible to calm them down, they won't listen. To even have a chance, &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;we would have to pay them well over 100 silver&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; .</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Rissa_HM_HaPeace_07</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_HM_HaPeace_00</Key>
    <Value>Greetings, follower of Elatt. May your journeys be safe!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_HM_HaPeace_01</Key>
    <Value>Well, well. The new Champion of the Holy Mission. What brings you here?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_HM_HaPeace_02</Key>
    <Value>What do you need, follower of Elatt?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_HM_HaPeace_03</Key>
    <Value>"Demands"? Oh wonderful. I have angry tribesmen lining up to join our armies, how do you want me to tell them they can't have their revenge? &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;They'll need a show of force&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; to make them back off.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_HM_HaPeace_04</Key>
    <Value>I suppose that might be enough to remind them of their duty. I’ll make it work somehow.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Gabriella_HM_HaPeace_a_04</Key>
    <Value>(Give Horror Chitin) Remind them that Elatt's sacrifice is the only reason the scourge hasn't killed us all.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Gabriella_HM_HaPeace_a_04-b</Key>
    <Value>(If you had such a thing, it would surely convince her.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_HM_HaPeace_05</Key>
    <Value>Oh wow, did you do this? It's a very impressive trophy... I think this might work.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Gabriella_HM_HaPeace_b_04</Key>
    <Value>(Offer her your Coralhorn Bow) Then force them to see reason if you have to.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_HM_HaPeace_06</Key>
    <Value>With a weapon like that? I think I might be able to.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_HM_HaPeace_07</Key>
    <Value>I'll get to work on my end. I'll make this truce happen if it's the last thing I do.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_HM_HaPeace_08</Key>
    <Value>I can't do the impossible. Unless you &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;have something to remind them of their duty, or something I can use to force them to see reason&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, I can't do a damn thing.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_HM_HaPeace_09</Key>
    <Value>Maybe if you could &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;bring me a trophy from a powerful Scourge Beast, or an exceptionally crafted bow from an Alpha Coralhorn&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, it might be enough of a show of force that I’ll be able to get through to them.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_HM_HaPeace_10</Key>
    <Value>It’s good to finally have peace again. Now I can focus on bringing in wild game and not on drilling troops!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Gabriella_HM_HaPeace_11</Key>
    <Value>Ugh... I’m really not enjoying this whole Chamberlady thing. Elatt’s name, I need a drink.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_HM_HaPeace_01</Key>
    <Value>Well well, [PlayerName] the Champion of Elatt. This is a surprise meeting. Here to finally pledge your aid in slaughtering those desert rats?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_HM_HaPeace_02</Key>
    <Value>Well, Elatt's newest Templar. What do you want [PlayerName]? Here to finally pledge your aid in slaughtering those desert rats?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_HM_HaPeace_03</Key>
    <Value>Well, that's too bad for him. We aren't going to stop fighting a war that we're finally winning. No force on Aurai will make me change my mind!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_HM_HaPeace_04</Key>
    <Value>You already have my word that I’ll pull back my armies. The message is already being sent to my warriors.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_HM_HaPeace_05</Key>
    <Value>Bah, it’s not fair when Elatt gives you his strength on top of your own! Fine! You win. I’ll call off my armies. I’m smart enough to know when I’m whupped.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sagard_HM_HaPeace_06</Key>
    <Value>No? Fine. Then leave me alone. I have plans for Levant’s destruction to create!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>OasisCitizen_HM_HaPeace_01</Key>
    <Value>Someone from the Holy Mission! Elatt be praised! There's a coup happening right now in Levant! Almost the entire army has taken control of the city and are besieging the Palace as we speak!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>OasisCitizen_HM_HaPeace_02</Key>
    <Value>Levant’s been closed off! I only managed to leave because they didn’t guard the Undercity Passage. It’s to the south of the city, at the bottom of the cliff. It leads straight into town but it’s full of smugglers and corsairs.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_OasisCitizen_HM_HaPeace_a_02</Key>
    <Value>Anything else you can tell me about that passage?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>OasisCitizen_HM_HaPeace_03</Key>
    <Value>Yes. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;That passage has an entrance to the Palace as well, but it needs a key&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. If you want to reach the King and Queen, you'll need to find one. Most of her soldiers should have a copy by now.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_OasisCitizen_HM_HaPeace_b_02</Key>
    <Value>What other news can you tell me?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>OasisCitizen_HM_HaPeace_04</Key>
    <Value>Levant is in the middle of a desperate famine, so everyone is starving. Many would do anything for some Travel Rations to fill their bellies.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>OasisCitizen_HM_HaPeace_05</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>LevantDoor_HM_HaPeace_01</Key>
    <Value>Under the order of Temporary Regent Cyrene, all access to and from the Kingdom of Levant is suspended. Violators will be shot.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Varaon_HM_HaPeace_01</Key>
    <Value>Hey, you. Mind getting me out of this death pit? My people need me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Varaon_HM_HaPeace_a_01</Key>
    <Value>Who are you, really?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Varaon_HM_HaPeace_02</Key>
    <Value>Just someone who cares deeply about the fate of the tribes of Old Levant, it's why those rats squatting in their shiny "Heroic Kingdom" locked me up in here. I didn't do anything that they wouldn't have done.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Varaon_HM_HaPeace_03</Key>
    <Value>I can offer you something interesting in exchange for my freedom, traveller. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;A key that opens a secret entrance to the Palace in Levant&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Varaon_HM_HaPeace_04</Key>
    <Value>There's a smuggler's tunnel under the city of New Levant that connects the desert to the slums. Further along is a passage that leads to the Palace itself, or so I hear. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;With this key, you can get inside from there&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Varaon_HM_HaPeace_b_01</Key>
    <Value>Why should I let a criminal out of here?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Varaon_HM_HaPeace_a_05</Key>
    <Value>What were you intending to do with that?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Varaon_HM_HaPeace_b_05</Key>
    <Value>What would I do with something like that?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Varaon_HM_HaPeace_c_01</Key>
    <Value>I'll get you out. Stand back while I break the lock.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Varaon_HM_HaPeace_d_01</Key>
    <Value>I'm not going to let you out.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Varaon_HM_HaPeace_05</Key>
    <Value>Criminal's a nasty word. I prefer to be called a freedom fighter. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Varaon_HM_HaPeace_06</Key>
    <Value>I hadn't decided yet. But something like this is always useful, wouldn't you say?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Varaon_HM_HaPeace_07</Key>
    <Value>None of my business, traveller. You do what you want with it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Varaon_HM_HaPeace_08</Key>
    <Value>Old Levant owes you a great debt, traveller. Should we ever return to power in Abrassar, I will gladly reward you with riches and power. Now, get me out of this place!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Varaon_HM_HaPeace_09</Key>
    <Value>Fine. Then at least leave here, so I can face my fate with dignity!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Varaon_HM_HaPeace_10</Key>
    <Value>Come to gloat, Levantin? Get out of here, and let me face my fate with dignity.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>BribeGuard_HM_HaPeace_01</Key>
    <Value>A follower of Elatt? How did you get in here? The gates are locked!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_BribeGuard_HM_HaPeace_a_01</Key>
    <Value>Elatt demands peace. Now, let me see the king and queen, or risk his fury.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>BribeGuard_HM_HaPeace_02</Key>
    <Value>Are you... are you threatening me,?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_BribeGuard_HM_HaPeace_a_02</Key>
    <Value>Elatt is. He wants peace and he wants it NOW. Do you want to be the one to deny a god?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>BribeGuard_HM_HaPeace_03</Key>
    <Value>Point taken. Here. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Take this key. It will open the rear entrance to the Palace from the smuggler's tunnel&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. If I were you, I’d watch out. Someone will likely have seen our little chat and will have sent reinforcements there.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_BribeGuard_HM_HaPeace_b_01</Key>
    <Value>(Give 3 travel rations) There's a famine going on here, isn't there? I have some travel rations that will fill your belly.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>BribeGuard_HM_HaPeace_04</Key>
    <Value>Dammit, I've been living on one meal a day for weeks. Why do you tempt me like this? What do you want?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_BribeGuard_HM_HaPeace_a_04</Key>
    <Value>Elatt wants peace. I want to see your king and queen. Show me how to reach them, and this food is yours.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>BribeGuard_HM_HaPeace_05</Key>
    <Value>Augh... I'll do it. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Here, take this key. There's a rear entrance to the Palace in the smuggler's tunnel in the slums&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. It's well guarded, so go armed if you want to live.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>BribeGuard_HM_HaPeace_06</Key>
    <Value>Now, let’s pretend we never had this discussion. I have no interest in meeting a firing squad up close.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>BribeGuard_HM_HaPeace_07</Key>
    <Value>Move along. Martial law is in effect. Do not cause trouble. Go about your business!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Markus_HM_HaPeace_01</Key>
    <Value>I'm just a merc, but I still can't let you in. There’s people who fled the city who went to hide near the oasis, I think. They’ll be more inclined to chat with you than I am.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_HM_HaPeace_01</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName]? What in Elatt's name are you doing here?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_HM_HaPeace_02</Key>
    <Value>Oh, he "demands" peace, does he? Does he have any idea how we've suffered at the hands of the Blue Chamber? No, we'll make peace when we're good and ready to. Until then, Cyrene controls this kingdom!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Yzan_HM_HaPeace_a_02</Key>
    <Value>What have you done to King Simeon and Queen Calixa?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Yzan_HM_HaPeace_a_02-b</Key>
    <Value>Yzan, are you seriously going to let this happen? I thought you believed in the ideals of Levant!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_HM_HaPeace_03</Key>
    <Value>I still do. It's Calixa and Simeon who lost sight of them. The Blue Chamber tried to starve us all to death! Sagard Battleborn ignored the way of the Blue Chamber Collective and took no prisoners! How could we negotiate peace with them?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Yzan_HM_HaPeace_a_03-a</Key>
    <Value>Surely you’ve seen all that the Holy Mission has done to end this conflict! We aren't your enemy.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_HM_HaPeace_03-b</Key>
    <Value>The lives of our people were threatened. All we ever did was defend ourselves! Why should we crawl to our enemies and beg them to forgive us?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Yzan_HM_HaPeace_a_03</Key>
    <Value>The Blue Chamber is willing to negotiate, even after Levant burned and pillaged their villages. This is proof they're willing to accept a fair peace.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_HM_HaPeace_04</Key>
    <Value>What? I find it hard to believe that they'd actually be willing to negotiate. What motive could they have to pursue a fair peace when they could demand our surrender?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Yzan_HM_HaPeace_b_03</Key>
    <Value>Levant attacked them first! You attacked Berg, and you killed one of our Champions! You are the ones who started this disaster!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_HM_HaPeace_05</Key>
    <Value>Only to defend ourselves from Old Levant's absurd demand that they control the entire region. It would have been the end of Levant. And even then, it was only a rogue offshoot of our army that led that attack, and yet the whole of Levant was punished for it!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Yzan_HM_HaPeace_c_03</Key>
    <Value>Because all the Blue Chamber Collective did was try to defend itself. How many people were killed by Levant's armies?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_HM_HaPeace_06</Key>
    <Value>Yeah? If their strategy to starve us all to death had succeeded, even more would have died! We had to pillage every village we attacked just to survive!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Yzan_HM_HaPeace_a_06</Key>
    <Value>Elatt will ensure they do not take advantage of you. He knows it would only lead to more war. The god of discipline plays no favourites.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_HM_HaPeace_07</Key>
    <Value>You're asking me to abandon everything in hopes that a faction outside our control can make a fair peace with a dying queen and an injured king! How could you expect that of us?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Yzan_HM_HaPeace_b_06</Key>
    <Value>We will have peace, one way or another. Stand aside. I'm here to speak to the actual rulers of The Heroic Kingdom.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_HM_HaPeace_08</Key>
    <Value>If he does not recognize Cyrene as the new Queen of Levant, then we do not recognize Elatt's power over Abrassar. We have no need of gods to tell us what to do.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Yzan_HM_HaPeace_c_06</Key>
    <Value>I won't let the Blue Chamber take advantage of Levant. I suffered under them too, remember? You can trust me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_HM_HaPeace_09</Key>
    <Value>You think I've forgotten how you mugged me, you rat?! Why in Elatt's name should I trust you?!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_HM_HaPeace_10</Key>
    <Value>I want to trust you... But what you're asking is far beyond either of us. The entire kingdom is at stake!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Yzan_HM_HaPeace_a_10</Key>
    <Value>Open your eyes! You're pitting Levant against a foe you can't possibly beat! Peace is your only chance for survival!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_HM_HaPeace_11</Key>
    <Value>I’ll take that chance. To make peace now would be to surrender to them! How can we trust them after all they've done to us?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Yzan_HM_HaPeace_b_10</Key>
    <Value>So regicide, betrayal and brutal crackdowns on your poorest citizens are the true ideals of Levant?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_HM_HaPeace_12</Key>
    <Value>It's what the damned Blues pushed us to! We never wanted any of this! </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Yzan_HM_HaPeace_c_10</Key>
    <Value>You left Cierzo because of how they forced Roland's problems onto you. You're doing that same exact thing to Levant right now!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_HM_HaPeace_13</Key>
    <Value>I... No, you can't say what we're doing is the same! I'm just... I'm trying to protect them! I don't... Damn you, [PlayerName]!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_HM_HaPeace_14</Key>
    <Value>Damn your sharp words. Damn you for making me doubt everything I've sacrificed for. Cyrene... I can't continue what we started. If you want to kill [PlayerName], you'll have to do it yourself.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_HM_HaPeace_15</Key>
    <Value>Enough lies! Levant is my home, and I will not let it continue to be destroyed! I will fight for it. I would die for it! And if I must kill you for it, then so be it!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_HM_HaPeace_16</Key>
    <Value>I don't believe we will meet again, [PlayerName]. I'm not hanging around to be tried for treason... </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Yzan_HM_HaPeace_a_16</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Yzan_HM_HaPeace_17</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyrene_HM_HaPeace_01</Key>
    <Value>We triumphed over our tyrants, that's what. They were ready make peace with our foes after so many of our soldiers were slaughtered. I can't stand by and allow that to happen. We have sacrificed too many lives for this to end peacefully!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyrene_HM_HaPeace_02</Key>
    <Value>I am the new queen of Levant now. Calixa is dying of a poison that has no cure, and Simeon is beaten and broken. I'll line the bastard up for the firing squad myself!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyrene_HM_HaPeace_a_02</Key>
    <Value>... You're the woman with the shield on her back. You shot Zephyrien with that poisoned bullet, didn't you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyrene_HM_HaPeace_03</Key>
    <Value>It was nothing personal. Old Levant was demanding to claim Abrassar from us, and there was no doubt in my mind that the Blue Chamber would accept their demands. Our kingdom and ideals would have been destroyed.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyrene_HM_HaPeace_04</Key>
    <Value>Sirocco would only offer to help us stop them if we killed Zephyrien and gave them half of the land we took in the war. It was an easy choice. One life for the lives of my entire people.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cyrene_HM_HaPeace_a_05</Key>
    <Value>What could he have done to deserve a death that cruel?!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyrene_HM_HaPeace_05</Key>
    <Value>I don't know and I don't care. Sirocco's reasons are none of my business. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyrene_HM_HaPeace_06</Key>
    <Value>Enough talk. I don't care if Elatt "demands" peace. He has no power here. Now leave and take that message to him, or you can join Simeon at the firing squad!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyrene_HM_HaPeace_07</Key>
    <Value>Yzan, you spineless coward! If you won’t fight for your Queen and country, then you are worthless to me! I’ll see you both shot for this!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyrene_HM_HaPeace_08</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyrene_HM_HaPeace_09</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyrene_HM_HaPeace_10</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyrene_HM_HaPeace_11</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cyrene_HM_HaPeace_12</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Simeon_HM_HaPeace_01</Key>
    <Value>... Gah... Elatt damn it all. Am I really so vulnerable without my wife to watch my back? Having to have my kingdom be saved by one of Elatt’s people... It’s beyond embarrassing.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Simeon_HM_HaPeace_a_01</Key>
    <Value>Are you going to make it, sire?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Simeon_HM_HaPeace_02</Key>
    <Value>Forget me, a few flesh wounds are barely enough to slow me down! Calixa’s the one who needs help. Cyrene shot her with something, I think she said it was poisoned!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Simeon_HM_HaPeace_03</Key>
    <Value>...That was Elatt, wasn't it? He makes a very compelling argument. Fine, &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;we'll set off for Monsoon as soon as humanly possible&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. But he'd better hold up his end of the deal!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Simeon_HM_HaPeace_04</Key>
    <Value>We’ll be along as soon as we can. The moment Levant is stable, we’ll be on our way.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Simeon_HM_HaPeace_05</Key>
    <Value>Ah! The latest Champion of the Holy Mission! I’d welcome you with drinks and stories, but things are not well in the Heroic Kingdom.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Simeon_HM_HaPeace_06</Key>
    <Value>I’m afraid I don't have time for you. We’re juggling a famine and a losing war!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Simeon_HM_HaPeace_07</Key>
    <Value>Can we get on with this already? My wife’s life is hanging in the balance!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Simeon_HM_HaPeace_08</Key>
    <Value>I don’t know if I’ll ever get used to this. Having Calixa speak to me like this is... beyond strange.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Simeon_HM_HaPeace_09</Key>
    <Value>You will always have a place at our table, [PlayerName]. I will never forget what you did for Calixa and me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Simeon_HM_HaPeace_10</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Simeon_HM_HaPeace_11</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Simeon_HM_HaPeace_12</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Calixia_HM_HaPeace_01</Key>
    <Value>(She breathes with difficulty... Her body is numb and paralyzed from the poison. Her armor somewhat softened the blow, but the bullet still pierced her skin. Elatt's power is keeping her alive, but just barely.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Calixia_HM_HaPeace_02</Key>
    <Value>So, what do I need to do? How does this work?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Calixia_HM_HaPeace_03</Key>
    <Value>You need to use a giant source of Mana to kill me, and I just have to survive it. Well, it's not like I have anything left to lose. Let’s do it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Calixia_HM_HaPeace_04</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Calixia_HM_HaPeace_05</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Calixia_HM_HaPeace_06</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Calixia_HM_HaPeace_07</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Calixia_HM_HaPeace_08</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Palace_door_HM_HaPeace_01</Key>
    <Value>(You hear king Simeon groaning. He seems to be conscious again.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_HaPeace_01</Key>
    <Value>(A sudden wave of heat floods through your veins. Elatt's anger is palpable.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_HaPeace_02</Key>
    <Value>They have brought their petty war to our city. They have spilled blood on our soil and wish to drag us into war on their behalf. No more!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_HaPeace_03</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName], I must rely on you once more. I will &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;speak with Cardinal Bourlamaque&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; and prepare a plan to settle this senseless conflict. Return to him as soon as possible.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_HaPeace_04</Key>
    <Value>(An invisible force shakes you from head to toe, and Elatt's voice comes like a gust of hot wind)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_HaPeace_05</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName], things go poorly in Abrassar. My messengers have been imprisoned. Civil war strikes the city of Levant. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;You are needed there, desperately&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elatt_HM_HaPeace_a_05</Key>
    <Value>Isn't Soeran closer than I am?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_HaPeace_06</Key>
    <Value>No, he is not. He is standing between both armies, trying to stop any further combat between either side. This task is up to you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_HaPeace_07</Key>
    <Value>(Elatt's fury erupts as potent as a volcano within you, then suddenly becomes calm. Elatt speaks to you and Simeon in your minds)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_HaPeace_08</Key>
    <Value>Simeon, &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;bring Calixa to Monsoon&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Accept terms of peace, and I will see to it that her life is saved. Until then, I will use what strength I can spare to keep her alive.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_HaPeace_09</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName], return to Monsoon with all possible haste. We must have a strong front ready to oversee negotiations between these foolish nations. Nothing must be left to chance.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_HaPeace_10</Key>
    <Value>Good, everyone needed for the Ascension is present.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_HaPeace_11</Key>
    <Value>Your body is beyond saving. Your spirit, however, is another story. The keys to divinity are an unyielding will in the face of certain death, and the full power of a Ley Line to fuel the spell.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_HaPeace_12</Key>
    <Value>I will divert Mana from across the Hallowed Marsh and temporarily create a new Ley Line under Monsoon. From you, Calixa, I will need your iron will.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_HaPeace_13</Key>
    <Value>The spell that led me to godhood was designed to destroy the entirety of my being. Only by resisting the spell and refusing to die was I able to survive it and be transformed. I will need you to show the same self-discipline and force of will.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_HaPeace_14</Key>
    <Value>I can guide you through the process and help you understand what to do, but ultimately, only you can transcend your own mortal flesh, Queen Calixa. Brace yourself.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elatt_HM_HaPeace_a_14</Key>
    <Value>Didn’t the spell cause the Scourge when you survived it, though? We can't do that again, in the middle of Monsoon! It would be a catastrophe!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elatt_HM_HaPeace_b_14</Key>
    <Value>Do you have a way to deal with the consequences of the spell, Elatt? How can we prevent another Scourge from happening?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_HaPeace_15</Key>
    <Value>Fear not. I have planned for this danger. Those of you who have reached the rank of Disciple, I call upon your aid. You are trained to absorb and destroy Corruption. I ask of you to join in my spell and dive your spirits into Calixa's.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_HaPeace_16</Key>
    <Value>I ask you to be a human barrier to contain the Corruption that the Ascension will unleash. But know that to take on such a task is to choose death. If the Corruption does not kill you now, then it will in a scant few weeks.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_HaPeace_17</Key>
    <Value>I cannot force you to give your lives, so I ask that you give them willingly. Will seven of you give your lives so that Calixa will Ascend without bringing further ruin to Aurai?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elatt_HM_HaPeace_b_17</Key>
    <Value>I want to help. Let me take Ellinara's place.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_HaPeace_18</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName], if you do this, know that &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;you will perish&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Even if you survive the initial task, you will have at most &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;a month to live&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elatt_HM_HaPeace_b_18</Key>
    <Value>I understand. I'm still sure I want to do this.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_HaPeace_19</Key>
    <Value>You are certain? You have much of your life ahead of you. You will truly take on this certain doom? &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;You choose to willingly give up your life&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elatt_HM_HaPeace_b_19</Key>
    <Value>Yes. I'm willing to sacrifice myself to contain the Corruption and spare Ellinara.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_HaPeace_21</Key>
    <Value>You are committed now, [PlayerName]. Join the circle and brace yourself.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_HaPeace_22</Key>
    <Value>(As you center your focus into Calixa, you feel Elatt's power fill you with great warmth. Then, for a brief painful moment you feel yourself torn from your very body, your spirit plunging into her.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elatt_HM_HaPeace_a_17</Key>
    <Value>What do you want me to do, Elatt?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_HaPeace_23</Key>
    <Value>You, as a Champion, should be on the front lines of the defense.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_HaPeace_24</Key>
    <Value>I need you to join the defense of Monsoon, Templar.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_HM_HaPeace_25</Key>
    <Value>&lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Go forth and protect Monsoon with your life&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Do not let a single Scourge Beast reach the temple! The safety of the city is in your hands.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_HaPeace_01</Key>
    <Value>If Calixa’s Ascension is necessary and our deaths can prevent a second Scourge, I'm willing to sacrifice my life.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_HaPeace_02</Key>
    <Value>You didn't have to do this for me, [PlayerName]. But if you insist... then I thank you. I will not forget your sacrifice on my behalf.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_HaPeace_03</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName], you're awake. Good. You have some time left in this world after all. How do you feel?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_HaPeace_a_03</Key>
    <Value>Not all that terrible, considering. I still feel stronger than I ever have.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_HaPeace_04</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName], the light of the Ascension is a balm against the Corruption, but it is not a cure. With every passing day, the Corruption will eat away at you. Should you fall now, you will surely not survive.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_HaPeace_05</Key>
    <Value>You likely only have &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;about a month before you truly stand at death's door. Make good use of the final days you have left to live&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Set your affairs to rest as best you can, so you may pass without regrets.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_HaPeace_a_05</Key>
    <Value>Well, I knew what I was getting into...</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_HaPeace_06</Key>
    <Value>Indeed you did. And I thank you for it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elinara_HM_HaPeace_b_05</Key>
    <Value>Oh crap. This was a bad idea.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_HaPeace_07</Key>
    <Value>Doesn't Elatt always tell you? Never do anything that you do not understand. Because now you live with the consequences of your rash action.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_HaPeace_08</Key>
    <Value>The others were able to protect Monsoon from the Scourge attack. There were very few casualties.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_HaPeace_09</Key>
    <Value>You have done your service to Aurai. Now, you are free to do with your remaining life what you wish. Live it well, and meet your ancestors with pride, [PlayerName].</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiations_HM_HaPeace_01</Key>
    <Value>Not to mention that the Holy Mission has been dragging out the preparations for negotiations for far too long! We should have started days ago!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiations_HM_HaPeace_02</Key>
    <Value>Forgive us for any delay on our end. One of our tribes has turned against us all. I fear they plan to begin a civil war, armed with a small army of ghosts and undead. Precautions had to be taken.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiations_HM_HaPeace_03</Key>
    <Value>Enough! Do not escalate this conflict further! The weapons shall be shared. Any who would use them to restart the conflict will have to answer to Elatt’s judgment.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiations_HM_HaPeace_03-b</Key>
    <Value>By “beasts” do you mean your own people? Perhaps a few less firearms in the hands of fools will make keeping order a little easier!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiations_HM_HaPeace_04</Key>
    <Value>How can you promise that when you can’t even keep order in your own city? I heard that one of your own people was captured, then was arrested and detained unlawfully in an illegal prison outside Monsoon! Consider me very skeptical, Cardinal!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiations_HM_HaPeace_05</Key>
    <Value>I must express concern about introducing further religious uncertainty. I’ve been informed that there was a small massacre of “heretics” here recently. To suddenly introduce a new goddess now would only inflame further strife!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiations_HM_HaPeace_06</Key>
    <Value>That tragedy was dealt with as best that humankind is capable. We may falter, but despite our failings, we would die to protect the people of both your factions.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiations_HM_HaPeace_07</Key>
    <Value>My people demand repayment for the many destroyed lives and homes. To agree to terms this unfavorable would tear the Blue Chamber Collective apart. I cannot agree to them in good faith.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiations_HM_HaPeace_08</Key>
    <Value>If repayment for lost homes and lives is what is needed to secure peace, then the Holy Mission will cover the cost. We understand that compromise is needed.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiations_HM_HaPeace_09</Key>
    <Value>Very well. The Blue Chamber Collective accepts these terms of peace.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiations_HM_HaPeace_10</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName], you have done much to aid in securing this peace. Come, drink the Peacemaker's Elixir with us.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiations_HM_HaPeace_11</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName], I have watched you grow and strive ever since you came to us. Though your actions often went unrecognized, rest assured that I have seen them. Your deeds deserve additional reward.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiations_HM_HaPeace_12</Key>
    <Value>All of you who serve the Holy Mission, come to my altar in the temple. I have need of you all.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiations_HM_HaPeace_13</Key>
    <Value>We have been summoned to the Temple. I will see you at Elatt’s Altar, [PlayerName].</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Negotiations_HM_HaPeace_14</Key>
    <Value>(The Cardinal does not respond... His spirit is currently battling the Corruption within Calixa as the Ascension ritual progresses.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Damian_Lockwell_HM_HaPeace_01</Key>
    <Value>At long last the war pushes back, far from our borders. It is a good time to earn some gratitude from the Blue Chamber now that their victory is assured.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Damian_Lockwell_HM_HaPeace_02</Key>
    <Value>If you’re looking for those Levantin agents we arrested, &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;they’re gone. They left this morning&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. I can assure you that I haven’t the slightest idea where they may be.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Damian_Lockwell_HM_HaPeace_a_02</Key>
    <Value>We both know that’s a lie. You had them locked up in an old cellar in the swamp!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Damian_Lockwell_HM_HaPeace_03</Key>
    <Value>What an absurd accusation. I released them! If they happened to be captured by the Blue Chamber moments after being set free, that’s their fault, not mine.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Damian_Lockwell_HM_HaPeace_04</Key>
    <Value>Another god... Has no one learned the lesson the first time?! Mark my words, our descendants will be pawns in their power games over Aurai. Mark my words.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Damian_Lockwell_HM_HaPeace_05</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_HaPeace_01</Key>
    <Value>Can’t talk for now, [PlayerName]. Ellinara has me running around coordinating our people. There’s a lot we need to do to be ready for the peace talks.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_HaPeace_02</Key>
    <Value>I will not allow violence on our watch. These talks will go through and we will have peace again!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_HaPeace_03</Key>
    <Value>I’m glad you were at my side back there, [PlayerName]. I don’t know if I’d still be here without your efforts.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_HaPeace_04</Key>
    <Value>Either way, thank you for walking this path with me. You’re a true friend, [PlayerName]. No, more like family, after all we’ve done.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_HaPeace_05</Key>
    <Value>I still can’t believe you went and did it. Even at my most dedicated, I’d have shied away from sacrificing my life, and yet you did it without a second thought.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_HaPeace_06</Key>
    <Value>I’m... going to miss you, [PlayerName]. I won’t let anyone forget what you did for all of us.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_HaPeace_07</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_Permadeath_01</Key>
    <Value>You’re still here, I see. You still choose to linger here between life and death, [PlayerName]? Why have you not gone to your well-deserved rest?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elatt_Permadeath_a_01</Key>
    <Value>I’m not ready let go just yet.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_Permadeath_02</Key>
    <Value>Perhaps I can lay your concerns to rest, then. Or at least, I can keep you company until you are ready to move on and meet your ancestors.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elatt_Permadeath_a_02</Key>
    <Value>I want to ask about places I’ve been.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elatt_Permadeath_b_02</Key>
    <Value>I want to ask about people I care for.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elatt_Permadeath_c_02</Key>
    <Value>I want to ask about you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Elatt_Permadeath_d_02</Key>
    <Value>Thank you for talking with me, Elatt.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_Permadeath_03</Key>
    <Value>Rissa is doing well enough. She is preparing to retire from her duties, and has picked a new successor for her as Chamberlady of Cierzo. Gabriella Sullivan’s niece should make for a good Chamberlady after a few years of training.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_Permadeath_04</Key>
    <Value>Rissa has retired as Chamberlady. The loss of Cierzo hurt her deeply. I don’t know if it will ever be rebuilt after what happened. She wishes you had chosen to become part of her family, but accepts that you did what was right for Aurai.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_Permadeath_05</Key>
    <Value>Oliele is doing well. She has committed to the philosopher’s path of the Holy Mission. If she continues her work at her current pace, she will likely be ready to become a Disciple in less than two years. She misses you, but does not grieve.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_Permadeath_06</Key>
    <Value>Oliele... She fights the Scourge at the Gates of Catharsis now. She is vicious and relentless in her work, and has gained the admiration of many. But her life will remain a violent one until she will finally be overcome by her foes.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_Permadeath_07</Key>
    <Value>Yzan... Hmm... Ah, there he is. He sails the sea near Oroshi. He has made his peace with no longer having a home, and has returned to his merchant ways. He will be alright, I think. He regrets his actions, but is determined to do better in the future.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_Permadeath_08</Key>
    <Value>... It pains me to say this. Yzan refuses to move on. His ghost lingers in Abrassar desert, craving a home. He curses your name, Levant itself, and all who caused his situation, save himself. I doubt he will ever rest in peace.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_Permadeath_09</Key>
    <Value>Elinara remains thankful for your sacrifice in her place. She has redoubled her efforts to preserve the joy and peace of everyone in Monsoon. I have no doubt that she will live enough for both of you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_Permadeath_10</Key>
    <Value>Cierzo is as lively as ever. Your old home in the Lighthouse has found a new family, and your story is told to the children at bedtime. I think you can rest easy knowing that you’ve become a local legend to them.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_Permadeath_11</Key>
    <Value>Cierzo remains destroyed. I doubt it will ever be rebuilt. You can rest at peace knowing that the ones who destroyed it have since turned on one another and none remain alive. Justice has, in some small way, been served.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_Permadeath_12</Key>
    <Value>Berg has changed for the better. Sagard Battleborn has handed his role as Chamberlord to Gabriella Sullivan, who is ruling it very fairly. I forsee great things in Berg’s future.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_Permadeath_13</Key>
    <Value>Berg remains in a state of chaotic flux. Gabriella Sullivan remains a good Chamberlady, but Sagard and his rogue troops continue to cause trouble. It may be some time before peace truly returns to Enmerkar.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_Permadeath_14</Key>
    <Value>Levant is greater than I could have ever dreamed. Calixa was a fine choice for goddess, and continues to uplift her city. I thank you for helping her ascend, [PlayerName].</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_Permadeath_15</Key>
    <Value>Levant is still dealing with difficulties. While things have greatly improved, the brutal conspiracy that took the life of the younger prince left bad blood in many minds. It may be years before the city truly benefits from Calixa’s new role.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_Permadeath_16</Key>
    <Value>Monsoon is doing well. Your deeds are remembered fondly, [PlayerName]. Many new missionaries have joined, hoping to one day be considered your equal. You can rest easy and proud.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_Permadeath_17</Key>
    <Value>Monsoon is well enough. Immaculates still cause trouble from time to time, and people have once again gone missing in the Marsh... but overall, things are better than they were. You are missed here, [PlayerName].</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_Permadeath_18</Key>
    <Value>I am proud of what you’ve accomplished, you know. When you first stood before me and swore to work with me for the sake of Aurai, I knew you had great potential, but you surpassed my hopes considerably.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_Permadeath_19</Key>
    <Value>Your willingness to volunteer for that final task, even when it was not required of you, was impressive. I will not forget it, [PlayerName]. You’ve left behind quite an impressive legacy.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_Permadeath_20</Key>
    <Value>I still seek a way to put an end to the Scourge forever, and I do foresee several groups with their own plans to do so. All I can do is trust that together, we can find a way. If the last century has proven anything, it’s that humanity is resilient.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_Permadeath_21</Key>
    <Value>You are welcome, [PlayerName]. It is the least I can do.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_Permadeath_22</Key>
    <Value>I will remain here if you wish for more company, until you are ready to let go of this life and move on to the next. Take the time you need.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elatt_Permadeath_23</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnKeeper_HM_Info_01</Key>
    <Value>So I hear you joined the Holy Mission! I expect I’ll be seeing you here quite often, then!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnKeeper_HM_Info_02</Key>
    <Value>I hear the Montcalm tribe in the Chersonese is trying to control a personal army of ghosts! If they ever send one after you, you should use weapons that deal elemental damage to fend them off!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnKeeper_HM_Info_02-b</Key>
    <Value>You need to deal with some corruption in the valley behind the Ghost Pass? Make sure you have lots of supplies and some way to deal with ghosts. Also, stay away from the Montcalm village! They’ll know you’re from Cierzo and kill you!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnKeeper_HM_Info_03</Key>
    <Value>I made my yearly visit to the Vigil to pay my respects. My grandpa died killing the Scourge beast that’s stuck in that crystal, you know? I’m glad his sacrifice helped protect this town, but I can’t help but feel unsettled every time I’m around that Vigil.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnKeeper_HM_Info_04</Key>
    <Value>Zephyrien? Yeah, he was here a while ago, looking for some information about a particular bandit group. I told him they sometimes &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide out in the Forest Hive to the south&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. If you’re going after him, be careful. The Hive Lords are no joke in a straight fight.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnKeeper_HM_Info_04-b</Key>
    <Value>I can’t believe that Oliele is locked up! At least 6 of my customers witnessed that incident and I can assure you, Richard came at her with a mace! Why Chamberlord Lockwell is making a mountain out of a self-defense case I just do not understand.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnKeeper_HM_Info_05</Key>
    <Value>You’re looking for Oliele? The girl with the glowing thing going on? She’s a regular here at the inn. &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;She spends a lot of her time in the slums&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;, though, trying to get information from the locals. She’ll probably be there around this time.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnKeeper_HM_Info_05-b</Key>
    <Value>There’s been more and more arguments among you Holy Mission types here at the inn. There’s this one group in particular that’s been asking hard questions, and some of the other members are getting very touchy about it. Can’t we all just behave like adults here?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnKeeper_HM_Info_06</Key>
    <Value>Some of my usual customers have been missing for a while. I know they didn’t go far from town, but I’m worried they haven’t come back yet. I’m hoping this isn’t about their concerns about Elatt... I don’t want another death like Richard’s to happen.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnKeeper_HM_Info_07</Key>
    <Value>You’re looking for someone who knows the Old Language? Well Mofat’s been around since before my great-grandmother’s time, he might still remember it. And if not, you can always count on that Soroborean caravan trader for weird stuff like this.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnKeeper_HM_Info_08</Key>
    <Value>Well, this war is going to get wrapped up real quick. If Elatt demands someone lay down their arms, it’s only a matter of time until that happens.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnKeeper_HM_Info_09</Key>
    <Value>Not that I’m complaining about everything that happened, but there’s still bullet holes and cracked supports in my inn because of that Scourge attack. The war’s over, great, but my inn’s still in shambles!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>InnKeeper_HM_Info_10</Key>
    <Value>Oliele’s missing? Hmm... Well, &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Alemmon&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; does go for walks out in the swamp quite often and if Lockwell is behind this, his &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;house guard&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; may be willing to spill the beans.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_prequest_01</Key>
    <Value>Welcome to Elatt's Temple, traveller. Is there something you need from us?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cardinal_HM_prequest_a_01</Key>
    <Value>I'm curious about joining the Holy Mission.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_prequest_02</Key>
    <Value>Joining the Holy Mission of Elatt is not a decision to be taken lightly, pilgrim. To join us is to cut all ties, abandon your bloodline, and live the rest of your life for the good of all Aurai.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_prequest_03</Key>
    <Value>To serve Elatt's cause is to accept the three tenets of the Endless Path. First, no one should suffer. Give of yourself, seek to ease the pains of others. Second, no one is perfect. Always work to improve yourself, in mind and body. Third, no one is safe. To protect Aurai, one must have iron discipline.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_prequest_04</Key>
    <Value>And never forget, the Scourge knows us. To pledge to Elatt is to be &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;forever marked as an enemy of the Scourge&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. Their hate of you will be boundless. Well, more than usual at least.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cardinal_HM_prequest_a_04</Key>
    <Value>That’s asking a lot. I’m not so sure anymore.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_prequest_05</Key>
    <Value>We must all come to our own decisions in life, pilgrim. Don't commit to what you don't understand.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cardinal_HM_prequest_b_04</Key>
    <Value>I'm not afraid of any of that.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_prequest_06</Key>
    <Value>Then I shall intercede on your behalf with Elatt. He will judge whether or not he will accept you. In the meantime, I would like you to prove that you understand the First Pillar of the Holy Mission.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_prequest_07</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_prequest_08</Key>
    <Value>Once you have spoken to them, pray to the altar at the back of this temple, and wait for Elatt to judge you. If he finds you worthy, he will invite you to join us.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_prequest_09</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Cardinal_HM_prequest_b_01</Key>
    <Value>I’m just stopping by.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_prequest_10</Key>
    <Value>I see. I have a great deal of things to administrate, please do not bother me unless it’s important.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_prequest_11</Key>
    <Value>I have called on Elatt. He has been watching you, [PlayerName], and would like to speak with you. Pray to the altar at the back of the temple, and heed his wisdom.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_prequest_12</Key>
    <Value>There are three people I’m aware of that need some help. Ease the burdens of any one of them, and you will have proven to me that you are ready to join us.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_prequest_13</Key>
    <Value>Mofat, one of our oldest members, can be found in the residential area of Monsoon and is in need of a certain alchemy ingredient. Zephyrien, one of our Champions, is in this Temple and needs someone to brew a potion.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_prequest_14</Key>
    <Value>And then there’s Monsoon’s Chamberlord, Damian Lockwell, whose paranoia could use calming down. He is across that bridge to the right once you leave the temple. They’re all important to this city, so take the time to introduce yourself too.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_prequest_15</Key>
    <Value>Welcome to Elatt's Temple, traveller. Be at ease, all are welcome here.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Cardinal_HM_prequest_16</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorean_HM_prequest_01</Key>
    <Value>At attention Zephyrien, we have a guest! What do you need from us, pilgrim?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorean_HM_prequest_01_Z</Key>
    <Value>Hey there, do you need the help of a Champion? Just point me at the problem, and Soeran or I will take care of it!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Sorean_HM_prequest_a_01</Key>
    <Value>I'm considering joining the Holy Mission, actually.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorean_HM_prequest_02</Key>
    <Value>Let me take a look at you... I see potential there, but it's very much a gem in the rough. What do you think, Zephyrien?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorean_HM_prequest_03</Key>
    <Value>Yep, you'll do. You look like you can handle a good scrap. As long as you're joining us to help people, that's good enough for me, really.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Sorean_HM_prequest_a_03</Key>
    <Value>You're both Champions? I have trouble telling you apart with that armor.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorean_HM_prequest_04</Key>
    <Value>That's easy. I'm the one of us who actually bothers to wear the helmet. Also, I'm the one with the warhammer. It's more than just a weapon to kill things with, it's a tool to rebuild what we've lost.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorean_HM_prequest_05</Key>
    <Value>And I happen to believe that if you have to get into a fight, you don't go armed with a stick. You use maximum force to remove whatever passes for the threat's head, and resolve the problem right there.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Sorean_HM_prequest_a_05</Key>
    <Value>What is serving Elatt like?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorean_HM_prequest_06_Z</Key>
    <Value>It's amazing. Every day, we make a difference in people's lives. Bearing some small portion of a god's power in your very being is incredible.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorean_HM_prequest_06</Key>
    <Value>It's also very dangerous. You will need to lay your life on the line daily. The three Pillars demand self-sacrifice…it's not for the faint of heart!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorean_HM_prequest_07</Key>
    <Value>You will likely be following the missionary's path. Your tasks will take you to places far and wide, to deal with conflicts that need to be resolved.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Sorean_HM_prequest_a_07</Key>
    <Value>And what do Champions do?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorean_HM_prequest_08</Key>
    <Value>Elatt's Champions are the pinnacle of the missionary's path. We are blessed with great strength, to enforce the peace. Whether that's destroying invading Scourge monsters, or punishing bandits on a kidnapping spree.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorean_HM_prequest_09</Key>
    <Value>If you're thinking of replacing one of us, think again. Elatt may be powerful, but he's not omnipotent. He can only provide the raw energy needed for two Champions at any given time. And neither of us has any intention of retiring anytime soon.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Sorean_HM_prequest_b_03</Key>
    <Value>Well, nice meeting you both.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorean_HM_prequest_10</Key>
    <Value>Nice to meet you, Pilgrim. I hope our paths cross again sometime.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorean_HM_prequest_11_Z</Key>
    <Value>I hope to see you out there in the field, pilgrim! Take the dive and join us!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorean_HM_prequest_12</Key>
    <Value>I look forward to working with you, pilgrim. May Elatt welcome you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorean_HM_prequest_13_Z</Key>
    <Value>Hey, if you ever want to gain the power of magic, we have our own path to the Ley Line under the Conflux Mountain. If you need backup, I could take you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorean_HM_prequest_13</Key>
    <Value>I can definitely tell you’ve got the spirit for it, but one needs discipline to walk the martial path of the Holy Mission.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorean_HM_prequest_14</Key>
    <Value>Discipline... Right, that reminds me! I need a discipline potion. My stocks are low... If you could &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;bring me one, I'd be in your debt&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorean_HM_prequest_14-b</Key>
    <Value>If you can’t find one for me, it’s pretty easy to brew. I’ll give you the recipe scroll. I don't care if you brew it or buy it, personally.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Sorean_HM_prequest_d_14</Key>
    <Value>I have that discipline potion for you, Zephyrien.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorean_HM_prequest_15</Key>
    <Value>Perfect, this'll be a big help. I sometimes feel like can't even make it through the day without at least one of these!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Sorean_HM_prequest_16</Key>
    <Value>Hey, by way of thanks, do you want to know how to make a Warrior's Elixir? You need to put Larva eggs, Krimp nuts, Crystal powder and water into an alchemy set and steam it! It’s a real help when you’re preparing for a big fight.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Soeran_HM_Initial_1</Key>
    <Value>Greetings, traveler. You are welcome to find sanctuary with me for as long as you need to.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Zephyrien_HM_Initial_1</Key>
    <Value>Oh, a visitor! Welcome to the city of Monsoon! If you see any Scourge, let me know and I’ll clear them out, no problem!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Damian_HM_prequest_01</Key>
    <Value>I'm a busy man, visitor. If you don’t have business with me, move along.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Damian_HM_prequest_a_01</Key>
    <Value>I was told to introduce myself to you, and that you need some kind of help.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Damian_HM_prequest_02</Key>
    <Value>Oh, winds be damned, you're another stupid pilgrim aren't you? You listen to me, visitor, you can't trust Elatt. Do you know what happens to people who serve him? He puts just a little bit of his soul inside you, and it just grows and grows until you're not you anymore.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Damian_HM_prequest_03</Key>
    <Value>I had to watch as someone I loved drifted further and further away, and then left forever without even bothering to say goodbye, all for this supposed "god". I don't know what Elatt is, but he's definitely not divine. If it wasn't for my opposition, I have no doubt he'd have enslaved this entire swamp by now!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Damian_HM_prequest_a_03</Key>
    <Value>I'll keep what you said in mind.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Damian_HM_prequest_04</Key>
    <Value>Bah, if you bend your knee to Elatt, you soon won't have a mind to keep it in. Don't make that mistake.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Damian_HM_prequest_b_03</Key>
    <Value>The people of Monsoon owe you a lot.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Damian_HM_prequest_05</Key>
    <Value>Don't bother sweet-talking me, I don't care. If you value your free will, just stay as far away from that... "thing" as you can.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Damian_HM_prequest_c_03</Key>
    <Value>You're raving. Elatt is the only reason we beat back the Scourge!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Damian_HM_prequest_06</Key>
    <Value>Did he, though? It's awfully convenient for him that we have to depend on him to hold off the Scourge. How can we be sure he's not playing them like puppets to make us worship him? Trusting in him is foolish to the extreme.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Damian_HM_prequest_07</Key>
    <Value>You just remember my warning. Don’t offer your free will to Elatt, he’ll gobble it right up.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Damian_HM_prequest_08</Key>
    <Value>Look, you want to do something to help me? &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Become a mage&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. By being in tune with life's vibrations, you'll resist that... "thing's" influence far better than a normal person.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Damian_HM_prequest_09</Key>
    <Value>Heed my warning, pilgrim. Do not sell your free will to Elatt. If your heart is set on taking that risk, become a mage.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Damian_HM_prequest_10</Key>
    <Value>So, you're a fellow mage, are you? Well, don't say I didn't warn you... Here, a gift from one mage to another. Considering all the nasty animals crawling in the swamp, this recipe might save your life!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Damian_HM_prequest_11</Key>
    <Value>You know how to become a mage, right? You’ll need to travel to the Ley Line &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;underneath the Conflux Mountain in the Chersonese&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. I know one of Elatt’s Champions usually hangs around the Holy Mission’s entrance to help new recruits.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Damian_HM_prequest_12</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Damian_HM_prequest_13</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Damian_HM_prequest_14</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Damian_HM_prequest_15</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_01_a</Key>
    <Value>(Pray to catch Elatt’s attention.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_01_b</Key>
    <Value>(Offer a prayer to Elatt.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_01_c</Key>
    <Value>(Ask for guidance.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_01_d</Key>
    <Value>Elatt, I want to join the Holy Mission.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_01</Key>
    <Value>(A voice speaks in your head. It’s gruff, but kind.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_02</Key>
    <Value>Welcome, [PlayerName]. I am Elatt, god of discipline.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Ellat_HM_prequest_a_02</Key>
    <Value>I’m hearing voices in my head!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_03</Key>
    <Value>Well, yes. I am Living Thought. How else did you think I'd speak with you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Ellat_HM_prequest_b_02</Key>
    <Value>My lord! It's an honor to hear your voice!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_04</Key>
    <Value>There is no need for you to speak to me like that. I do not require reverence from my followers. Only their dedication. Even one good deed is worth more than a thousand words of worship.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Ellat_HM_prequest_c_02</Key>
    <Value>Alright, how do you do it? Is there a sorcerer hiding inside the altar?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_05</Key>
    <Value>Hah! Do you wish to check for yourself?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Ellat_HM_prequest_a_05</Key>
    <Value>Huh... It's totally solid. If this is a trick, it's very impressive.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_06</Key>
    <Value>Indeed. A trick so impressive I lost my physical form, becoming Living Thought. I assure you, I am the genuine article. No tricks here.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Ellat_HM_prequest_a_03</Key>
    <Value>You should know, Damian Lockwell is paranoid about you.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_07</Key>
    <Value>I am aware. He disappoints me, but he is free to come to his own conclusions. Only he has the power to change his views of me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Ellat_HM_prequest_b_03</Key>
    <Value>Do you think I have a place the Holy Mission?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_08</Key>
    <Value>I sense a certain potential in you...If you wish, I will accept you into my Holy Mission. But be warned, to accept my blessing is to become the mortal enemy of all Scourgekind. They will seek your destruction everywhere.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_09</Key>
    <Value>Always remember the three pillars of our cause. First, no one should suffer. Give of yourself, seek to ease the pains of others. Second, no one is perfect. Always work to improve yourself, in mind and body. Third, no one is safe. To protect Aurai, one must have iron discipline.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_10</Key>
    <Value>Above all, never do something you do not understand. You must think and question the world around you! Only then will achieve truth.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_11</Key>
    <Value>[PlayerName], will you cast aside all the ties that bind you, and live your life for the good of all people on Aurai, and become a shield against the Scourge and the Corruption?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Ellat_HM_prequest_a_11</Key>
    <Value>That depends. What happens when I join you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_12</Key>
    <Value>Ah, you are thinking. Good. If you join me, I will grant you a small portion of my essence, which will empower you to better protect others. However, the Scourge can sense it and will be driven to attack you, as they are driven to kill me.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Ellat_HM_prequest_b_11</Key>
    <Value>On second thought... I'm not ready for this.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_13</Key>
    <Value>That is your right. I confess that I'm disappointed. My offer stands, should you change your mind.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_14</Key>
    <Value>(You call out to Elatt, but you do not hear his voice... Will you pledge yourself to the Holy Mission?)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Ellat_HM_prequest_c_11</Key>
    <Value>Yes, I commit myself to your cause.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_15</Key>
    <Value>(You feel your spirit grow in strength. It's warm, like being close to a campfire.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_16</Key>
    <Value>Then it is done. I welcome you into my heart, [PlayerName] and grant you the title of Missionary. Do good in my name, and I shall do good by you. I reward those who prove their Love, Self-improvement, and Discipline with newfound power.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_16-b</Key>
    <Value>I shall grant you the power to bind light to your weapon. It is a spell, so if you wish to make use of it, you should head to the Holy Mission’s entrance on the Conflux Mountain in the Chersonese the next time your travels take you there.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_16-c</Key>
    <Value>Zephyrien often trains there, and may guide your through the path to the Ley Line, where you can gain the power of Mana. I am certain you will be called to visit the Chersonese on a mission soon enough.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_17</Key>
    <Value>Ellinara will give you tasks on my behalf. Speak with her from time to time, and she will tell you what needs doing. She is just outside my Temple’s entrance.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Ellat_HM_prequest_a_17</Key>
    <Value>So we aren't going to speak like this again?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_18</Key>
    <Value>To narrow my focus to any precise place or person blinds me to events going on everywhere else. To continue to protect Aurai, I must see the larger view.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_19</Key>
    <Value>If you prove your dedication to the cause, we shall speak again, as I bestow upon you new tools for your work.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_20</Key>
    <Value>Finally... I sense the potential of a great mage within you. Should you wish to open yourself up to Mana, seek our entrance to the Conflux Mountain. Zephyrien often travels there and will glady help.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_21</Key>
    <Value>(You do not hear Elatt’s voice from the altar, but you feel connected to it somehow, like a spider’s thread links you to it.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_22</Key>
    <Value>(As you reach out to Elatt, you see a a flash of a strange skeleton in a cave in the Chersonese...)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_23</Key>
    <Value>(As you reach out to Elatt, you see the Blue Chamber in Berg, with diplomats starting to gather for a meeting... You sense... worry.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_24</Key>
    <Value>(As you reach out to Elatt, you see Oliele in the slums of the Kingdom of Levant... You sense... equal parts curiosity and concern.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_25</Key>
    <Value>(As you reach out to Elatt, you see both Enmerkar and Abrassar, as if from very high up. You sense... burning righteous fury.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_26</Key>
    <Value>(As you reach out to Elatt, you see flashes of every region, as Elatt watches over Aurai. You sense... satisfaction.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_27</Key>
    <Value>(You feel like this is a major turning point in your life... &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;Will you dedicate yourself to the Holy Mission of Elatt&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;?)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_28</Key>
    <Value>(You sense nothing from the altar.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_29</Key>
    <Value>(As you reach out to Elatt, you see a campsite near a mountain along the Pilgrim Road. You sense... confusion and concern.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_30</Key>
    <Value>(An Altar to Elatt is placed here. If you wish to speak to him, this would be the place to do it.)</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Ellat_HM_prequest_31</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_prequest_01</Key>
    <Value>Oh! [PlayerName]! You came! How are you holding up?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_prequest_a_01</Key>
    <Value>I’m doing alright. How are things for you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_prequest_b_01</Key>
    <Value>The journey was a lot harder than I thought it would be. What about you?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_prequest_02</Key>
    <Value>I’ve joined the Holy Mission and spoken with Elatt himself. I’ve become a Missionary in his service. He is... a lot less formal than I expected. He hasn’t forgotten what it’s like to be human.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_prequest_03</Key>
    <Value>Have you given my previous words any thought? About joining the Holy Mission with me?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_prequest_a_03</Key>
    <Value>I’ve been thinking about it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Oliele_HM_prequest_b_03</Key>
    <Value>Not really. Joining the Holy Mission doesn’t really interest me that much.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_prequest_04</Key>
    <Value>Well, thanks for coming anyways. It’s nice to see a familiar face.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_prequest_05</Key>
    <Value>If you choose to join us, you should &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;speak with Cardinal Bourlamaque&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. He will ask Elatt to judge your worth. You’ll find him in the temple in the northern part of Monsoon.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_prequest_06</Key>
    <Value>Oh, I didn’t tell you, did I? I made the trip to the Conflux Mountain and opened myself to Mana. I’m glad Zephyrien had my back for that. It was a challenge.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_prequest_07</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_prequest_08</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Oliele_HM_prequest_09</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_prequest_01</Key>
    <Value>A new pilgrim, huh? It's good to see new blood come into the Holy Mission. I'm getting too old for active duty, shameful as that is. I miss the good old days when I could wallop a Scourge Beast with a mere quarterstaff!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Player_Mofat_HM_prequest_a_01</Key>
    <Value>How old are we talking?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_prequest_02</Key>
    <Value>I knew Elatt before he was a grown man. I can still remember a time before the Scourge, when Elatt and I would journey across Aurai without that threat hanging over us.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_prequest_03</Key>
    <Value>Bourlamaque sent you to help me, didn't he? Good timing too. My eyesight isn't what it used to be. Wandering around at night in the marsh is getting very difficult for me. And &lt;color=#00CCFF&gt;&lt;b&gt;I could really use some Firefly powder&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; for one of my experiments.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_prequest_04</Key>
    <Value>You know how to get firefly powder, right? Get some fireflies to follow you around and bring them to a kind of flat red flower. Then, collect the powder that the flower provides.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_prequest_05</Key>
    <Value>Ah, firefly powder! Exactly what I needed. Thank you, you've done good by me. Say... I’ll let you in on my secret recipe, my friend. Remember, moderation is the key. Drink this potion too often and you'll find yourself thinking in slow motion!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_prequest_06</Key>
    <Value>Watch yourself out in the Marsh. It’s never safe out there. Drop your guard for an instant and you’ll either be lizard food, or end up swimming in toxic water.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_prequest_06_a</Key>
    <Value>What’s on your mind?</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_prequest_06_b</Key>
    <Value>We need to talk about that trouble in the swamp.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_prequest_07</Key>
    <Value>I think I’ve tried every alchemical combination of ingredients in Aurai by this point. It’s hard to accept there may be no more discoveries!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_prequest_08</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_prequest_09</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_prequest_10</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_prequest_11</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Mofat_HM_prequest_12</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_prequest_01</Key>
    <Value>Welcome to the city of Monsoon, home of Elatt, the god of discipline. If you have any problems at all, or see a Scourge Beast of any kind, please let us know, and we will take care of it.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_prequest_02</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_prequest_03</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_prequest_04</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_prequest_05</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_prequest_06</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_prequest_07</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_prequest_08</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Elinara_HM_prequest_09</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Galira_HM_Initial_01</Key>
    <Value>Talk is cheap. I prefer action. Unless someone is in trouble, I don’t much care for small-talk.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Galira_HM_Initial_02</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Galira_HM_Initial_03</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>Galira_HM_Initial_04</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ZephyrienConflux_HM_Initial_1</Key>
    <Value>I’ve always enjoyed coming here. You can really feel the hum of Mana as it passes through the mountain. </Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ZephyrienConflux_HM_Initial_2</Key>
    <Value>Well, well, a visitor! Careful around this place, it’s full of nasty Troglodytes. If you want to get to the heart of the mountain, this is probably the quickest way, but also the most dangerous.</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ZephyrienConflux_HM_Initial_3</Key>
    <Value>If you want to go ahead, I’ll give you a hand. I’ll watch your back, Champion’s honor!</Value>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ZephyrienConflux_HM_Initial_4</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <Key>ZephyrienConflux_HM_Initial_5</Key>
    <Value />
  </Dialogue>
</ArrayOfDialogue>